<collection>

<!-- Achievements: IN GAME -->

	<c id="perle" name="Fountain Pearl">
		Using the pearl your Dinoz can recover health at the Fountain of Youth each day.
	</c>

	<c id="pteroz" name="Pteroz Trophy">
		The Pteroz Trophy is awarded to players who have defeated the strange Pteroz. It also unlocks the Pteroz in the Dinoz Shop.
	</c>

	<c id="hippo" name="Hippoclamps Trophy">
		The Hippoclamps Trophy is awarded to players who have defeated the wild Hippoclamp. It also unlocks Hippoclamps in the Dinoz Shop.
	</c>

	<c id="rocky" name="Rockies Trophy">
		The Rockies Trophy is awarded to players who have defeated the sleeping Rocky. It also unlocks Rockies in the Dinoz Shop.
	</c>

	<c id="quetzu" name="Quetzu Trophy">
		The Quetzu Trophyis given by Mandragore to players who have defeated the Archdorogon Grizorg. This allows you to buy Quetzu when you go to the Dinoz shop.
	</c>
	
	<c id="labowi" name="Trophée des Smogs">
		The Smogs Medallions were given out during the crisis of the Corrupted Laboratory. Unfortunately only one smmog was created during the quest.
	</c>

	<c id="tour" name="Dinoland Tour">
		This yellow shirt is awarded for your participation in the Dinoland Tour! You are now a Dinoland grand explorer.
	</c>

	<c id="vener" name="Venerable Eye">
		The Venerable Eye is an extremely rare item. Only the finest warriors can possess it! People say that it has incredibly powerful magical abilities.
	</c>

	<c id="taurus" name="Taurus the magnificent">
		You helped Baobob to dispatch Taurus, the infamous Moueffe, to the depths of the Dark World. You're not ready to meet him again yet, although word of your courage is already spreading throughout Dinoland.
	</c>

	<c id="belius" name="Belius the illustrious">
		You have defeated the powerful Belius, the infernal Santaz. He has been sent back to the depths of the Dark World.
	</c>
	
	<c id="scorp" name="Starship Scorpius">
		You've banished the infernal Winks Scorpius. He's been sent back to the Shadow World where he belongs!
	</c>

	<c id="no" name="Deactivated">
		A test item that nobody can have (allows you to block the special Dinoz).
	</c>

	<c id="msg" name="Official Dinoland Stamps">
		Send private messages with this unlimited supply of official Dinoland postal stamps.
	</c>

	<c id="magnet" name="Negative Lodestone Shard">
		This Negative Lodestone Shard was offered by the Rockies King himself! Who knows what mysterious powers it holds.
	</c>

	<c id="plume" name="Sidereal Feather">
		This feather, a gift from a distant traveller, allows you to edit presentation on the player tab as well as accessing the "roleplay" section in the forum.
	</c>

	<c id="kaura" name="Kabuki Aura">
		The Kabuki Aura gives you access to Totem Island where you may find Kabukis, survivors of the Huge Cataclysm!
	</c>

	<c id="demon" name="Demon Scroll">
		This ancient scroll gives you access to the Demon Shop in the Twilight Cemetary!
	</c>

	<c id="pmi" name="Illustrated Mission Guidebook">
		The Illustrated Mission Guidebook lets you see the list of missions which have been completed by your Dinoz, and which remain to be completed.
	</c>

	<c id="pda" name="Diamantite Pebble">
		The Diamantite Pebble is a stone which is packed with a naturally occurring array of elements which, when combined under pressure, allow the owner to see all their dinoz at a glance. The diamantite, on the other hand, is only for show.
	</c>

	<c id="fdjv1" name="FDJV 2010">
		Ce trophée remercie les joueurs ayant fait un long périple jusqu'au Festival du Jeu video édition 2010 pour rencontrer les marionnettistes de l'ombre !
	</c>
	
<!-- Achievements: NIMBAO -->

	<c id="dico1" name="Dictionary">
		A very old book, maybe it will help you solve a riddle? Unfortunately, for the time being, it is locked with a highly complex padlock.
		Is there someone who knows how to open this book perhaps? For the moment, it seems not...
	</c>

	<c id="dicarb" name="Arborian Dictionary">
		A very old book, which you have managed to open, maybe now it can be used to decipher the Arborian language.
	</c>

	<c id="caush" name="Mandragore Doll">
		A doll in the likeness of Mandragore, which can be used as a voodoo doll, punching-bag or a pillow, as you choose.
		It is in pretty poor condition, the previous owner must have taken their frustrations out on it on a regular basis.
	</c>

	<c id="fmedal" name="3-Eyed Medallion">
		You have reconstructed the medallion which allows you to access a new part of the celestial island of Nimbao.
		You must find the correct place to use this medallion in order to use the portal correctly.
	</c>
	
<!-- Achievements: CLAN WAR (old version of the Mana War before Thomas P changed) -->

	<!-- Clan War: 1 -->
	<c id="war1a" name="Warriors Necklace">
		This necklace was forged from a rare mineral and is a reward for the strongest warrior during the 1st Clan War!
	</c>

	<c id="war1b" name="Teknotik Stone">
		Rumours say that by touching this strange stone you can go mad causing strange behaviour. In any case the stone is very rare, reserved only for impressive Dinoz masters during the 1st Clan War!
	</c>

	<!-- Clan War: 2 -->	
	<c id="war2a" name="Darkness Triad">
		This jewel, composed of three blood gems set in an aura of darkness, is awarded to the best tacticians during the 2nd Clan War!
	</c>

	<c id="war2b" name="Nugget of Tawny-Amber">
		An piece of uncut tawny-amber, a highly valuable rare material, offered to Dinoz who showed remarkable bravery during the 2nd Clan War!
	</c>

	<!-- Clan War: 3 -->
	<c id="war3a" name="Infernal Trowel">
		Your talents as master builder of the castle have been recognised, and this enchanted trowel is awarded only to the best clans during the 3rd Clan War!
	</c>

	<c id="war3b" name="Jade Nail">
		This highly valuable nail, made entirely from jade, is offered to masters who have shown remarkable bravery during the 3rd Clan War!
	</c>
	
	<!-- Clan War: 4 -->
	<c id="war4a" name="Flaming Shield">
		This shield is given to Clans who crushed their enemies defences during the 4th Clan War!!
	</c>

	<c id="war4b" name="Stone of Orientation">
		The stone of orientation is given to Clans who have distinguished themselves during the 4th Clan War. The stone allows you to heal in the caves, but it's still only a stone, don't rely on it for directions.
	</c>

	<!-- ------------------------------No one has this on our server------------------------------- -->	
	<c id="war5a" name="Goblin Skull">
		By repeatedly destroying the castles of your enemies during the ?th Clan War, you hqve finally found a perfect 'Goblin Skull', congratulations !
	</c>

	<c id="war5b" name="Bewitched Bell">
		This rare magical bell is used to broadcast your accomplishments during the ?th Clan War. Perfect for impressing your friends, but unfortunately there isn't an 'OFF' switch!
	</c>

	<!-- Clan War: 5 -->	
	<c id="warfa" name="Mog Mug">
		This mug is bewitched by the spirit of a mog, which sings a ballad every hour to keep you awake, therefore allowing you to defend your clan at any time. It's a fitting reward for your awesome exploits in the 5th Clan War, even if there's a decent chance it'll end up gathering dust in a cupboard.
	</c>

	<c id="warfb" name="Chokokookie">
		It is said that Chokokookies are the Dorogons' snack of choice. You have been awarded this to thank you for your impressive contribution to the 5th Clan War. You have tried it, and it tastes like roast Korgon, only sweeter.
	</c>
	
	<c id="warfc" name="Korg Kup" ::ignore::>
		This cup was synthesized by melting down any Korgons found to be hoarding too much gold. It is special in that it amplifies the effects of its contents, like the caffeine in the coffee curently contained within. An impressive reward for a great performance in the 5th Clan War.
	</c>

	<!-- ------------------------------No one has this on our server------------------------------- -->	
	<c id="warga" name="Arm'or">
		Gold armour - commonly called Arm'or' is very useful for parades and festivals. Unfortunately it's not very effective in fights. It is only awarded to winners of the ?th Clan War.
	</c>

	<c id="wargb" name="Demyon Boots">
		You have received the Demyon Boots for your participation in the ?th Clan War. No longer will your Dinoz get blisters on their feet while attacking enemy castles.
	</c>

	<!-- ------------------------------No one has this on our server------------------------------- -->	
	<c id="warha" name="An'or">
		A gold ring, studded with three rubies "one ring to destroy them all" is engraved in small writing on the inside. Only the winners of the ?th Clan War deserve to wear it !
	</c>

	<c id="warhb" name="Na'arg">
		A pale blue ring, given as a reward to clan members following their exploits during the ?th Clan War... legends tell of certain people going crazy upon removing it...
	</c>
	
	<!-- Clan War: 6 -->	
	<c id="waria" name="Sparkling Samurai">
		For winning the 6th Clan War, you have been awarded this samurai helmet! Its previous owner was a powerful shogun who won countless battles, the helmet striking fear in the very hearts of the enemies who saw it.
		Unfortunately, it is just too shiny to be worn in battles.
	</c>

	<c id="warib" name="Ghost Samurai">
		The ghost samurai helmet is reputed to guard the souls of warriors who fought against it on the battlefield. it is the proof of your considerable achievements in the 6th Clan War.
		However, these helmets are now purely decorative, as it is impossible to wear the helmet without hearing the screams of the ghosts within...
	</c>

	<c id="waric" name="Errant Knight">
		You have found a helmet belonging to someone who participated in a great war. It is proof of your valiant conduct during the 6th Clan War.
		This helmet is of poor quality, so it's not that surprising that the soldier who wore it was defeated by their enemy.
	</c>

<!-- Achievements: MANA WAR-->
	
	<!-- Mana War: 1 -->	
	<c id="warja" name="Sword of Mana">
		This sword holds a great secret. According to legend, it was broken during an epic combat in an ancient war.
		Its blade was forged in the purest crystalised mana. You have been awarded this sword for winning the 1st Mana War.
	</c>

	<c id="warjb" name="Mana Capsule">
		Having received sufficient quantities of mana during the 1st Mana War, the king authorised you to keep some in a sealed chest to reward you for your extraordinary efforts during these troubled times.
	</c>

	<c id="warjc" name="Ice Flame">
		It is quite rare that a drop of Mana crystalises at the bottom of the storage reservoirs. Once this forms, the Mana can no longer be used as energy, but the object itself is sufficiently rare to attract dedicated collectors. It is a beautiful trophy which was awarded to you for your valiant performance in the 1st Mana War.
	</c>
	
	<!-- Mana War: 2 -->	
	<c id="warka" name="MiniDjinn">
		Baby Djinn is a powerful being, valuable ally on the battlefield, it will decimate your enemies when fully grown... which should be in a few hundred years!
		You have been awarded MiniDjinn for winning the 2nd Mana War.
	</c>

	<c id="warkb" name="Minifrit">
		Baby Ifrit is hot-blooded, and will engulf your enemies in flames when fully grown... which should be in a few hundred years!
		You have been awarded Minifrit for putting in an excellent performance in the 2nd Mana War;
	</c>

	<c id="warkc" name="Miniggdra">
		A young shoot of the powerful Yggdrasil fell at your feet during a ferocious battle during the 2nd Mana War. Once fully grown, Miniggdra will will get ever bigger and better, taking you even closer to legend status!
	</c>

	<!-- Mana War: 3 -->		
	<c id="warla" name="Vertiginous Citadel">
		This vestige of a bygone civilisation now floats aimlessly in the skies. The King has given it to you in the hope that you'll do the housework from time to time...
		Watch out though, the generator will only work for around a century, after which time the citadel will crash to earth on Dinoland.
		In any case, it has been given to you in recognition of your triumph in the 3rd Mana War.
	</c>

	<c id="warlb" name="Jade Palace">
		You have won an unforgettable stay in the tower room of the extravagant Jade Palace, which offers magnificent views over all of Dinoland.
		This stay has been awarded to you in recognition of your performance in the 3rd Mana War!
	</c>

	<c id="warlc" name="Floating Island">
		The King has rewarded you with a stay in the unspoiled floating islands. You will have to tidy the place up a bit after you recover from the 3rd Mana War.
	</c>

	<!-- ------------------------------No one has this on our server------------------------------- -->	
	<c id="warma" name="The Burger of Champions">
		The King's head chef has prepared his speciality for you. This hamburger is reserved exclusively for the elite warriors of the ?th Great Mana War.
		Only a few masters have ever tasted this culinary delight.
	</c>

	<c id="warmb" name="Gromster Ribsteak">
		In recognition of a terrific performance in the ?th Great Mana War, the King's head chef has prepared one if the finest Gromster Nimbao Ribsteaks you will ever experience.
		Once you've sampled a few, you start to appreciate the effort required to transport the whole thing to Dinotown in one piece.
	</c>

	<c id="warmc" name="Roast Coq">
		The giant chickens are not rare, but when the King's head chef gets a hold of one it becomes very much something out of the ordinary.
		This will delight your senses after a great effort in participating in the ?th Great Mana War.
	</c>

	<!-- ------------------------------No one has this on our server------------------------------- -->	
	<c id="warna" name="Shrimp Helmet">
		This unique relic, forged by the most famous blacksmith in Dinoland, pays tribute to a great dinoz master. This was awarded to you for winning the ?th Mana War. The last war of the Epoqalypse!
	</c>

	<c id="warnb" name="Ring of Sushi">
		Forged at the very heart of Dinoville Castle, this ring allows the wearer to see life through rose-tinted glasses and to smell of fish, it was awarded to you in recognition of your performance in the ?th Mana War. The last war of the Epoqalypse!
	</c>

	<c id="warnc" name="Maki Belt">
		Never go to war without your belt on, and if you get really hungry, no problem, easily portable, it can even double as a pillow. Enjoy your prize for participating in the ?th Mana War. The last war of the Epoqalypse!
	</c>

	<!-- Mana War: 4 -->		
	<c id="waroa" name="Portrait of an old sensualist">
		This portrait of a famous martial arts master (an old acquaintance of master Zenith it seems) comes to you for your victory
		in the 4th Mana War. May his face show you the the way in battle.
	</c>

	<c id="warob" name="Portrait of a crafty cat">
		This portrait of a powerful martial arts master is offered to you for your valiant efforts in the 4th Mana War.
		If one day your paths should cross, do not accept anything he offers you to drink... Your life depends on it!
	</c>

	<c id="waroc" name="Portrait of a man with empty eyes">
		This portrait of an enigmatic man is offered to you for your active participation in the 4th Mana War.
		His advice is worth its weight in gold but his thoughts are impenetrable.
	</c>

	<!-- Mana War: 5 -->
	<c id="warpa" name="Shiva, lord of destruction">
		This miniature statue was fashioned on the image of an all powerful god. Did he create another world beyond the realm of Dinoland? Nobody knows… 
		The destruction and creation of entire worlds, not mere castles, are his concern. It is given to you for having won the 5th Mana War.
	</c>
	
	<c id="warpb" name="Ganesh, lord of wisdom">
		This miniature statue is the embodiment of wisdom, intelligence and prudence. It is given to you as proof of your valour and courage during the 5th Mana War.
	</c>
	
	<c id="warpc" name="Ananta, lord of the nagas">
		This miniature statue of an immense serpent signifies the eternal and the infinite. Just like your courage, it has no limits. It is given to you for your active participation in the 5th Mana War.
	</c>

	<!-- Mana War: 6 -->
	<c id="warqa" name="Illumiating Doll">
		This little guy lights up the dark when you need him to. It's proabably wise to avoid giving him a hug at this moment.
		It is given to you for you victory in the 6th Mana War.
	</c>
	
	<c id="warqb" name="Flamable Doll">
		Whatever you do, don't try and grab him by the tail! You'll regret it... The resourceful dino masters will no doubt see his application as a portable lighter.
		It's offered to you for proving your valor during the 6th Mana War.
	</c>
			
	<c id="warqc" name="Drenched Doll">
		A living breathing sprinkler, this little guy is fantastic for those sweltering summer days, fill the pool or power your water fountain with this bubbling geiser of hapiness.
		It's offered to you for your participation in the 6th Mana War!
	</c>
	
	<!-- Mana War: 7 -->
	<c id="warra" name="Magic Lantern">
		This lantern lights up in the dark when it senses danger. Keep it close to hand, it could help you in a distant war.
		It is given to you for your victory in the 7th Mana War!
	</c>
	
	<c id="warrb" name="Oil lamp">
		Great for snatching a smoke break on those long watches on the wall of your clan castle. Might be useful for toasting marshmallows too.
		It is given to you for showing your worth in the 7th Mana War.
	</c>
	
	<c id="warrc" name="Little lantern">
		A nice little night light that will surely come in handy during those late night inter-clan role plays.
		It will forever remind you of the 7th Mana War...
	</c>
	
	<!-- Mana War: 8 -->
	<c id="warsa" name="Freeman Vigilante">
		This defensive military turret rewards your flamboyant victory in the 8th Mana War! Entirely reprogramable, it should come in handy against any extraterrestrial invaders too...
	</c>
	
	<c id="warsb" name="Testroom Vigilante">
		This surveilance turret is a reward for your bravery during the 8th Manna War. Thanks to her smooth clean lines and modern design, she'll be at home in your lounge room.
	</c>
	
	<c id="warsc" name="Fortress Vigilante">
		This turret as sexy as it is merciless is a reward for your participation in the 8th Mana War. Also available in blue.
	</c>
	
	<!-- Mana War: 9 -->
	<c id="warta" name="Mjöllnir">
		This 240volt hammer rewards your outrageous victory in the 9th Mana War. Great for hammering nails or recharging a smartphone
	</c>
	
	<c id="wartb" name="Obsidian Axe">
		This axe is given to you in recognition for your bravery during the 9th Mana War. Forged in the heart of Mt Tongariro, it will resist the fire of your success. 
	</c>
	
	<c id="wartc" name="Lodbrok Axe">
		This axe, direct from the colder regions of Dinoland seems to have spent a bit of time cutting up red fruits... You've earned it through your participation in the 9th Mana War.
	</c>
	
	<!-- Mana War: 10 -->
	<c id="warua" name="Diamond Ore">
		This little lump of ore is loaded with diamonds and represents your victory in the 10th Mana War! If you ever come across hard times you can always sell one or two of these shiny little rocks...
	</c>
	
	<c id="warub" name="The cubic coffer">
		This little chest, sealed for all eternity, represents your bravery in the 10th Mana War! If you ever manage to get it open, who knows what you'll find within...
	</c>
	
	<c id="waruc" name="Gaia">
		A little bit of the land of the Titans is given to you for your participation in the 10th Mana War! Let it serve as a warning to be vigilant of usurpers...
	</c>
	
	<!-- TODO -->
	
	<c id="warva" name="Chaussure à pointe">
		Cette chaussure à pointe en mithril récompense votre incroyable victoire à la 13ème guerre du Mana.
	</c>
	<c id="warvb" name="Chausson ninja">
		Ce chausson ninja furtif récompense votre bravoure sur cette 13ème guerre du mana.
	</c>
	<c id="warvc" name="Sandale Sparte">
		Cette sandale sparte à la mode est le symbole de votre courage à la 13ème guerre du mana.
	</c>
	
	<c id="warwa" name="Collier de diamant">
		ce collier de diamant récompense votre incroyable victoire à la 14ème guerre du Mana.
	</c>
	<c id="warwb" name="Collier aurifère">
		Ce ce collier aurifere 6000 carrats récompense votre bravoure sur cette 14ème guerre du mana.
	</c>
	<c id="warwc" name="Collier Sélénites">
		Un collier en pierre de lune est le symbole de votre courage à la 14ème guerre du mana.
	</c>
	
	<c id="warxa" name="Grenade étourdissante d'apparat">
		Cette grenade récompense votre assomante victoire à la 15ème guerre du Mana.
	</c>
	<c id="warxb" name="Bombe d'huile de collection">
		Cette bombe d'huile de ricin antique récompense votre bravoure sur cette 15ème guerre du mana.
	</c>
	<c id="warxc" name="Grenade de Damas">
		cette grenade remplie de salpêtre aromatique est le symbole de votre courage explosif à la 15ème guerre du mana.
	</c>
	
	<c id="warya" name="Coeur de la guerre">
		Ce coeur vaillant récompense votre incroyable victoire à la 16ème guerre du Mana.
	</c>
	<c id="waryb" name="Oeil d'Odin">
		Cet oeil divin récompense votre bravoure sur cette 16ème guerre du mana.
	</c>
	<c id="waryc" name="Rognon martial">
		Ce rein  de champ de bataille est le symbole de votre courage à la 16ème guerre du mana.
	</c>
	
	<c id="warza" name="Orbe du tourment">
		Cet orbe ténébreux récompense votre incroyable victoire à la 17ème guerre du Mana.
	</c>
	<c id="warzb" name="Orbe de glace">
		Cet orbe en glace du Mont Blanc récompense votre bravoure sur cette 17ème guerre du mana.
	</c>
	<c id="warzc" name="Orbe de feu">
		Cet orbe de feu grégeois est le symbole de votre courage à la 17ème guerre du mana.
	</c>
		
	
<!-- Achievements: CHAMPIONSHIP OF THE CLANS (COTC) -->

	<!-- COTC: 1 -->
	<c id="ch1x1a" name="Pro League Gold Cup">
		This cup is awarded to the winners of the Pro League in the 1st Championship of the Clans : only true champions have one !
	</c>

	<c id="ch1x1b" name="Pro League Silver Cup">
		This cup is awarded to clans from the Pro League that made it to the final phases of the 1st Championship of the Clans : a reward for a truly impressive feat !
	</c>

	<c id="ch1x2a" name="Intermediate League Gold Cup ">
		This cup is awarded to the winners of the Intermediate League in the 1st Championship of the Clans : It is a prestigious distinction only given to solid players !
	</c>

	<c id="ch1x2b" name="Intermediate League Bronze Cup">
		This cup is awarded to clans from the Intermediate League that made it to the final phases of the 1st Championship of the Clans : not an easy award to win !
	</c>

	<c id="ch1x3a" name="Little League Cup" ::ignore::>
		This trophy is awarded to the winners of the Little League in the 1st Championship of the Clans : we hope to see you in the Intermediate league next season!
	</c>

	<c id="ch1x3b" name="Little League Chalice" ::ignore::>
		This trophy is awarded to clans from the Little League who made it to the final phases of the 1st Championship of the Clans!
	</c>

	<!-- ------------------------------No one has this on our server------------------------------- -->
	<c id="ch2x1a" name="Pro League Gold Cup">
		This cup is to reward the participants of the Pro League in the 2nd Championship of the Clans: reserved for players with a thirst for blood and action!
	</c>

	<c id="ch2x2a" name="Amateur League Silver Cup">
		This trophy is to reward those who won it all in the Amateur League of the 2nd Championship of the Clans: congratulations from everyone on the jury!
	</c>

	<c id="ch2x2b" name="Amateur League Amethyst Cup">
		This trophy is to reward those from the Amateur League who made it to the final phases of the 2nd Championship of the Clans!
	</c>

	<c id="ch2x3a" name="Little league Gold Cup">
		This trophy is to reward those who won it all in the Little League of the 2nd Championship of the Clans: we hope to see you in the Amateur League next time!
	</c>

	<c id="ch2x3b" name="Little League Silver Cup">
		This trophy is to reward those from the Little League who made it to the final phases of the 2nd Championship of the Clans!
	</c>

	<!-- ------------------------------No one has this on our server------------------------------- -->
	<c id="ch3x1a" name="Dinocolada Sunrise">
		It's time to hit the beach! As a winner of the Elite League of the 3rd Championship of the Clans, you can enjoy feeling like a true champion, sipping a Dinocolada Sunrise - the drink of champions!
	</c>

	<c id="ch3x1b" name="Strawberry Dinocolada">
		Making it to the finals of the Elite League of the 3rd Championship of the Clans is no mean feat. There's nothing like a sneaky Strawberry Dinocolada to unwind after your recent activity!
	</c>

	<c id="ch3x2a" name="Honey Victorcake">
		The dedication required to win the Pro League of the 3rd Championship of the Clans deserves to be rewarded. You definitely deserve a Honey Victorcake to get your strength back before the next event!
	</c>

	<c id="ch3x2b" name="Pistachio Victorcake">
		It takes guts even to sign up for the Pro League of the Championship of the Clans, and even more to get to the final phases of the 3rd Championship! This succulent Pistachio Victorcake makes it all worthwhile.
	</c>

	<c id="ch3x3a" name="Gilded Caramel Log">
		The dedication required to win the Pro League of the 3rd Championship of the Clans deserves to be rewarded. You definitely deserve a Gilded Caramel Log to get your strength back before the next event!
	</c>

	<c id="ch3x3b" name="Caramel Log">
		It takes guts even to sign up for the Amateur League of the Championship of the Clans, and even more to get to the final phases of the 3rd Championship! This tasty Caramel Log makes it all worthwhile.
	</c>

	<c id="ch3x4a" name="Hard Boiled Golden Egg">
		This trophy is awarded to the winners of the Little League in the 3rd Championship of the Clans: we look forward to seeing your in the Amateur League next time!
	</c>

	<c id="ch3x4b" name="Hard Boiled Bluish Egg">
		This trophy is to reward the Little League clan members who made it to the final phases of the 3rd Championship of the Clans!
	</c>

	<!-- ------------------------------No one has this on our server------------------------------- -->
	<c id="ch4x1a" name="Supernova">
		A young, bright sun, a recognised symbol of power is given as the reward for winning the Elite League in the 4th Championship of the Clans. May the force burn within you as strongly !
	</c>

	<c id="ch4x1b" name="Crimson Sun">
		As a finalist of the Elite League in the 4th Championship, you have been awarded this sun which will remain powerful and majestic for the rest of its life..
	</c>

	<c id="ch4x2a" name="Spirit of Fire">
		You are the Champion of the Pro League of the 4th Championship. The spirit of fire burns within you and this trophy represents that fire and the courage you have demonstrated.
	</c>

	<c id="ch4x2b" name="Will-o'-the-wisp">
		To make it to the finals of the Pro League in the 4th Championship takes guts and committment. The flame of hope burns within you like never before.
	</c>

	<c id="ch4x3a" name="Dark Flame">
		You surely had to make some sacrifices to become the champion of the Intermediate League of the 4th Championship, so you have been rewarded with a flickering shadow flame as a token of your achievement.
	</c>

	<c id="ch4x3b" name="Blue Flame">
		Just to sign up for the Intermediate League of the 4th Championship takes guts, and for making it to the final stages, you have been awarded a bright blue flame.
	</c>

	<c id="ch4x4a" name="Cinders">
		This trophy is to congratulate the winners of the Little League in the 4th Championship of the Clans. These are the remains of a once powerful fireball.
	</c>

	<c id="ch4x4b" name="Ashes">
		This trophy is to thank the participants of the 4th Clan Championship who made it to  of the final phase of the Little League !
	</c>
	
	<!-- COTC: 2 -->
	<c id="ch5x1" name="Radiant Seedling">
		You have been presented with a young seedling taken from the grounds of the Archdorogon's palace in recognition of your performance in the 2nd Championship of the Clans.
	</c>

	<c id="ch5x2" name="Sacred Shrub">
		You have been presented with a small shrub taken from the Archdorogon's private greenhouse for successfully claiming 5 victories in the 2nd Championship of the Clans.
	</c>

	<c id="ch5x3" name="Celestial Bonsaï">
		You have been awarded an impressive bonsaï tree, from the Archdorogon's personal collection for managing to win 6 battles during the 2nd Championship of the Clans.
	</c>

	<c id="ch5x4" name="Majestic Tree">
		A magnificent tree which grew in the private gardens of the Archdorogon has been given to you in recognition of your flawless record in the 2nd Championship of the Clans.
	</c>

	<!-- ------------------------------No one has this on our server------------------------------- -->
	<c id="chfx1" name="Gold Figurine">
		You were awarded this massive gold-plated figurine for being the most powerful Clan in the 6th Championship of the Clans. She represents brute force, the absolute power which allows you to crush your enemies and establish your supremacy.
	</c>

	<c id="chfx2" name="Silver Figurine">
		You were awarded this silver-plated figurine for being one of the top 5 clans in the 6th Championship of the Clans. She represents the strategy and wisdom which allowed you to defeat your enemies, all the time bearing in mind that violence is not the only way to defeat edversaries.
	</c>

	<c id="chfx3" name="Bronze Figurine">
		You were awarded this bronze-coloured figurine to commemorate your performance in the 6th Championship of the Clans. She represents dynamism and discipline, which allow you to floor your enemies in a flash.
	</c>

	<c id="chfx4" name="Plastic Figurine">
		This plastic figurine was awarded to you for your performance in the 6th Championship of the Clans. She represents courage and self-sacrifice, essential traits necessary for opening the gates to the pantheon of Dinoland!
	</c>
	
	<!-- COTC 3 -->
	<c id="chgx1a" name="Mercenary">
		This figurine of a mercenary, selling his services for a noble cause, has been awarded to you for your performance in the Pro league of the 3rd Championship of the clans.
	</c>

	<c id="chgx1b" name="Celestial Hero">
		This figurine of the celestial hero, the extraordinary warrior battling for peace and destroying the most evil of demons with one thrust of his sword, has been given to you in recognition of your victory in the Pro league in the 3rd Championship of the clans.
	</c>

	<c id="chgx2a" name="Magician">
		This figurine of a magician, who thanks to his powerful spells which render the most aggressive monsters dosile, has been given to you in recognition of your performance in the Amateur league in the 3rd Championship of the clans.
	</c>

	<c id="chgx2b" name="Elven Sorceror">
		This figurine of a high ranking Elven Sorceror, capable of detroying entire regiments of monsters using powerful ancient magic, has been awarded to you in recognition of your victory in the Amateur league of the 3rd Championship of the clans.
	</c>

	<!-- ------------------------------No one has this on our server------------------------------- -->
	<c id="chgx3a" name="Martial Artist">
		This figurine of a martial artist has been awarded to you for your participation in the final phases of the medium league of the 7th Championship of the Clans.
	</c>

	<c id="chgx3b" name="Berserker">
		This figurine of a warrier, who turned mad with rage by the bloody battles in which he fought, has been awarded to you for winning the medium league of the 7th Championship of the Clans.
	</c>

	<c id="chgx4a" name="Ancient Warrier">
		This figurine of a now retired warrier has been awarded to you for your participation in the final phases of the starter league of the 7th Championship of the Clans.
	</c>

	<c id="chgx4b" name="Chaplain">
		This spiritual figure, invaluable healer and essential team member, has been awarded to you for winning the starter league of the 7th Championship of the Clans.
	</c>

	<!-- COTC: 4 -->
	<c id="chhx1a" name="Long-forgotten Joypad">
		This vestige of a forgotten civilization has been awarded to you for your participation in the Pro League of the 4th Championship of the clans. The wear and tear on this object shows that it was heavily used for some time before giving up the ghost.
	</c>

	<c id="chhx1b" name="Legendary Joypad">
		This long-forgotten hobby gadget was a limited edition cast in solid gold. It has been awarded to you for winning the Pro final of the 4th Championship of the clans. This object is extremely precious as it remained in perfect condition over the years.
	</c>

	<c id="chhx2a" name="Unknown Joypad">
		A mysterious aura emanates from this sculpture. The instant you start to recognize it, the memory vanishes. It has been awarded to you in recognition of your participation in the final phase of the Amateur League of the 4th Championship of the clans.
	</c>

	<c id="chhx2b" name="Three-handed Deluxe Joypad">
		This strange sculpture is the product of a disturbed spirit, in spite of this it has conserved an extraordinary aura. You have been awarded this prize for winning the final of the Amateur League in the 4th Championship of the clans.
	</c>

	<c id="chhx3a" name="Super Second-hand Controller">
		This strange object has been awarded to you in recognition of your performance in the Starter League of the 4th Championship of the Clans. This was the work of a renowned sculpter who had a fantasmagorical vision of a world governed by technology...
	</c>

	<c id="chhx3b" name="Ancestral Super Controller">
		This object must have brough joy to millions in its day. It has been awarded to you for winning the Starter League of the 4th Championship of the Clans. If only we knew how to use the thing.
	</c>

	<c id="chhx4a" name="Part-time Controller">
		This lump of plastic, remnants of an ancient civilisation, is given to you for you participation in the finals of the Starter League of the 8th Championship of the Clans! The markings on the device show that it was used regularly before giving up the ghost.
	</c>

	<c id="chhx4b" name="Ancestral Controller">
		With it's origins in a civilisation that knew of the art of gaming, this object is given to you for you victory in the Starter League of the 8th Championship of the Clans. Incredibly the thing still works! Proof of it's reliability...
	</c>
	
	<!-- COTC: 5 -->
	<c id="chix1a" name="YooEmmDee Disk Reader">
		This relic from a civilization which disappeared a long time ago was awarded to you in recognition of your participation in the Pro League of the 5th Championship of the Clans.
		Unimaginable power in the palm of your hand, you could even watch Paradino Festival movies on it but everyone made fun of it...
	</c>

	<c id="chix1b" name="ThreeDee Monolith">
		This entertainment machine was awarded to you for winning the Pro League of the 5th Championship of the Clans.
		Proof positive that it's always possible to succeed, even if you're wearing blue salopettes and a red helmet! Warning, causes dizziness and damages sight.
	</c>

	<c id="chix2a" name="Black Block">
		This monster, when you actually got it to work, you had to make the most of it rather than risk turning it off again. A luxury gadget and no mistake.
		It was awarded to you in recognition of your participation in the Amateur League of the 5th Championship of the Clans.
	</c>

	<c id="chix2b" name="Super Monolith">
		The renaissance of what we liked to call the monolith back in the day. As solid as it ever was, and just as incredible!
		It was awarded to you for winning the Amateur League of the 5th Championship of the Clans.
	</c>

	<c id="chix3a" name="Forgotten Machine">
		This bizarre object was awarded to you in recognition of your participation in the Starter League of the 5th Championship of the Clans.
		Some really loved this piece of kit apparently, but we don't even know what it is.
	</c>

	<c id="chix3b" name="Grey Monolith">
		This object was the pride and joy of millions back in its day. It was awarded to you for winning the Starter League of the 5th Championship of the Clans.
		A catchy tune from years gone by resurfaces in your head... Ta da da da da dada... tuuuut...
	</c>

	<c id="chix4b" name="Play & Watch">
		This little bit of eternal plastic from an oil obsessed civilisation is given to you for your participation in the Finals of the Starter League of the 5th Championship of the Clans.
		On the back there are two hollow places inficating that there might be two cylindrical objects that goe with it... What could they have been?
	</c>

	<c id="chix4a" name="TamagoDino">
		Issu d'une civilisation antique qui avait l'art du jeu, cet objet vous est offert pour avoir remporté la finale de la ligue Starter du 5th Championnat des clans.
		Certains prétendent que cet objet contiendrait une archive des premiers dinoz de Dinoland, ils passaient leur temps à dormir parait-il...
	</c>
	
	<!-- COTC: 6 -->
	<c id="chjx1a" name="Fireball">
		This trophy is given to you in recognition of your participation in the finales of the Pro League during the 6th Championship of the Clans!
	</c>
	
	<c id="chjx1b" name="Golden Star">
		This trophy is offered to you for your victory in the final of the Pro League of the 6th Championship of the Clans! 
		While you may feel invincible wearing it, don't take any unnecessary risks, lest you fall from on high...
	</c>
	
	<c id="chjx2a" name="Gold coin">
		This trophy is given to you for your participation in the finales of the Amateur League during the 6th Championship of the Clans!
		A coin so lucky even Buddah's belly can't compare!
	</c>
	
	<c id="chjx2b" name="Toadstool">
		This trophy is offered to you for your victory in the final of the Amateur League of the 6th Championship of the Clans!
		Legend has it that those who bite into this friendly little mushroom will double in size for one whole day. Highly sought-after by those measuring less than 1 metre...
	</c>
	
	<c id="chjx3a" name="The Inhabited Shell">
		This trophy is given to you for your participation in the finales of the Starter League during the 6th Championship of the Clans!
		The tortoise that inhabits this shell no longer dares to stick his neck out, for fear of being projected into a wall at speed!
	</c>
	
	<c id="chjx3b" name="Angry Shrrom">
		This little figuring is offered to you for your victory in the final of the Starter League of the 6th Championship of the Clans!
		It has been said that it brings luck to jump on this mushrooms head...
	</c>

	<!-- COTC BLITZ: 1 (7th COTC) -->
    <c id="chkx1b" name="Cloudy sword">
		You have earned this sword through your participation in the final phase of the 7th Championship of the Clans. 
		In case any trouble brews with you neighbouring Dino Master, just flash this baby... That ought to calm things down.
    </c>
    
    <c id="chkx1a" name="Chocobo">
		This trophy signifies your victory in the 7th Championship of the Clans. This will make people think twice whe you enter the battle...
    </c>
    
    <c id="chkx2b" name="Tomberry">
        This object is yours for your aprticipation in the finals of the 7th Championship of the Clans.
        This will settle most arguments... Better to be on your good side.
    </c>
    
    <c id="chkx2a" name="Mog">
        This is yours for your victory in the 7th Championship of the Clans.
       This shows you for the master strategist that you are. The inexperienced would do well to heed your words.
    </c>
    
    <c id="chkx3b" name="Magician">
       This object is given to you for your participation in the starter league of the 7th Championship of the Clans.
        An object that sums up your participation in one word: Magic!
    </c>
    
    <c id="chkx3a" name="Pampa">
       This is only for the winners of the starter league of the 7th Championship of the Clans.
        Your motto in life is: We came, we saw, we conquered. 
    </c>
	
	<!-- COTC BLITZ: 2 (8th COTC) -->
	<c id="chlx1b" name="Arabalest of Participation">
		This arbalest had been awarded to you in recognition of your participation in the finals of the Elite League of the __ Clan Championship!
	</c>
	
	<c id="chlx1a" name="Sharp Shooter">
		This incredible trophy represents your skill. As the winner of the __ Championship of the Clans, you've earned it! 
		Will you be able to make it happen again next time?
	</c>
	
	<c id="chlx2b" name="Shadow bow">
		This trophy marks your participation in the finals of the Pro League in the __ Championship of the Clans.
	</c>
	
	<c id="chlx2a" name="Apollo's bow">
		A badge of honour. This trophy marks you as the winner of the Pro League in the __ Championship of the Clans. 
		With this you're ready to take on the elites...
	</c>
	
	<c id="chlx3b" name="Long Bow">
		This bow shows your dedication and marks you as a participant in the finals of the Starter League of the __ Championship of the Clans.
	</c>
	
	<c id="chlx3a" name="Recurve bow">
		This bow denotes the champions of the Starter League in the __ Championship of the Clans. 
		A favourite of the inhabitants of the Steppes, this will help you as you continue towards the Pro League.
	</c>
	
	<!-- COTC BLITZ: 3 (9th COTC) -->
	<c id="chmx1b" name="Frozen Claw">
		This relic was awarded to you for your participation in the finals of the Elite league of the 9th Championship of the Clans.
		Frozen claw, cool down your enemies, or your cola.
	</c>
	
	<c id="chmx1a" name="Cutting Claw">
		This incredible trophy marks your victory in the final of the Elite league of the 9th Championship of the Clans.
		Made from a special herb found growing only in secret locations of Dinoland, it's sure to be a 'knock out' for your enemies and your friends alike!
	</c>
	
	<c id="chmx2b" name="Shark Dagger">
		This dagger shows your dedication in reaching the finals of the Pro Leage of the 9th Championship of the Clans.
		Made from sharks teeth it's fantastic for carving a path in battle or through your beard.
	</c>
	
	<c id="chmx2a" name="Lava Dagger">
		You've received this wonderful dagger for your incredible victory in the Pro League of the 9th Championship of the Clans.
		A flaming knife which cuts and cauterises at the same time, ideal for those DIY amputations.
	</c>
	
	<c id="chmx3b" name="Styletto">
		This trophy was given to you for your valiant effort in reaching the finals of the Starter League of the 9th Championship of the Clans.
		A simple weapon. Stick 'em with the pointy end...
	</c>
	
	<c id="chmx3a" name="Damascus">
		This oriental dagger is offered to you for your victory in the Starter League of the 9th Championship of the Clans.
		Made of Damasc Steel, this is the perfect weapon for those sushi parties you seem to love so much...
	</c>
	
	<!-- COTC BLITZ: 4 (10th COTC) -->
	<c id="chnx1b" name="Magma Shield">
		This little figurine is yours after you prved your wprth reaching the finals of the Elite Leage of the 10th Championship of the Clans.
		A shield that works perfectly with the Lava Dagger... Oh you, you don't have that? What a shame...
	</c>
	
	<c id="chnx1a" name="Legendary Shield">
		Only the best of the best may wear this badge of honour. Awarded to you for your victory in the 10th Championship of the Clans.
		It once belonged to a young man who had the ridiculous tendancy of wearing green tights and pointy ears...
	</c>
	
	<c id="chnx2b" name="Pavise Templar">
		This full body shield is your reward for reaching the finals of the Pro League during the 10th Championship of the Clans.
		Passed from generation of crusader to generation, it's a reminder of a more barbaric time.
	</c>
	
	<c id="chnx2a" name="Freedom Shield">
		Given to you for your victory in the Pro League of the 10th Championship of the Clans.
		Possesion of this sheild will fill you with so much patriotism that it will no doubt spill out and result in the invasion of your neibouring Dinomaster's yards. You may also find yourself in spandex...
	</c>
	
	<c id="chnx3b" name="Umbo Shield">
		This object is yours for the hard work you put in getting to the finals of the Starter League of the 10th Championship of the Clans.
		Cet objet vous est offert pour avoir participé aux phases finales de la ligue Starter du 14ème Championnat des clans.
		Easily deflects the flying bacteria from your grandma's sneezes...
	</c>
	
	<c id="chnx3a" name="Shield of Steel">
		Offered to you for your incredible victory in the Starter League of the 10th Championship of the Clans.
		Steel shield compatible with all types of glass electric cooktops.
	</c>
	
	<!-- COTC BLITZ: 5 (11th COTC) -->
	<c id="chox1a" name="Lightning Fist">
		This epic trophy was hard won during your battles to reach the finals of the Elite League of the 11th Championship of the Clans.
		Always read the instructions before use.
	</c>
	
	<c id="chox1b" name="The Palm of the Plobmer">
		This exceptionally rare glove is yours for your victory in the Elite League of the 11th Championship of the Clans.
		Sure to be a knockout success in any rescue mission for lost princesses...
	</c>
	
	<c id="chox2a" name="The Hand of Gotham">
		This glove is yours after your amazing effort in reaching the finals of the Pro League of the 11th Championship of the Clans.
		Wearing this glove will fill you with an insatiable need for justice.
	</c>
	
	<c id="chox2b" name="Street Fighting Man">
		This legendary glove is yours for your victory in the Pro League of the 11th Championship of the Clans.
		The manufacturer takes no responsibility for any injury, disability or death caused to the wearer, or the wearer's victims...
	</c>

	<c id="chox3a" name="Patate de forain">
		Cette incroyable technique vous a été révelée pour avoir participé aux phases finales de la ligue Starter du 15ème Championnat des clans.
		A vous la victoire à la sortie des boîtes.
	</c>
	
	<c id="chox3b" name="Point américain">
		Cet incroyable trophée vous est offert pour avoir remporté la finale de la ligue Starter du 15ème Championnat des clans.
		Délivre un coup de poing au bon goût de liberté.
	</c>
	
<!-- CDC Blitz 6 -->
	<c id="chpx1a" name="Dinde rotie">
		Cette dinde rotie au miel du Jura vous est offerte pour avoir remporté la finale de la ligue Elite du 16ème Championnat des clans. 
	</c>
	
	<c id="chpx1b" name="Cuissot succulent">
		Ce cuissot grillé à la braise vous est offert pour avoir participé aux phases finales de la ligue Elite du 16ème Championnat des clans.
	</c>
	
	<c id="chpx2a" name="Fraisier goutu">
		Ce fraisier aux fraises des bois vous est offert pour avoir remporté la finale de la ligue Pro du 16ème Championnat des clans.
	</c>
	
	<c id="chpx2b" name="Hot-Dog Chinois">
		Ce hot-dog issus de la plus pure tradition de street-food chinoise vous est offert pour avoir participé aux phases finales de la ligue Pro du 16ème Championnat des clans.
	</c>
	
	<c id="chpx3a" name="Radis Max">
		Cet incroyable trophée vous est offert pour avoir remporté la finale de la ligue Starter du 16ème Championnat des clans.
		Le croquer vous donne du beaume au coeur !
	</c>
	
	<c id="chpx3b" name="Carotte tempo">
		Cette incroyable trophée vous a été offert pour avoir participé aux phases finales de la ligue Starter du 16ème Championnat des clans.
		Une carotte qui donne la patate !
	</c>
	
<!-- CDC Blitz 7 -->
	<c id="chqx1a" name="La paume du plombier">
		Ce gant extrêmement rare vous est offert pour avoir remporté la finale de la ligue Elite du 15ème Championnat des clans. 
		Un accessoirement indispensable pour quiconque souhaite aller sauver la princesse... qui sera probablement dans un autre chateau.
	</c>
	
	<c id="chqx1b" name="Point fulgurant">
		Cette fabuleuse relique vous est offerte pour avoir participé aux phases finales de la ligue Elite du 15ème Championnat des clans.
		Lire attentivement la notice avant utilisation.
	</c>
	
	<c id="chqx2a" name="La main d'Eve">
		Cette relique légendaire vous est offerte pour avoir remporté la finale de la ligue Pro du 15ème Championnat des clans.
		Posseder cette relique ocrtoie le pouvoir de combattre d'égal à égal contre une créature céleste. Si le combat à lieu en métropole, le fabriquant décline toute responsabilité en cas de dommages collatéraux.
	</c>
	
	<c id="chqx2b" name="Main de Gotham">
		Ce Gant vous est offert pour avoir participé aux phases finales de la ligue Pro du 15ème Championnat des clans.
		Enfiler ce gant génère un irrépressible besoin de justice.
	</c>
	
	<c id="chqx3a" name="Point américain">
		Cet incroyable trophée vous est offert pour avoir remporté la finale de la ligue Starter du 15ème Championnat des clans.
		Délivre un coup de poing au bon goût de liberté.
	</c>
	
	<c id="chqx3b" name="Patate de forain">
		Cette incroyable technique vous a été révelée pour avoir participé aux phases finales de la ligue Starter du 15ème Championnat des clans.
		A vous la victoire à la sortie des boîtes.
	</c>
	
<!-- CDC Blitz 8 -->
	<c id="chrx1a" name="La paume du plombier">
		Ce gant extrêmement rare vous est offert pour avoir remporté la finale de la ligue Elite du 15ème Championnat des clans. 
		Un accessoirement indispensable pour quiconque souhaite aller sauver la princesse... qui sera probablement dans un autre chateau.
	</c>
	
	<c id="chrx1b" name="Point fulgurant">
		Cette fabuleuse relique vous est offerte pour avoir participé aux phases finales de la ligue Elite du 15ème Championnat des clans.
		Lire attentivement la notice avant utilisation.
	</c>
	
	<c id="chrx2a" name="La main d'Eve">
		Cette relique légendaire vous est offerte pour avoir remporté la finale de la ligue Pro du 15ème Championnat des clans.
		Posseder cette relique ocrtoie le pouvoir de combattre d'égal à égal contre une créature céleste. Si le combat à lieu en métropole, le fabriquant décline toute responsabilité en cas de dommages collatéraux.
	</c>
	
	<c id="chrx2b" name="Main de Gotham">
		Ce Gant vous est offert pour avoir participé aux phases finales de la ligue Pro du 15ème Championnat des clans.
		Enfiler ce gant génère un irrépressible besoin de justice.
	</c>
	
	<c id="chrx3a" name="Point américain">
		Cet incroyable trophée vous est offert pour avoir remporté la finale de la ligue Starter du 15ème Championnat des clans.
		Délivre un coup de poing au bon goût de liberté.
	</c>
	
	<c id="chrx3b" name="Patate de forain">
		Cette incroyable technique vous a été révelée pour avoir participé aux phases finales de la ligue Starter du 15ème Championnat des clans.
		A vous la victoire à la sortie des boîtes.
	</c>
	
	
<!-- Version anglaise seulement -->

	<c id="cinec1" name="Dinoz d'Or">
		This magnificent trophy was awarded to the first winner of the Grand Prize at the first Cinema Paradino Film Festival.
	</c>

	<c id="cinec2" name="Outstanding Contribution DAFTA">
		This magnificent trophy was awarded to the winner of the Cinema Paradino Film Festival Outstanding Contribution Award.
	</c>

	<c id="cinec3" name="Best Parody DAFTA">
		This magnificent trophy was awarded to the winner of the Cinema Paradino Film Festival Best Parody Award.
	</c>

	<c id="cinec4" name="Best Adaptation DAFTA">
		This magnificent trophy was awarded to the winner of the Cinema Paradino Film Festival Best Adaptation Award.
	</c>

	<c id="hallow" name="Jack-O-Lantern">
		This magnificent trophy was awarded to the winners of the 1st Halloween contest!
	</c>


<!-- Récompenses TID -->

	<c id="tid1" name="Zen Medal">
		Congratulations on winning the Inter-Dojo Tournament!
		The zen medal is awarded to the top Dojo in Dinoland, there is no more powerful Dinoz master!
		You get all the glory, the fame and the respect of all other Dinoz masters...!!
	</c>

	<c id="tid2" name="Master Zenith">
		Congratulations on winning the tournament!
		This solid gold statue of Master Zenith is the equivalent of the Oscar for the bravest Dinoz master in all of Dinoland, no other master is above you!
		You have earned the glory, the adoration, and the adulation of other Dinoz masters and mistresses....!!
	</c>

<!-- Récompenses Gazette -->

	<c id="gazeli" name="Extreme Reporter">
		The exciting article which you wrote for the Dinoland gazette won you this trophy.
		Dinoz masters around the world are showing off your work!
	</c>

<!-- Récompenses Monster Hunter -->

	<c id="hunt1" name="Ultimate Hunter">
		Your exploits in the monster hunt are the stuff of legends.
		The soul of the hunter burns within you and all monsters roaming Dinoland now know that you have your eye on them.
	</c>

	<c id="hunint" name="Ultimate International Hunter">
		You were the most formidable hunter in the International Monster Hunt.
		The soul of a true hunter burns within you and all dinoz masters who roam the Kingdom of Dinoland are aware of your ascent to legendary status. Time will tell stories of your greatness and bravery.
	</c>

	<c id="xhunt3" name="King of Hunters">
		You were the most formidable hunter in the International Monster Hunt.
		The soul of a true hunter burns within you and all dinoz masters who roam the Kingdom of Dinoland are aware of your ascent to legendary status. Time will tell stories of your greatness and bravery.
	</c>

	<c id="xhunt2" name="Prince of Hunters">
		You were the second most formidable hunter in the International Monster Hunt.
		The soul of a true hunter burns within you and all dinoz masters who roam the Kingdom of Dinoland are aware of your ascent to legendary status. Time will tell stories of your greatness and bravery.
	</c>

	<c id="xhunt1" name="Royal Hunter">
		You were one of the most formidable hunters in the International Monster Hunt.
		The soul of a true hunter burns within you and all dinoz masters who roam the Kingdom of Dinoland are aware of your ascent to legendary status. Time will tell stories of your greatness and bravery.
	</c>

<!-- Récompense Réalisateur de film -->

	<c id="cinema" name="Golden Film Reel">
		Your film has been chosen by the Dinoville Academy of Film and Television as the best adventure/melodrama/comedino/mind-altering/fantasy movie of the festival.
		You now join the ranks of the greatest directors who know how to touch our imaginations by transporting us to another world as only you know how!
	</c>

	<c id="cinem2" name="Silver Film Reel">
		Special Award given by the Dinoville Film Festival Committee.
	</c>

<!-- Récompense Inventeur -->

	<c id="eugene" name="The Eugene Prize for Physics">
		Your unparalleled creativity has earned you this magnificent medal, and only Dinoz masters with an extraordinary IQ are entitled to wear it.
		Some say you are a genius, others that you just got lucky, but in any case, the most important thing is that they are talking about you!
	</c>

<!-- Récompense Littérature -->

	<c id="litter" name="Literature Prize">
		This literature prize has been given to you in recognition of the prose you created and which has inspired thousands of Dinoz masters. It will be talked about for years to come, or at least until Dinoland experiences another catastrophe like the collapse of jazz Island.
		Suffice to say that it won't be for some time...
	</c>

<!-- DinoLoto -->

	<c id="clover" name="DinoLoto Winner">
		You have been awarded this prize for being the owner of the luckiest Dinoz in Dinoland (as selected by the DinoLot draw)!
		Congratulations!
	</c>

</collection>