<dinoz>

	<r id="mouef" name="Moueffe" gfx="0" elts="2:0:0:0:0" price="16000" levelup="50:20:10:5:15" demon="600:demmou:belius">
	Moueffes are distant cousins of Dragons, and are proud of it. They love fire, have a tough and resistant hide, plus an outstanding sense of combat.
	</r>

	<r id="pigmou" name="Softpig" gfx="1" elts="2:0:0:0:0" price="20000" levelup="60:15:10:10:5" skill="ccorne" demon="800:dempig">
	Softpigs are small animals, renowned for their ferocity and stubborness. They only understand those more powerful than themselves. For this reason they are notoriously hard to tame, but once a Master has established his authority, they will defend him without fail.
	</r>

	<r id="winks" name="Winks" gfx="2" elts="0:0:1:1:0" price="20000" levelup="5:10:45:30:10" skill="coque" demon="700:demwnk">
	Winks have strange powers. They are rare Dinoz who can mutate, both temporarily and permanently. They have developed in time a veritable science, passed from generation to generation.
	</r>

	<r id="plan" name="Glidwings" gfx="3" elts="0:0:0:2:0" price="16000" levelup="10:10:10:50:20" demon="700:dempla:belius">
	Glidwings are strange flying Dinoz. Their body contains many small receptors and muscles perfectly accustomed to control every inch of their wings. This enables them to manipulate and amplify wind and electricity, which they can use as powerful weapons. Although it must be said that they are not very intelligent and are easily controlled by a Master.
	</r>

	<r id="casti" name="Castivorous" gfx="4" elts="0:1:0:0:1" price="16000" levelup="10:40:15:10:25">
	Covered in thick hair, castivorous are peaceful herbivores. Despite their small legs they are very agile and can run quite fast. They are loyal companions to their masters and don't cause any trouble, except when they shed their thick coat of fur.
	</r>

	<r id="rocky" name="Rocky" gfx="5" elts="0:0:0:1:0" price="18000" levelup="20:10:10:55:5" item="rocky" skill="rock">
	Rockies are often found hiding amongst stones. They are living half-animal half-mineral creatures, whose bodies are made entirely of Lodestone. This gives them the power to produce electricity at will by rubbing their bodies.
	</r>

	<r id="pteroz" name="Pteroz" gfx="6" elts="0:0:0:0:3" price="22000" levelup="40:10:5:15:30" item="pteroz">
	Pteroz are flying Dinoz who soar above Big All-Hot. They have an impressive sense of territory and it's sensible to not disturb a Pteroz Mother protecting her eggs. They are quite hard to tame but really good fighters.
	</r>

	<r id="nuagoz" name="Cloudoz" gfx="7" elts="0:0:0:1:1" price="16000" levelup="5:5:30:30:30">
	Life appears in strange forms; Cloudoz are a perfect example of this: made from a mix of water, air and lightning, a great deal of luck is required to give them life without them evaporating instantly. If successful they become very efficient fighters and are held in high regard by Dinoz Masters.
	</r>

	<r id="sirain" name="Sirain" gfx="8" elts="0:0:2:0:0" price="16000" levelup="15:10:55:10:10">
	Sirains are masters of the Atlanteid Islands. They have good tactical knowledge and always keep cool head in battle. Due to these skills, they can expose their opponents' weaknesses.
	</r>

	<r id="hippo" name="Hippoclamp" gfx="9" elts="1:1:1:1:1" price="28000" levelup="20:20:20:20:20" item="hippo">
	Hippoclamps are an elite soldier of the Atlanteid Islands. Many scientists have studied them and have concluded, that they are almost certainly the result of a successful mutation experiment on Kumps made by the Winks.
	</r>

	<r id="gorill" name="Gorilloz" gfx="10" elts="0:2:0:0:0" price="16000" levelup="15:65:5:10:5" demon="700:demgrl">
	Gorilloz are guardians of Dinoland's large forests, especially the Grumhel Forest. Although they are strong and ferocious, they rarely show themselves unless they must protect their territory from intruders. Gorilloz are at one with nature, and behind their stern looks they are very intelligent Dinoz.
	</r>

	<r id="wanwan" name="Wanwan" gfx="11" elts="0:1:0:1:0" price="19000" levelup="15:30:5:40:10" demon="900:demwan">
	Wanwan were once considered man's best friend, before they returned to the wild. Wanwan are vivacious, able to make multi-assaults, and their long, sharp teeth are deadly. Their fur conducts electricity, enabling them to store lightning and discharge when they choose.
	</r>

	<r id="santaz" name="Santaz" gfx="12" elts="1:0:1:0:2" price="50000" levelup="5:20:10:5:60" item="no" skill="crush">
	Santaz are from the mountains of Caushemesh. They are extremely rare and desired by Dinotown Dinoz Masters. They are difficult to tame but are very powerful and have the ability to perfectly master the Air element.
	</r>

	<r id="feross" name="Feross" gfx="13" elts="1:1:1:0:0" price="50000" levelup="30:30:30:5:5" item="no" skill="carap">
	Feross are particularly rare Dinoz. Their natural habitat is the haze of the Sticky Swamp, so it's very hard to see one of them and even harder to capture one. In spite of their nice mood, their mighty horn is extremely dangerous to their enemies.
	</r>

	<r id="kabuki" name="Kabuki" gfx="14" elts="0:0:1:0:3" price="50000" levelup="10:10:30:10:40" item="no" skill="ninja" demon="800:demkab:belius">
	Natives of the Caushemesh mountains, only a few Kakubis can be found in Dinotown Kingdom. People say that a small group of them exist, living isolated on a Southern island. In any case, they are fierce fighters!
	</r>
	
	<r id="mahamu" name="Mahamuti" gfx="15" elts="0:2:2:0:0" price="30000" levelup="5:40:40:10:5" item="no" skill="quake">
	Extinct for hundreds of years, the only way to get hold of a Mahamuti is to find a frozen one. The majority of masters who are in possession of this species are often caught off guard when it finally defrosts... They are known to destroy everything in their path...
	</r>
	
	<r id="toufu" name="Tofufu" gfx="17" elts="0:2:0:2:0" price="50000" levelup="10:30:5:30:25" item="no" skill="sesqui">
	Tofufus are descended from their distant cousins, the Wistitis, and are extremely difficult to catch. They are quick and smart, and it seems as though someone has taught them kung-fu...
	</r>
	
	<r id="quetzu" name="Quetzu" gfx="18" elts="2:0:2:0:0" price="35000" levelup="40:10:40:10:0" item="quetzu" proba="25" active="nimba2">
	The Quetzu race originated on Nimbao, and since the end of the reign of Grizorg, and the isle becoming accessible to all Dinoz masters once more, it is becoming more and more common to see them around Dinoland.
	Their strength and agility remain unbalanced, and rarely do we find Quetzus advanced in years, when their potential is truly fulfilled.
	</r>
	
	<r id="soufle" name="Etherwasp" gfx="16" elts="0:1:1:1:2" price="35000" levelup="0:20:20:20:40" item="no"  active="abo" skill="napoma">
	Etherwasps are truly unique dinoz. After spending some time as larvae, they only really unveil their true form in adulthood, becoming a flying dinoz capable of mixing it up with the best of them!
	Originally from Nimbao, they are reclusive creatures, but since the troubles on the island escalated, they have started to be seen more and more.
	</r>
	
	<r id="smog" name="Smog" gfx="19" elts="1:0:0:2:2" price="35000" levelup="10:0:20:40:30" item="no">
	Smog DNA was discovered by the great professor. Extracted from blood found in a leech trapped in ice, he successfully recreated the genetic code of this dinoz who was amongst the most formidable predators on the planet.
	</r>
	
	<r id="trice" name="Tricerithumps" gfx="20" elts="2:2:0:1:1" price="35000" levelup="40:40:0:10:10" item="no" skill="cognon">
	Recently imported from the lands of Thorgnole, the Tricerithumps is extremely sought after by the discerning dino masters. Due to their aggressive nature, it can be difficult to move these dinoz from port to port without leaving a few broken planks behind!
	</r>
	<!------------- TODO ------------

	<r id="kump" name="Kump" gfx="20" elts="0:0:2:0:0" price="0" levelup="10:15:50:5:20" item="no">
	Kumps are soldiers and scouts. They are always on the first line at the time of conflicts or territory defense. They are also privileged subjects of the Winks experimentations, and that can bring some of them to possess outstanding strengths or skills.
	</r>

	-->

</dinoz>
