<effects>

	<e id="bouee" name="Buoy" icon="bouee">
		This buoy enables your Dinoz to cross water without drowning.
	</e>

	<e id="matesc" name="Climbing Gear" icon="matesc">
		Climbing Gear enables your Dinoz to climb mountains.
	</e>

	<e id="lantrn" name="Lantern" icon="lantrn">
		This Lantern enables your Dinoz to explore deep caves without the risk of getting lost.
	</e>

	<e id="pelle" name="Lucky Shovel" icon="pelle">
		This Shovel enables your Dinoz to *dig* and search for hidden treasures.
	</e>

	<e id="pelle2" name="Upgraded Shovel" icon="pelle2">
		This shovel handle is *much stronger*, and provides better grip so you'll get fewer blisters.
	</e>
	
	<e id="brkpel" name="Broken Shovel" icon="brkpel">
		The Lucky Shovel is broken, it will have to be fixed before you can use it again.
	</e>
	
	<e id="brkpe2" name="Broken Shovel" icon="brkpe2">
		The upgraded shovel finally broke, it will have to be fixed before you can use it again.
	</e>	

	<e id="marais" name="Swamp Mud">
		Sticky mud from the Swamp. It stinks, and it even moves from time to time as if it's trying to escape.
	</e>

	<e id="wpure" name="Pure Water">
		Some pure water from the Fountain of Youth. Keep it in your bag in case you are thirsty.
	</e>

	<e id="basalt" name="Basalt Shard">
		A seemingly useless piece of Basalt.
	</e>

	<e id="gant" name="Zors Glove">
		Zors Glove is a mysterious object. No one knows much about it.
	</e>

	<e id="zenbro" name="Flag-Zen" hidden="1"></e>

	<e id="nenuph" name="Waterlily Pads">
		These Waterlily pads are popular with the Zenzen monks.
	</e>

	<e id="chutes" name="Flag-Gant" hidden="1"></e>

	<e id="jvbz" name="Flag-Pecheur" hidden="1"></e>

	<e id="qwood" name="Flag Dian Korgsey" session="1"></e>
	<e id="qwhy" name="Flag Dian Korgsey" session="1"></e>
	<e id="qtame" name="Flag Dian Korgsey" session="1"></e>

	<e id="dian" name="Flag Missions Dian Korgsey" hidden="1"></e>
	<e id="grdmis" name="Flag Missions Gardien Foret" hidden="1"></e>
	<e id="humiss" name="Flag Missions Nicolas Hulot" hidden="1"></e>

	<e id="rasca" name="Scorpscuba Caller" icon="rasca">
		This small flute enables you to attract Scorpscubas and also gives you access to the Underwater Dome.
	</e>

	<e id="fcharm" name="Fire Charm">
		The Fire Charm increases the strength of your Dinoz Fire attack.
	</e>

	<e id="wcharm" name="Bao Charm">
		Bao Charm increases your Dinoz' defense against Water attacks.
	</e>

	<e id="palmes" name="Korgon Fins">
		Your Dinoz can cross water using the Korgon fins.
	</e>

	<e id="astone" name="Old Stone">
		This old stone was found by your Dinoz whilst digging. What is it for?
	</e>

	<e id="totem" name="Ashpouk Totem">
		An ancient relic of the Ashpouk civilization. According to the Professor, it's a precious Totem.
	</e>

	<e id="tourna" name="Flag-Tournoi" hidden="1"></e>

	<e id="vmem" name="Flag-Vénérable" hidden="1"></e>
	
	<e id="vkill" name="Venerable">
		This Dinoz has defeated the Venerable.
	</e>	

	<e id="fflag" name="Flag-Shaman-Charme-Feu" hidden="1"></e>

	<e id="ccard" name="Membership Card">
		This membership card allows your Dinoz to access the Lavapit Training Center!
	</e>

	<e id="admin" name="Irma's Spirit">
		This powerful effect enables your Dinoz to continue to move and fight when you please.
	</e>

	<e id="shflag" name="Flag-Shaman-Missions" hidden="1"></e>

	<e id="amulst" name="The Strategy in 130 lessons">
		This thorough book enables your Dinoz to deactivate his 'Attack' and 'Event' skills when he pleases (in the Details tab). It's an important guide for the good strategists of Dinoland wishing to adapt to the fighting conditions of each location!
	</e>

	<e id="medal1" name="Bronze Medal">
		This Bronze Medal is awarded to a Dinoz for reaching the 10th stage of the BrutForce Tournament.
	</e>

	<e id="medal2" name="Silver Medal">
		This Silver Medal is awarded to a Dinoz for reaching the 20th stage of the BrutForce Tournament.
	</e>

	<e id="medal3" name="Gold Medal">
		This Gold Medal is awarded to a Dinoz for reaching the 30th stage of the BrutForce Tournament.
	</e>

	<e id="medal4" name="Diamond Medal">
		This Medal, made entirely from diamond, is awarded to the Legendary Dinoz who wins the BrutForce Tournament!
	</e>

	<e id="gshop" name="Flourishing Branch of the Warden">
		This branch was offered by the Forest Warden as a sign of gratitude for your services. That's not all, it also gives you access to the Fruity Shop!
	</e>

	<e id="bckpck" name="Very Useful Backpack">
		This Backpack is extremely useful, with its numerous pockets and its fastenings drooping everywhere. It gives you one more *Slot* in your combat gear!
	</e>

	<e id="reinca" name="Reincarnated">
		This Dinoz has been reincarnated. Beware! He is very powerful!
	</e>
	
	<e id="renais" name="Renaissance">
		This Dino has been Reborn anew. It's incredibly powerful!
	</e>

	<e id="fspele" name="Flag-Popotholeler" hidden="1"></e>

	<e id="cup1" name="Bronze Cup">
		This cup was awarded to the team captain for taking part in the SuperDom!
	</e>

	<e id="cup2" name="Silver Cup">
		This cup was awarded to the team captain for his victories in the SuperDom!
	</e>

	<e id="cup3" name="Gold Cup">
		This cup was awarded to the team captain for his exploits in the SuperDom!
	</e>

	<e id="cup4" name="Diamond Cup">
		This cup was awarded to the team captain for his domination in the SuperDom!
	</e>

	<e id="sylkey" name="Blacksylva Key">
		This key allows you to open the Blacksylva Door and access the Magnetic Steppes.
	</e>
	
	<e id="morsso" name="Piece of the Dark World">
		This item allows your Dinoz to access part of the Dark World.
	</e>
	
	<e id="lvlup1" name="1st Limit Break">
		Your dinoz has realised its potential, it can now go beyond level 50 and level up as far as level 60!
	</e>
	
	<e id="lvlup2" name="2nd Limit Break">
		Your dinoz has realised its potential, it can now go beyond level 60 and level up as far as level 70!
	</e>
	
	<e id="lvlup3" name="3ème limite brisée">
		Your dinoz has realised its potential, it can now go as far as level 80!
	</e>
	
	<e id="newski" name="Drop of Ether">
		Your dinoz bathed in pure ether, it can now evolve using a whole new skills tree!
	</e>
	
	<!-- STEPPES MAGNETIQUES -->	

	<e id="rodtmp" name="Flag-Rodeur" session="1"></e>

	<e id="corail" name="Coral">
		This piece of Coral is so tough, it's almost unbreakable!
	</e>

	<e id="ice" name="Ice Cube">
		This piece of ice is so cold, it never defrosts!
	</e>

	<e id="potion" name="Anti SEDH Potion">
		This potion neutralises the effects of the SEDH Active poison.
	</e>

	<e id="twshop" name="Boutique-TeamW-Flag" hidden="1"></e>

	<e id="trader" name="Trader-Flag" hidden="1"></e>

	<e id="skull" name="Skully Souvenir">
		This old bone helps you remember the path to the cemetary.
	</e>

	<e id="plaza" name="Dinoplaza-Flag" hidden="1"></e>

	<e id="conts1" name="Dinoz Contest Gold Medal">
		This Gold Medal is awarded to a Dinoz for his victory in the Dinoz Contest!
	</e>

	<e id="conts2" name="Dinoz Contest Silver Medal">
		This Silver Medal is awarded to a Dinoz for his victory in the Dinoz Contest!
	</e>

	<e id="conts3" name="Dinoz Contest Bronze Medal">
		This Bronze Medal is awarded to a Dinoz for his victory in the Dinoz Contest!
	</e>

	<e id="maudit" name="Cursed!">
		This curse stops your Dinoz from earning experience in battle!
	</e>

	<e id="sphere" name="Sphere-Flag" hidden="1"></e>
	
	<e id="demon" name="Demon">
		This Dinoz is a real demon... but where do they come from?
	</e>
	
	<e id="wine" name="Bottle of Wine" hidden="1"></e>
	
	<!-- ILE DES MONSTRES -->

	<e id="monisl" name="Monster-Island-Flag" hidden="1"></e>

	<e id="mgard1" name="Guard1-Flag" session="1"></e>

	<e id="mgard2" name="Guard2-Flag" session="1"></e>

	<e id="cuzmal" name="Cuzcous Curse">
		Your Dinoz has been cursed by the Cuzcous guard...
	</e>

	<e id="mcapt" name="Capture Glove">
		This item can be used by your Dinoz to capture monsters who'll then be able to help you during fights!
	</e>

	<e id="nocapt" name="Disable-Glove" hidden="1"></e>

	<e id="msergt" name="Sergeant-Flag" session="1"></e>
	
	<!-- DinoFight -->
		
	<e id="dfight" name="DinoFight">
		This Dinoz has undergone extensive training in DinoFight, and is now ready to fearlessly explore the lands of Dinoland!
	</e>
	
</effects>