<ingredients>

	<!-- FISHES -->
	<i id="fish" name="Lujidanee Grouper" rarity="C" price="100">
		A common species in Dinoland and this fish is very popular due to it caramelised taste.
	</i>
	<i id="fishu" name="Avenger-Fish" rarity="U" price="300">
		It steals leerfish to give to the poor.
	</i>
	<i id="fish1" name="Fridge-Eel" rarity="R" price="1500">
		Most of the Eels are "electric", but this species is refrigerable. People use it to refresh their drinks or to preserve food by wrapping it with them.
	</i>
	<i id="fish2" name="Globulos" rarity="R" price="1500">
		Globulos is very soft and sticky but it bounces surprisingly well when thrown against a wall. This funny property makes it very popular!
	</i>
	<i id="fish3" name="Super-Fish" rarity="R" price="1500">
		Defender of Groupers and Globulos! Nobody really knows the identity of Super-Fish. Super-Fish is a neglected hero.
	</i>

	<!-- PLANTS -->
	<i id="fruitc" name="Pelinae Leaves" rarity="C" price="75">
		Pelinae is liked for the fresh perfume it emits, it can be found in houses throughout Dinoland.
	</i>
	<i id="fruitu" name="White Phalisk Boletus" rarity="U" price="130">
		A Mushroom of the Mushgood family, which is easy to cook in a green sauce. Some prefer it in omelettes, others like it in soup, but everybody agrees on the fact that pan-fried Phalisk Boletus is delicious.
	</i>
	<i id="fruit1" name="Whimsical Orchid" rarity="R" price="230">
		An improbable fusion between rare Orchids. It generally grows upside down, covered by a layer of hair which gives it camouflage properties.
	</i>
	<i id="fruit2" name="Figonicia Roots" rarity="R" price="230">
		Figonicia is a bad-tempered plant. That's the reason why its root are so exposed, it prevents them from growing again.
	</i>
	<i id="fruit3" name="Sadiquae Mordicus" rarity="R" price="230">
		Sadiquae Mordicus is very dangerous! Often many meters high, they can digest a human in less than a few hours. At an early age, the worst they can do is eat one of your fingers.
	</i>
	<i id="fruit4" name="Pickye Deftlyna" rarity="R" price="500">
		Pickye Deftlyna is only found on Nimbao. Very difficult to pick, the slightest wrong move and it launches heavenward...
	</i>
	<i id="fruit5" name="Ethereal Spore" rarity="U" price="150">
		The Ethereal Spore grows on the Caushemesh islands thanks to the ether that runs across their rock. Although inedible, it does give off a pleasant smell if prepared properly.
	</i>	
	<i id="fruita" name="Dark Shoot" rarity="U" price="300">
		The dark fruit relies on the darkness surrounding it for nourishment. Once it comes into contact with sunlight, it disintegrates extremely quickly. It's best to be careful with it and never let it see daylight. (It's a dreadful movie anyway.)
		Once it has been dried though, it can be conserved for several years.
	</i>	

	<!-- ENERGIES -->
	<i id="enfdr" name="Lightning Energy" rarity="C" price="300">
		Lightning energy is easy to capture as its all round us. You just have to know how to find it by hitting a stone or moving an iron bar during a thunderstorm.
	</i>
	<i id="enair" name="Air Energy" rarity="U" price="1000">
		In spite of the fact that Air is present everywhere on Dinoland, only certain breezes can be transformed into pure energy.
	</i>
	<i id="enfeu" name="Fire Energy" rarity="R" price="4000">
		Fire in its natural state is very valuable.
	</i>
	<i id="enbois" name="Wood Energy" rarity="R" price="4000">
		If finding a tree is an easy, then harbouring Wood Energy is near impossible! You have often to climb high in the leaves to find it...
	</i>
	<i id="eneau" name="Water Energy" rarity="R" price="4000">
		Water energy can be found on every water surface, but they move so quickly that nobody ever succeeds in capturing them! This is why their price is so high.
	</i>

	<!-- ARTEFACTS -->
	<i id="art" name="Sharpened Flint" rarity="C" price="150">
		A sharpened pebble made by who-knows-who to do who-knows-what.
	</i>
	<i id="artu" name="Ancient Text Fragment" rarity="U" price="1000">
		The text engraved on this fragment is unreadable. But you can be sure that a collector will pay well to get it.
	</i>
	<i id="art1" name="Precious Old Ring" rarity="R" price="8000">
		This gold ring dates back hundreds of years and would be a beautiful exhibit in a museum!
	</i>
	<i id="art2" name="Fine-cut Chalice" rarity="R" price="8000">
		This Chalice used to be part of a complete crockery collection (you are free to find the rest). You are impatient to put your hand on the cauldron!
	</i>
	<i id="art3" name="Karat Necklace" rarity="R" price="8000">
		This superb piece instantly bestows its wearer with both class and elegance.
	</i>
	<i id="artr1" name="Flawless Brooch" rarity="R" price="30000">
		You're incredibly lucky! This highly valuable brooch is like new, despite its age.
	</i>
	<i id="artr2" name="Superb Royal Crown" rarity="R" price="40000">
		This extremely rare crown was once worn by the King of Dinoland.
	</i>
	<i id="artr3" name="Mechanical Arm" rarity="R" price="15000">
		This artifact resembles a hand, it must have been made using some forgotten technology, and even if it doesn't work any more, it still has great value...
	</i>	

	<!-- HUNTING -->
	<i id="chasc" name="Fur Tuft" rarity="C" price="350">
		A handful of good-quality fur! Not enough to make a coat, but it's better than nothing....
	</i>
	<i id="chasu" name="Sharp Claws" rarity="U" price="750">
		These claws are less frightening on a string than on a hairy paw! Make sure you don't hurt yourself.
	</i>
	<i id="chas1" name="Chocolate Horn" rarity="R" price="1000">
		Although its very rare, sometimes animals are born with a chocolate horn.(black or hazelnut chocolate, it depends). Normally these animals don't last long as everybody wants them..
	</i>
	<i id="chas2" name="Viscous Eye" rarity="R" price="1300">
		This eye makes a really disgusting noise in your bag!
	</i>
	<i id="chas3" name="Monstrous tongue" rarity="R" price="10000">
		A hunting trophy which would make most Dinoland Masters envious! If in perfect condition, this monster tongue will be sold for a lot of money.
	</i>
	<i id="chas4" name="Dorogon Tooth" rarity="R" price="12000">
		Very few people can claim to own this particular hunting trophy! This freshly extracted Dorogon Tooth should fetch a nice price.
	</i>
	<i id="chas5" name="Radioactive Rock" rarity="U" price="500">
		This rock, extracted from the sloughed rock hide of a Groulem, has been affected by exposure to ether and now has a strange glow to it. It's recommended that you don't carry it on your person for any more than a day or you risk losing your hair.
 	</i>	

	<!-- SPECIAL -->
	<i id="dgrain" name="Devourer Seeds" rarity="S" max="100" price="15000">
		Devourer seeds are very rare ingredients which can only be found in the Magnetic Steppes. More important than their rarity, they are highly desired by the finest gourmets, renderring them invaluable.
	</i>

</ingredients>