<scenarios>

	<!-- Freezer -->

	<s id="congel">
		<t id="congel_done">::name:: is frozen! You can defrost him by accessing his page via "My Account"</t>
		<t id="decongel_done">::name:: defrosting in progress! He will be able to move and fight tomorrow!</t>
		<t id="decongel_max_dinoz">You can't defrost your Dinoz right now because you have reached the maximum number of active Dinoz. Freeze another one first.</t>
	</s>

	<!-- Dark World -->

	<s id="dworld">
		<t id="concentrate">::name:: is hypnotized by Bao and is focusing!</t>
		<t id="entered_portal">::name:: has fallen through the portal and landed in an unknown yet strangely familiar dark world....</t>
		<t id="enter_tower">You enter the Dark Tower. A mysterious guardian stands in front of your Dinoz!</t>
		<t id="leave_tower">After defeating the guardian, your Dinoz finds the Blacksylva Key and a portal opens offering you a possible return to Dinoland...</t>
	</s>

	<!-- Magnetic Steppes -->
	<s id="magnet" name="Magnetite Burst">
		<t id="tower_won">You have control of the Devourer! Keep hold of it until midnight to get its precious seeds!</t>
		<t id="tower_max_defender">You have reached the maximum number of Dinoz you can use to defend the Devourer.</t>
		<t id="grains_credited">Congratulations! While controlling the Devourer you gained <b>::count::</b> seed(s). They have been added to your list of Ingredients.</t>

		<!-- First Fight -->
		<t id="fight_wteam">While you are approaching, you are attacked by strange Dinoz!</t>
		<t id="fight_wteam_done">Wait! This Dinoz is too weak to be part of the Rockies King's elite troops!</t>
		<t id="fight_wteam_regen">Electroheals</t>

		<!-- 4 Separate Fights -->
		<t id="fight_wteam_start">While you are approaching, a Team-W Dinoz appears ... your Dinoz attacks him!</t>
		<t id="fight_wteam_lost">You shall not pass!</t>
		<t id="fight_wteam_won1">Why are you attacking us? We will retaliate!</t>
		<t id="fight_wteam_won2">You are spies of the Rockies King! Your time will come!</t>
		<t id="fight_wteam_won3">You want to kill us all?!? Hurry up! Take refuge to the south camp!</t>
		<t id="fight_wteam_end">Wait! Bigbeastly isn't in his normal state ... as you have followed here, stop fighting for a moment and let us talk as civilised people....</t>

		<t id="fight_darkdinoz">While you are arriving at the Magnetic Steppes, some strange shadows suddenly surround you. It seems that you have been ambushed....</t>
		<t id="fight_potion_stolen">That's a disaster! The enraged Smashrooms have stolen your Anti SEDH Potion!</t>

		<t id="fight_sking_start">You recognize Wanwan Bigbeastly of Team-W. He seems to be controled by the dark Smashrooms. But are they smart enough to control him by themselves???</t>
		<t id="fight_captain_help">It looks like you need some help ... Team-W: attaaaaaack!</t>

		<t id="fight_sking_end1">After the fight, you find the Anti SEDH Potion you made on the ground. You use it on Bigbeastly so he can recover...</t>
		<t id="fight_sking_end2">The Rockies King and the captain are waiting to reward you for your valiant efforts in the battle....</t>

	</s>

	<!-- 7 Magic Stars -->

	<s id="star" name="The Sideral Feather">
		<t id="fight_megawolf">While you are approaching, a huge wolf appears!</t>
		<t id="fight_star_found">At the end of the fight, you notice a shiny object on the ground: its a magic star!</t>
		<t id="eat_star_found">After having eaten the Pie, your Dinoz notices something shiny a few meters away ... Congratulations! You have found one of the 7 magic stars!</t>
		<t id="dig_star_found">While digging, you hear a strange noise. You dig a bit further and find one of the 7 magic stars! Congratulations!</t>
		<t id="resurrect_star_found">When your Dinoz wakes up in Dinotown, he notices that someone has given him the last magic star! He can't recall who gave it to him, but remembers a strange Dinoz who looked like a monkey with a multicoloured coat. He gave your Dinoz the 7th star. But who is he?!?</t>
	</s>

	<!-- Kabuki Quest -->

	<s id="kabuki" name="Aura Kabuki">
		<t id="yakuzi_run">Yakuzi takes his chance and flees!</t>
		<t id="kabuki_defend">Help!!!!</t>
		<t id="strange_dinoz">Who is this strange Dinoz?!?</t>
		<t id="igor_fight">Dinoz, attack him!</t>
		<t id="igor_leave">After having defeated you, Igor flees to Totem Island with his loyal Dinoz...</t>
		<t id="enter_ilost">As expected, your Dinoz has got lost on the road to Totem Island. Your Dinoz travels in circles and cirles for hours and hours without finding the right path.</t>

		<t id="yakuzi_help1">Huh?!? What are you doing HERE?</t>
		<t id="yakuzi_help2">WHAT? Professor Igor is on Totem Island?!?</t>
		<t id="yakuzi_help3">Let's try again together! With my Kabuki Aura, we should be able to do it!</t>

		<t id="igor_final_start">You finally arrive on the Totem Island. But what's going on?</t>
		<t id="igor_final_talk">WHAT?? How have you been able to follow me here without an Aura?!?</t>
		<t id="igor_final_talk2">Attaaaaaaack!!!</t>
		<t id="yakuzi_final_talk">Wait!</t>
		<t id="yakuzi_final_talk2">We are going to help you!!!</t>

		<t id="igor_lost_fight">You have defeated Igor and his loyal Dinoz! You have also obtained the Kabuki Aura!</t>
	</s>
	
	<s id="kabegg"></s>

	<!-- Monster Island -->

	<s id="monisl" name="Monster Island">
		<t id="veguard_stop">Stop that waterwanderer! KSSSS... That's an order!</t>
		<t id="cuzboss_begin">Who dares to wake me from my slumber!</t>
		<t id="cuzboss_end">You have been cursed!</t>
		<t id="grotox_begin">I can't let a simple soldier insult my ancestors! Charge!</t>
		<t id="grotox_end">You're not a normal soldier......</t>

		<t id="end_antrax1">Grotox...</t>
		<t id="end_grotox1">Antraxov...</t>
		<t id="end_antrax2">I think it's time we made peace...</t>
		<t id="end_grotox2">All those deaths....and for what? Nothing?</t>
		<t id="end_antrax3">The proof is right there in front of us, our two families used to rule the Cuzcous Empire......together.</t>
		<t id="end_grotox3">You're right, there's no reason for us to be at war...</t>
		<t id="end_grotox4">So the war's over now? We're at peace?</t>
		<t id="end_antrax4">Yes, but it's going to take a long time for our people to forget about this war and come to terms with our new found friendship.</t>
		<t id="end_grotox5">We should help them to understand. We'll also need to rebuild our kingdoms......together.</t>
		<t id="end_antrax5">It's our duty......</t>
		<t id="end_come">Before leaving, the two kings approach you and ask to see you in their palaces so that they can each give you a reward.</t>
	</s>

	<!-- Dungeons -->

	<s id="dngeon">
		<t id="dun_cant_enter">Your Dinoz cannot enter as somebody is already inside...</t>
		<t id="dun_got_item">You have found </t>
		<t id="dun_need_key">This door requires '::key::'</t>
		<t id="dun_keys0">The Red:The Black:The Dead:The Enchanted:The Magic:The Blazing:The Plastic:The Metal:The Cardboard:The Living:The Enormous:The Tiny:The Divine:The Disguised</t>
		<t id="dun_keys1">Goblins:Dragons:Trees:Angels:Octopus:Kabukis:Omnivores:Romeos:Magicians:Plumbers</t>
		<t id="dun_keys2">Key</t>
		<t id="dun_heal_point">Heal your Dinoz here!</t>
		<t id="dun_no_scenario">The ancient scroll you just found crumbles in your hands...</t>
		<t id="dun_level">Level ::n::</t>
		</s>

	<!-- ALZAIMER -->
	<s id="alzaim" name="Itinerary of the unlucky vagabond"></s>
	<s id="joujou" name="The quest for the lost toy"></s>
	
	<!-- CLINIQUE -->
	<s id="clinik" name="Dinoland Clinic"></s>
	
	<!-- NIMBAO L'ILE VOLANTE -->
	<s id="friend"></s>
	<s id="nimbao" name="Nimbao Island">
		<t id="lucette_heal">Ahahaha ... Lucette... you just can't help yourself, can you, you always have to go in heavy-handed ! I think they've learnt their lesson, so let them go.</t>
	</s>
	<s id="nimba2" name="The discovery of Quetzu">
		<t id="pistac_heal">Father, noooo! Quick, I have to help him!</t>
		<t id="mandra_heal">Come on, get back up!</t>		
	</s>	
	
	
	<!-- DOJO -->
	<s id="dojo"></s>	
		
	
	<!-- INVOCATIONS -->
	<s id="invoc"></s>
	
	<!-- NOUVELLES QUETES -->
	<s id="intro" name="Taurus the Magnificent">
		<t id="bao_heal">Come on, young Dinoz Master, get up!</t>
	</s>
	<s id="caush" name="The Nightmare era">
		<t id="union">::name:: is ready to try to open the gates to Caushemesh!</t>
		<t id="entered_door">::name:: has opened the door... what mysteries are to be found behind it?</t>
	</s>
	
	<s id="king" name="The King's Missions"></s>
	<s id="fmedal" name="The path to the Celestial Temple"></s>	
	<s id="smog" name="20000 Leagues under the iles"></s>
	
</scenarios>
