<spells>

	<s id="heal1" name="Healing Charm" mana="5">
		Restores up to 10 health points for each defending Dinoz after the next battle.
	</s>

	<s id="mordef" name="Mercenaries" mana="7" manawar="1" gold="10000" daily="1">
		This will increase the minimum number of defenders during the next attack by 2.
	</s>

	<s id="heal2" name="Healing Spell" mana="10">
		Restores up to 30 health points for each defending Dinoz after the next battle
	</s>

	<s id="nowat" name="Thousand-Year Drought" mana="12" manawar="1" gold="5000" daily="1">
		During the next battle, the water element of all combattants will be reset to zero.
	</s>

	<s id="reset" name="Mana Corruption" mana="10">
		This spell immediately changes the ingredients required to produce more mana.
	</s>

	<s id="antib" name="Zodiac Shield" mana="20">
		Cancels out the next use of Scale in battle.
	</s>

	<s id="shield" name="Time Shield" mana="25" manawar="0" gold="20000" daily="1">
		Protects your castle from enemy attacks for one hour.
	</s>

	<s id="noatt" name="Absolute Terror" mana="20" manawar="1" gold="5000" daily="1">
		An attacker will flee the battlefield at the start of the next combat (as long as they are not alone).
	</s>

	<s id="antihy" name="Mirrored Shield" mana="7" manawar="1" gold="5000" daily="1">
		Instead of hypnotising an enemy Dinoz, the next Dinoz to use Hypnosis will join the opposing team.
	</s>

	<s id="nofdr" name="High Voltage" mana="15" manawar="1" gold="5000"  daily="1">
		During the next battle, the lightning element of all combattants will be reset to zero.
	</s>

	<s id="heal3" name="Enchanted Healing" mana="20">
		Restores up to 100 health points for each defending Dinoz after the next battle
	</s>

	<s id="invoc" name="Abomination" mana="30" manawar="1" gold="5000" daily="1">
		Prepares a special welcome for the next attackers! 
	</s>

	<s id="paint1" name="Red Respray" mana="5" permanent="1" manawar="1" gold="20000">
		Give your castle a red tint. It doesn't do much but at least it looks good.
	</s>

	<s id="moral" name="Morale Boost" mana="25" permanent="1" manawar="1" gold="40000">
		Doubles the morale point gain after a battle.
	</s>

	<s id="moredf" name="Troops from the World Beyond" mana="30" permanent="1">
		Increases the maximum number of Dinoz which can be assigned to defending the castle by five.
	</s>

	<s id="paint2" name="Black Beauty" mana="20" permanent="1" manawar="1" gold="50000">
		Give your castle a dark tint. It doesn't do much but at least it looks good.
	</s>

	<s id="singat" name="Magic Fog" mana="45" permanent="1">
		Blocks anyone from attacking your castle for thirty seconds after a battle.
	</s>

	<s id="mindef" name="Defensive Reinforcements" mana="40" permanent="1" manawar="1" gold="30000">
		Increases the minimum number of defenders for all attacks by one.
	</s>
	
	<s id="invisi" name="Spectral Form" mana="10" max="1" reputationMax="99" noWar="1">
		The castle becomes invisible for 10 hours, therefore is sheltered from attacks, however, your Dinoz will not be able to attack another clan. This spell is cast automatically and cannot be saved.
	</s>	

</spells>