<!--
	LABELS:
		* A : Improvement
		* B : BugFix
		* N : New Feature
		
		Click <more/> to force display separation instead of using the automatic system 
-->
<updates>
	<u id="26" date="2011-12-01" type="B">
		Invocation display bug corrected.<br/><more/>
		Trophy wall improvements made to the "My Account" page.
	</u>
	<u id="25" date="2011-11-30" type="A">
		Clan page navigation improved.<br/><more/>
		Improvements made to the problem of writing in the forums using Internet Explorer 8.
	</u>
	<u id="24" date="2011-11-29" type="N">
		Age of Invocations
		<more/>
		<ul class="ul" style="width:200px">
			<li>A unique invocation for each race of dinoz.</li>
			<li>4 new magic objects.</li>
			<li>Timeline added at the bottom of the news page.</li>
			<li>New Chen and Gulom missions.</li>
		</ul>
	</u>
	<u id="23" date="2011-08-19" type="B">
		Infiltration motor bug fixed
		This problem was due to an update of Adobe Flash Player which made it incompatible with previous versions.
	</u>
	<u id="22" date="2011-07-27" type="A">
		Rebalancing online! (+ more)
		<more/>
		<ul class="ul" style="width:200px">
		<li>Hypnosis only affects a dinoz for 3 cycles.</li>
		<li>Bubble reduces attack damage in the following way: (AIR + WATER) / Total of Dinoz Elements.
	 Bubble gives a minimum protection of 30%.</li>
		<li>Relaxative Pill rebalanced: Speed gain reduced to +50%.</li>
		<li>The combat engine updated from 10 to 100.</li>
		<li>Dinoz which have defeated the Venerable will earn an icon in their status.</li>
		</ul>
	</u>
	
	<u id="21" date="2011-07-12" type="B">
		Bug with the magic object Ember which blocked affected dinoz from removing objects fixed. 
	</u>
	<u id="20" date="2011-06-29" type="A">
		Added time remaining for unequipping a magic object
	</u>	
	<u id="19" date="2011-06-23" type="B">
		Problem with the intelligent name entry system for clan searches corrected
	</u>
	<u id="18" date="2011-06-07" type="AN">
		Clan page design modifications.
		Account page design modifications.
		Distinction system added.
	</u>
	<u id="17" date="2011-06-02" type="N">
		Colossus skill rebalanced
		Infiltration issues fixed
	</u>
	<u id="16" date="2011-05-20" type="N">
Infiltrations updated. If you win the fight after being discovered, you can continue the infiltration from where you were.
	</u>
	<u id="15" date="2011-05-17" type="B">
		Dojo page access issues corrected
		Paradino festival navigation issues fixed
	</u>
	<u id="14" date="2011-05-09" type="A">
		Display of dojo statistics improved
	</u>
	<u id="13" date="2011-05-02" type="N">
		New missions prepared.
	</u>
	<u id="12" date="2011-04-04" type="N">
		New Clan options added <more/>: Select league and modify league for the COTC
	</u>
	<u id="11" date="2011-03-04" type="B">
		Leader selection bug fixed.
	</u>
	<u id="10" date="2011-03-04" type="N">
		Dojo combat results hidden by default on the day of the combat.
		Keeps the excitement - watch without knowing the result!
	</u>
	<u id="9" date="2011-02-25" type="N">
		New welcome page.<more/> Clearer and more complete, you can now find all the info you need on your favourite game.
		Take part in player surveys - they'll help us to better plan your updates.
	</u>
	<u id="8" date="2011-02-25" type="N">
		New account options added <more/>fast movement, fewer notifications, battle summary etc. <a href="/user/account">Click here</a>
	</u>
	<u id="7" date="2011-02-19" type="N">
		Clan page modification interface added.
	</u>
	<u id="6" date="2011-02-17" type="N">
		Ajax acceleration implemented<more/>
		Page navigation interface improved.
	</u>
	<u id="5" date="2011-02-10" type="B">
		Dinoz no longer ungroup after attacking a castle. There's no longer any need to select them all again.
	</u>
	<u id="4" date="2011-02-10" type="N">
		The final phase battles of the IDT can now be accessed without logging in.
	</u>
	<u id="3" date="2011-01-25" type="A">
		Your personal announcement board has been improved allowing for improved formatting.
	</u>
	<u id="2" date="2011-01-25" type="N">
		Speed up navigation by customising your laft-hand menu bar. <a href="/user/account">Click here</a>
	</u>
	<u id="1" date="2011-01-25" type="A">
		Your inventory is now grouped by category.
	</u>
	<u id="0" date="2011-01-25" type="A">
		New actions for your Dinoz.<more/>
		Breaking up a group and changing the leader can now be done in one click!
	</u>
</updates>
