<uvars>
	<v id="farmer">
		Flag showing if a player is a potential farmer
	</v>
	
	<v id="saboss">
		Flag qui dit si on a affronter le boss sangsue
	</v>
	
	<!--- IMPORTANT -->
	<v id="tuto">
		Shows whether the new player welcome tutorial is active for a given player.
	</v>
	
	<v id="ptuto">
		Progression in the tutorial, contains the ID of the current objective?
	</v>
	
	<v id="buyer">
		Flag which shows if a player is a coder or not?
	</v>
	
	<v id="elites">
		Number of Elite days the player has REMAINING?
	</v>
	
	<v id="elite">
		If the player has used an Elite day today
	</v>
	
	<v id="surge">
		Cosmetic surgery at the clinic. This value represents what the PLAYER HAS REMAINING.
	</v>
	
	<v id="conver">
		Conversion from Gold to Treasury Notes. This value represents what the CAN STILL BE CONVERTED by the player.
	</v>
	
	<v id="arcadu">
		Number of combats against the 1st Colossus from Big All Hot
	</v>
	<v id="behemu">
		Number of combats against the 2nd Colossus (Behemount) at the Steppes
	</v>
	<v id="serpe">
		number of combats against the 3rd Colossus (Serpether) on Caushemesh
	</v>
	
	<v id="tradok">
		You have succeeded in collecting the 100 devourer grains to conclude your deal with Jasper K.
	</v>
	
	<!-- MARKETING -->
	<v id="mkt1">
		Flag to show that the player has received a reminder email for caushemesh
	</v>
	<v id="mkt1ok">
		Flag to show that the user came back to the site following the mail about caushemesh
	</v>
	
	<!-- FLAGS / TEMPORARY VARS -->
	
	<v id="gather" temporary="1">
		Flag pour spécifier que ce joueur a déjà vidé trop de grilles de gather (hors event) aujourd'hui
	</v>
	
	<v id="xmasev" temporary="1">
		Flag pour spécifier que ce joueur a déjà accéder à l'étape journalière de l'event xmasevent
	</v>
	<!-- BETA STUFF -->
	<v id="beta">
		Variable which shows whether a player is ready and willing to participate in a BETA.
	</v>	
	
	<v id="dicarb">
		Variable which shows if the player has unlocked the ability to decipher the Arborian language.
	</v>
		
	<v id="airpur">
		This player has completed Klutz's Airpur mission.
	</v>
	<v id="brocan">
		Counts the number of times the player talks to the second-hand dealer at the market. The more they talk to him, the better they know how not to get ripped off.
	</v>
	<v id="paques">
		The number of eggs the player has bought from Madame Urma.
	</v>	
	<v id="pelle2">
		The number of hits this object inflicted on the shovel, which will make it break only after a certain time.
	</v>
	<v id="dig">
		Number of digging actions that have been carried out.
	</v>
	<v id="tuto1">
		Progression tracker for the introductory tutorial.
	</v>
	<v id="hbegin">
		Progression tracker when smartBegin is active. As the counter progresses, the less we help the player.
		This helps the player get to grips with the game. (remember, over 60% of lost players had no Irmas left)
	</v>
	
	<v id="codedf">
		If the player has used a DinoFight code or not.
	</v>	<!-- variables de limitations -->
	<v id="quetzu">
		Number of Quetzu Dinoz the player has bought. As this Dinoz is rare, there is a limit so that they don't start appearing everywhere.
	</v>
		
	<!-- variables pour trophés -->
	<v id="utitle">
		Player's Title. This must come from the selection made available from trophies earned.
	</v>
	
	<v id="irma">
		Number of Irma's Potions consumed
	</v>	
	<!--
	<v id="irma">
		Nombre de potions d'irmas achetées en boutique.
	</v>
	<v id="angel">
		Nombre de potions d'anges achetées en boutique.
	</v>
	-->
	<v id="deaths">
		Number of times the Dinoz has died.
	</v>
	<v id="pdays">
		Number of days of activity on the site (and inactivity since registration).
	</v>
	<v id="moves">
		Number of moves made.
	</v>
	
	<v id="chasse">
		Number of hunts.
	</v>
	<v id="peche">
		Number of fishing trips.
	</v>
	<v id="cueill">
		Number of times the player has been out gathering ingredients.
	</v>
	<v id="energy">
		Number of times this player has re-energised their Dinoz.
	</v>
	<v id="fouill">
		Number of searches carried out by the player
	</v>	
	<v id="healpv">
		Number of HP restored by objects and by resting.
	</v>	
	
	<!-- UPS -->
	<v id="lvlup">
		Number of level-ups.
	</v>
	<v id="upwood">
		Number of wood level-ups.
	</v>
	<v id="upfire">
		Number of fire level-ups.
	</v>
	<v id="upthun">
		Number of lightning level-ups.
	</v>
	<v id="upwatr">
		Number of water level-ups.
	</v>
	<v id="upair">
		Number of air level-ups.
	</v>
	<!-- FIGHTS -->
	<v id="fights">
		Nombre de combats réalisés.
	</v>
	<v id="killm">
		Nombre de monstres tués.
	</v>
	<v id="killd">
		Nombre de Dinoz tués.
	</v>
	<!--
	<v id="killpv">
		Nombre de points de vie enlevés aux adversaires.
	</v>
	-->
	<v id="brkpel">
		Nobmre de pelles que le joueurs à cassé.
	</v>
	<v id="market">
		Nombre de ventes conclues au marché.
	</v>
	<v id="sbuyer">
		Nombre d'achats réalisés en boutique.
	</v>
	<v id="mbuyer">
		Nombre d'achats réalisés au marché.
	</v>
	<!-- GDC -->
	<v id="gdcdef">
		Nombre de fois que le joueur à défendu le château en Guerre des clans
	</v>
	<v id="gdcatt">
		Nombre de fois que le joueur à attaqué le château ennemi en Guerre des clans
	</v>
	
	<!-- GDM -->
	<v id="gdmchg">
		Nombre de fois que le joueur à chercher à changer de clan durant la GDM
	</v>
	
	<!-- CDC -->
	<v id="cdcmov">
		Nombre de déplacements réalisés durant les batailles du championnat des clans.
	</v>
	<v id="cdcfgt">
		Nombre de combats réalisés durant les batailles du championnat des clans.
	</v>
	<!-- CLANS -->
	<v id="clans">
		Nombre de clans dans lequel le joueur a été
	</v>
	<v id="clancr">
		Nombre de clans que le joueur a créés.
	</v>
	
	<v id="beauty">
		Nombre de titres de beautés remportés par les Dinoz du joueur.
	</v>
	<v id="clanac">
		Number of clan-related actions carried out by the player
	</v>	
	
</uvars>