<texts>
	<t id="objective_points">Objective: ::points:: points</t>
	<t id="select_animal">Select a new animal:</t>
	
	<t id="_STANDARD_A_NAME">cat</t>
	<t id="_STANDARD_B_NAME">dog</t>
	<t id="_STANDARD_C_NAME">rabbit</t>
	<t id="_MOUSE_NAME">mouse</t>
	<t id="_GHOST_NAME">ghost</t>
	<t id="_CHEETAH_NAME">cheetah</t>
	<t id="_LION_NAME">lion</t>
	<t id="_SHEEP_NAME">sheep</t>
	<t id="_GNU_NAME">yak</t>
	<t id="_SQUIRREL_NAME">squirrel</t>
	<t id="_ELEPHANT_NAME">elephant</t>
	<t id="_KOALA_NAME">koala</t>
	<t id="_HYENA_NAME">hyena</t>
	<t id="_BEAR_NAME">bear</t>
	<t id="_HEN_NAME">chicken</t>
	<t id="_PIOUZ_NAME">Piouz</t>
	<t id="_HIPPO_NAME">hippo</t>
	<t id="_FROG_NAME">frog</t>
	<t id="_CHAMELEON_NAME">chameleon</t>
	<t id="_SNAKE_NAME">snake</t>
	<t id="_PANDA_NAME">panda</t>
		
	<t id="_STANDARD_A_DESC">No special behaviour.</t>
	<t id="_STANDARD_B_DESC">No special behaviour.</t>
	<t id="_STANDARD_C_DESC">No special behaviour.</t>
	<t id="_MOUSE_DESC">The mouse can switch places with the selected animal.</t>
	<t id="_GHOST_DESC">Other animals can move through the ghost.</t>
	<t id="_CHEETAH_DESC">Two cheetahs can be moved on the same turn.</t>
	<t id="_LION_DESC">When you make a combo, lions will devour any naighboring animals.</t>
	<t id="_SHEEP_DESC">When they arrive on the board, sheep will try to land near other sheep.</t>
	<t id="_GNU_DESC">At the end of a move, gnu will attract any other gnu in their line of sight.</t>
	<t id="_SQUIRREL_DESC">If you make a combo with squirrels, you can play again immediately!</t>
	<t id="_ELEPHANT_DESC">Every elephant counts for two animals!</t>
	<t id="_KOALA_DESC">When you make a koala combo, only one animal is added to the board.</t>
	<t id="_HYENA_DESC">When you line up 4 or more hyenas, you can play again immediately.</t>
	<t id="_BEAR_DESC">The bear can devour a targeted animal.</t>
	<t id="_HEN_DESC">When involved in a combo, the chicken leaves a surprise egg behind.</t>
	<t id="_PIOUZ_DESC">At the end of the move, a neighboring animal is transformed into a piouz.</t>
	<t id="_HIPPO_DESC">When it arrives on the board, a hippo crushes an animal already on the board.</t>
	<t id="_FROG_DESC">Frogs can combine even if they're not lined up straight.</t>
	<t id="_CHAMELEON_DESC">At the end of a move, the chameleon transforms into a neighboring animal</t>
	<t id="_SNAKE_DESC">When involved in a combo, the snake devours all animals within range</t>
	<t id="_PANDA_DESC">Only 3 pandas are required to make a combo!</t>

</texts>
