<d place="baobob" name="Mr Bao Bob" gfx="baobob">
	<phase id="begin" next="question:nothing">
		Hello, hello! What do you want young Master Tamer?
	</phase>

	<a id="question">I've got a question for you</a>
	<a id="nothing">Nothing</a>

	<phase id="question" next="mission:quest2:quest3:quest4:no">
		A question? Mmmmmm... what do you think about a little Mission for your Dinoz instead?
		Some friends and I organize rallies around Dinoland. You could take part, if you're interested.
	</phase>

	<a id="mission">Yes, I'd like that</a>
	<a id="no" target="nothing">No thanks</a>
	<a id="quest2" cond="active(steppes)+!fx(palmes)">What about my question?</a>
	<a id="quest3" cond="active(steppes)+fx(palmes)+!fx(sylkey)">What about my question?</a>
	<a id="quest4" cond="scenario(magnet,8)">What about my question?</a>

	<phase id="nothing">
		Oh well. Bon voyage!
	</phase>

	<phase id="mission" missions="bob"></phase>

	<phase id="quest2">
		Return to me when you have obtained the Korgon fins from Grumhel Forest.
		Then I'll answer any question you want.
	</phase>

	<a id="bye" target="nothing">I have to leave</a>

	<phase id="quest3" next="where:bye">
		A question? Mmmmm ... I see that you have obtained the Korgon fins.
		That means that you should be able to survive... maybe...
	</phase>

	<a id="where">Where?</a>

	<phase id="where" next="where2:how:danger:bye">
		Mmmm ... You must round up seven Dinoz and bring them here. Not necessarily yours,
		they can also be Dinoz of members of your Clan. Once you have enough Dinoz I'll send you on your way.
	</phase>

	<a id="where2">But where exactly?</a>
	<a id="how">What do I need to do?</a>
	<a id="danger">Is it dangerous?</a>

	<phase id="where2" next="how:danger:bye">
		Mmmm ... it's a place ... I can't say any more. But know that you'll find a key there,
		THE key for the Blacksilva door. It'll allow you to continue your adventure. If you survive that is....
	</phase>

	<phase id="how" next="where2:danger:concen:bye">
		How you ask? Listen. You must round up seven Dinoz and bring them here. Not necessarily yours,
		they can also be Dinoz of members of your Clan. Each Dinoz needs to focus. Once you have enough Dinoz I'll send you on your way.
	</phase>

	<phase id="danger" next="where2:how:bye">
		Dangerous? It's fair to say that you'll only have a few chances to survive ...
		But as the saying goes, nothing ventured, nothing gained, no?
	</phase>

	<a id="concen">I want my Dinoz to focus!</a>

	<phase id="concen" next="ok:bye">
		If you would like I can hypnotize your Dinoz. This will focus your Dinoz.
		Don't worry, you can stop the hypnosis at any point, if you want.
	</phase>

	<a id="ok">Ok</a>

	<phase id="ok" url="/dino/::did::/act/concentrate"></phase>

	<phase id="quest4" next="noingr:ingr:bye">
		A question? Mmmmm ... You'll need some ingredients if you would like me to help you.
		If I guess well, the question you want to ask me....
	</phase>

	<a id="ingr" cond="fx(gshop)+fx(ice)+fx(corail)">Here are the ingredients!</a>
	<a id="noingr" cond="!(fx(gshop)+fx(ice)+fx(corail))">Here are the ingredients!</a>

	<phase id="noingr">
		Mmmm....Coral that never breaks, Ice that never melts, and a Branch that never fades.
		It seems that there's something missing, my friend.
	</phase>

	<phase id="ingr" noeffect="gshop:ice:corail" effect="potion" scenario="magnet:9" next="potion">
		Poum poum palalam poum poum palalam PAM! Done, a wonderful Anti SEDH Potion is ready for you...
	</phase>

	<a id="potion">So you are an Antique Monkey!!!</a>

	<phase id="potion">
		Good bye my good friend, come back again when you can!
	</phase>

</d>