<!-- ***************************************************************************** -->
<!-- Agathe et Lechton, habitent l'acropole de Caushemesh --->

<d place="cacrop" name="Ivan Tocry" gfx="lechton" cond="scenario(caush,42-)">
	<phase id="begin" fast="1">
		The Acropolis is silent. The doors and windows of every room are boarded up.
		There is a dismal atmosphere looming over the town. In spite of the emptiness you feel evil eyes watching your every move.
		You can barely make out a man of considerable years hiding in a dark alley, afraid, he doesn't dare make a move towards you.
	</phase>
</d>

<d place="cacrop" name="Jules Avemerite" gfx="agathe" cond="scenario(caush,19+)+scenario(caush,42-)">
	<phase id="begin" fast="1">
		The little girl that you saved is staying at her grand-father's side, she waves to you, but she clearly doesn't want to be seen.
		It's going to take a little more time before you can discuss matters openly with the denizens of this town.
	</phase>
</d>

<!-- Une fois la quête terminée, un des habitants ouvrira une boutique dans le village pour vendre de nouveaux objets. -->

<d place="cacrop" name="Ivan Tocry" gfx="lechton" frame="sour" cond="scenario(caush,43+)">
	<phase id="begin" fast="1" next="salut">
		The Acropolis is starting to look more like it used to, the residents are starting to leave their homes, at least a little.
		Even a whole generation who spent their lives in hiding couln't have been wiped out in this short time.
		The old man remains guarded, and distrusting, but he waves to you nonetheless.
	</phase>
	<a id="salut">Are things getting better?</a>
	<phase id="salut">
		[Yes, we will never be able to thank you enough for what you have done for us.
		The wounds of the past will take some time to heal, but once again we have the hope, the hope that will allow us to rebuild our country.]
	</phase>
</d>

<d place="cacrop" name="Jules Avemerite" gfx="agathe" frame="normal" cond="scenario(caush,43+)">
	<phase id="begin" fast="1">
		The young girl has found her smile.
		She is no longer paying you any attention and is now playing with the other children in the square in front of the Acropolis.
		Danger seems so far away when you are watching a scene such as this.
	</phase>
</d>

