<!-- ANIMATION DE NOEL 2011 -->

<!-- LISTE DE JOZE BOVE -->

<d place="port" name="Atchoz" gfx="lutin" cond="(active(xmasavent)|admin())+gvar(xavent,0)+event(xmasavent)">
	<phase id="begin" frame="atchoz" background="1">
		[Good day Dinoz master!]
		[They've put me in charge of organising the *Holiday Quiz*. Post your answers on the forums, and our specially trained elves will pick a winner every day. There should be something for everyone to take part in. Remember to visit every day so you don't miss your best chance to win ! ]
		[The first question is a "Guess Who" type affair: ]
		[* "I am a fictional character with a french-sounding foe. I'm a mighty pirate but I won't hurt a soul. Who am I ?" *]
		[_(To submit your answer, simply head to the "Discussions about the game" forum, and find the Holiday Quiz thread.)_ ]
		
		[For the next question, *go and see Simploz at the Fountain of Youth tomorrow* !]
	</phase>
</d>

<!-- LISTE DE L'ETRE ETRANGE -->

<d place="fountj" name="Simploz" gfx="lutin" cond="gvar(xavent,1)+event(xmasavent)">
	<phase id="begin" frame="simploz" background="2">
		[Good day Dinoz master!]
		[Atchoz asked me to give you the second question of the Holiday Quiz... are you ready?]
		[The second question is a riddle:]
		[My first is in Santa but never in Tanned, my second in Piano but never in Planned. My third is in County and also Tyrone, my fourth is in Goal but never in Loan!]
		[It's something that is quite common over the holiday season! ]
		[_(To submit your answer, simply head to the "Discussions about the game" forum, and find the Holiday Quiz thread.)_]
		
		[Come back and see me tomorrow for the third question!
	</phase>
</d>

<d place="fountj" name="Simploz" gfx="lutin" cond="gvar(xavent,2)+event(xmasavent)">
	<phase id="begin" frame="simploz" background="2">
		[Hello again Dinoz master!]
		[Day three in the DinoRPG quest for knowledge:]
		[The third question is a competition:]
		[* "What is your favourite joke ?" * The funniest one wins the prize !]
		[_(To submit your answer, simply head to the "Discussions about the game" forum, and find the Holiday Quiz thread.)_]
		
		[Come back and see me tomorrow for the fourth question!
	</phase>
</d>

<d place="fountj" name="Simploz" gfx="lutin" cond="gvar(xavent,3)+event(xmasavent)">
	<phase id="begin" frame="simploz" background="2">
		[Back again I see.. welcome!]
		[Well here you are, day number 4, this is the fill in the blanks round:]
		[* "When I'm in the middle of combat on DinoRPG, I _____________ ." * The funniest one wins a prize !]
		[_(To submit your answer, simply head to the "Discussions about the game" forum, and find the Holiday Quiz thread.)_]
		
		[Come back and see me tomorrow for the fifth question!]
	</phase>
</d>

<d place="fountj" name="Simploz" gfx="lutin" cond="gvar(xavent,4)+event(xmasavent)">
	<phase id="begin" frame="simploz" background="2">
		[Hello there Dinoz master!]
		[Are you ready for today's question? Good, then I'll begin:]
		[Today we'd like you to come up with an unlikely title for a news article on DinoRPG]
		[* For example, "Free unlimited napodinoz for everyone until March 2016!" * The funniest one wins a prize !]
		[_(To submit your answer, simply head to the "Discussions about the game" forum, and find the Holiday Quiz thread.)_]
		
		[Come back and see me tomorrow for the sixth question!]
	</phase>
</d>


<d place="fountj" name="Simploz" gfx="lutin" cond="gvar(xavent,5)+event(xmasavent)">
	<phase id="begin" frame="simploz" background="2">
		[Hi Dinoz master! Hope you're feeling festive!]
		[Todays question : What is your holiday wish?]
		[* For example, "For Epoq to marry Scarlett Johanssen and name their first child Dino is a good one..." * The top answers win prizes!]
		[_(To submit your answer, simply head to the "Discussions about the game" forum, and find the Holiday Quiz thread.)_]
		
		[Come back and see me tomorrow for the next question!]
	</phase>
</d>

<d place="fountj" name="Simploz" gfx="lutin" cond="gvar(xavent,6)+event(xmasavent)">
	<phase id="begin" frame="simploz" background="2">
		[Hi Dinoz master! Long time no see!]
		[Question number seven. Are you ready?:]
		[Today all you need to do is name one of your favourite movies.]
		[* If it matches any of the films in the admins top 10, you'll be in the draw for a prize!]
		[_(To submit your answer, simply head to the "Discussions about the game" forum, and find the Holiday Quiz thread.)_]
		
		[Come back and see me tomorrow for question number eight!]
	</phase>
</d>

<d place="fountj" name="Simploz" gfx="lutin" cond="gvar(xavent,7)+event(xmasavent)">
	<phase id="begin" frame="simploz" background="2">
	[Good day there!]
	[Seven rounds down, it's time for number 8:]
		[We want you to come up with a theme song for DinoRPG]
		[* You don't need to write the lyrics, just give us the title (and an explanation if needed) and our favourites win a prize!]
		[_(To submit your answer, simply head to the "Discussions about the game" forum, and find the Holiday Quiz thread.)_]
		
		[I'll have question number nine for you tomorrow!]
	</phase>
</d>

<d place="fountj" name="Simploz" gfx="lutin" cond="gvar(xavent,8)+event(xmasavent)">
	<phase id="begin" frame="simploz" background="2">
	[You've got the hang of this now - here we go with an easy one!]
	[Question 9:]
	 [_(What do you enjoy most about DinoRPG and why? Short answers only please)_]
	 [_(Sarcasm, such as *handsome admins*, will not win, even if you mean it :p )_]
		[_(To submit your answer, simply head to the "Discussions about the game" forum, and find the Holiday Quiz thread.)_]
		
		[I'll have question number ten for you tomorrow!]
	</phase>
</d>

<d place="fountj" name="Simploz" gfx="lutin" cond="gvar(xavent,9)+event(xmasavent)">
	<phase id="begin" frame="simploz" background="2">
	[We really have to stop meeting like this... OK, day 10 !]
	[Our last question :]
	 [_(If you could go anywhere in the world right now, and still log in to DinoRPG obviously, where would it be, and why? )_]
	_(We hope you've enjoyed this opportunity to find out a little bit about and hopefully have some fun with the community.)_
	[We're not quite done yet though. Some of you may have met my friends last year, and they seem really keen to come back, maybe with some more prizes".]
	[That said, they do get around, they could be anywhere, so keep your eyes open! Good Luck!]
	</phase>
</d>
