<!--  QUETE DE l'appeau : permet l'accés au Dome Soulaflotte -->

<d place="chutes" name="Atlantean Guard" gfx="apostoph" cond="admin()|fx(bouee)">

	<phase id="begin" next="rasca:thanks">
		The Underwater Dome can only be accessed with a Scorpscuba.
	</phase>

	<a id="rasca"cond="!fx(rasca)">A what?!?</a>
	<a id="thanks" cond="fx(rasca)">Ok, thanks!</a>

	<phase id="rasca" next="where:thanks">
		A Scorpscuba is a big fish with hollow bones that stores enough oxygen to travel to the depths
		of the Underwater Dome. Well, it usually stores enough oxygen....
	</phase>

	<a id="where">Do you know where I can find one?</a>

	<phase id="where" next="call:thanks">
		Scorpscubas are very common here. You just have to know how to call them.
	</phase>

	<a id="call">Great! ... Hmmm ... have you got their number?</a>

	<phase id="call" next="appeau:thanks">
		Oh dear, young Dinoz Masters, when will they understand. In fact, you need a special object: a Scorpscuba caller.
		It's a small flute that you place in the water. It simulates the wave pattern of a
		huge malefic black shark from the pestillential abyss, the perfect meal for all Scorpscubas.
		They dash for it and you use it to ride down to the Dome.
	</phase>

	<a id="appeau">A Caller...</a>

	<phase id="appeau" next="old:thanks">
		Yes. A Scorpscuba Caller is made from the bones of very old Scorpscuba. Of course,
		the older scorscuba are far more bad-tempered and dangerous than younger Scorpascubas....
	</phase>

	<a id="old">Ummm...</a>

	<phase id="old" next="thanks" effect="jvbz">
		I have a friend, Joveboze, who is fisherman at Frish Port.
		If you think you're up to it, I'll ask him to take you out to hunt an old, giant Scorpscuba so you can get yourself a quality flute.
	</phase>

	<phase id="thanks">
		Enjoy your stay on the Atlanteid Islands.
	</phase>

</d>

<d place="port" name="Joveboze" gfx="joveboze" cond="fx(jvbz)">

	<phase id="begin" next="trad:sry">
		He'a li'l boy! ya wanto kik old Scorpass?
	</phase>

	<a id="sry">... sorry?!?</a>
	<a id="trad">Get an interpreter</a>

	<phase id="trad" fast="1">
		Nobody here seems to ever understand what Joveboze is saying. You have a feeling that it's
		a local dialect of the Frishers, or even a language which Joveboze has created himself.
	</phase>

	<phase id="sry" next="go:trad">
		Ifyar notrady dont'ome, elsjump inthboat, k?
	</phase>

	<a id="go">Follow Joveboze</a>

	<phase id="go" next="attack:back" fast="1">
		Joveboze takes you out to sea, it seems ships avoid this area. After a short wait, you see something in the water:
		a huge Scorpscuba! If the Atlantean Guard was right, you're about to be attacked. What are you going to do!
	</phase>

	<a id="attack">Attack!</a>
	<a id="back" target="attack">Step back!</a>

	<phase id="attack" fight="rasca" bg="rasca" noeffect="jvbz" effect="rasca" fast="1">
		After capturing the Scorpscuba, Joveboze takes you back to Frish Port and begins carving your flute.
		He hasn't said anything since the Scorpscuba attack though he does occasionally look at you approvingly out of the corner of his eye.
		After he finishes carving your flute, he gives you a firm handshake, wishes you luck on your future travels and then hands you the Scorpscuba Caller.
	</phase>

</d>



