
<d place="auree" name="Nicolas Mulot" gfx="hulot">

	<phase id="begin" next="welcome:sick:sickstatus" fast="1">
		A man dressed in safari clothing is standing at the Edge of the Grumhel Jungle. He seems to be waiting for something....
	</phase>
	<a id="welcome" cond="!mission(toxic)|mission(hucure)">Talk to him</a>
	<a id="sick" cond="!curmission(hucure)+mission(toxic)+!mission(hucure)">Talk to him</a>
	<a id="sickstatus" cond="curmission(hucure)">Talk to him</a>

	<phase id="welcome" next="who:better:missions">
		Grumhel Jungle! This wild yet tranquil place is protected from agressors by its dangerous wildlife.
		Today the Jungle has a mysterious aura that charms hundreds of explorers every year!
	</phase>

	<a id="who" cond="!mission(hucure)">But ... who are you?</a>
	<a id="better" cond="mission(hucure)">You seem to be much better...</a>
	<a cond="fx(humiss)+(!mission(toxic)|mission(hucure))" id="missions">Check missions list</a>

	<phase id="who" next="role">
		Nicolas Mulot! journalist for Ouïaïa magazine and lover of Dinoland!
	</phase>

	<a id="role">Isn't it a bit dangerous for a journalist to be here?</a>

	<phase id="role" next="flora:fauna:myst:missions">
		Not for an extreme journalist like me. I'm here to discover all things wild! 
		An undiscovered world, beautiful wildlife, wonderous plants in all their glory,
		there are so many fabulous things to discover at every turn!
	</phase>
	<a id="myst">What kind of mysteries exist here?</a>
	<a id="fauna">Tell me about the Jungle wildlife...</a>
	<a id="flora">Are there nice plants around here?</a>
	<a id="fear" cond="!fx(humiss)">Ah ... you're scared? Is it that you don't want to enter the jungle alone?</a>

	<phase id="myst" next="fear:flora:fauna:missions">
		I don't know for the moment ... But ... I am sure that there are a lot of fabulous things
		hidden in this jungle! You just have to be daring enough to enter ....
	</phase>

	<phase id="flora" next="whynot:fauna:myst:missions">
		The beauty of these millenium trees is hidden to most, but
		for those who know where to look, they're a sensual delight. Exotic scents,
		multicoloured flowers, luxurious vegetation, Grumhel Jungle really is a wonder of Mother Nature!
	</phase>

	<a id="whynot">Why haven't you entered the jungle then?</a>

	<phase id="whynot" next="fear:other:missions">
		Let's just say that there are some pretty dangerous plants in the jungle ... like the
		"Black Virulent Toxicae" or the "Giant Liver-Eating Lily"....
	</phase>

	<phase id="fauna" next="flora:myst:missions">
		Between Bramble Eaters, Korgons and Tawny-Bats. The Grumhel Jungle contains many hidden dangers
		beyond your wildest dreams! Much like Hostile Land and Promised Land, this part of Dinoland
		cannot be so easily travelled....
	</phase>

	<phase id="fear" next="explore:other">
		I think it would be a good idea to first plan a reconnaissance mission before choosing to delve into depths
		of Grumhel Jungle!
	</phase>

	<a id="explore">I can help you if you want?</a>
	<a id="other">I have another question!</a>

	<phase id="explore" next="missions" effect="humiss">
		That would be an excellent idea! The jungle is difficult to explore single-handedly,
		a helping hand would be very welcome indeed. Thanks young man!
	</phase>

	<phase id="other" next="flora:fauna:myst:missions">
		Are you sure you want to enter the mysterious Grumhel Jungle?
	</phase>


	<phase id="sick" next="problem" fast="1">
		While Nicolas Mulot is talking you notice, with horror, that his face is puffing up and is beginning
		to become covered with warts and spots!!
	</phase>

	<a id="problem">Wooaaww! What's happening to your face!?!</a>

	<phase id="problem" next="curesearch">
		Ehmm ... Hellow. I don't meen two bwe roode, but I fink that the plwaants you have bwought were
		 a bit... ehmm tofic ...
		I fink fhat my plwaant allergies are plwaying up ... Can
		you maybe felp me to fwind a rwemedy? ...
	</phase>

	<a id="curesearch">Let's see...</a>

	<phase id="curesearch" missions="hulot"></phase>
	<phase id="missions" missions="hulot"></phase>

	<phase id="sickstatus" next="curesearch">
		So, have you fwound a rebedy?
	</phase>

	<phase id="better" next="flora:fauna:myst:missions">
		The remedy you gave me worked perfectly!
	</phase>

</d>
