<!-- QUETE DU MINEUR : pelle utilisable une fois et réparable -->

<d place="corail" name="Coral Miner" gfx="mineur" cond="fx(bouee)">

	<phase id="begin" next="yes:nothing:repair:nothing2:repair2:give:no">
		Pinc! Pinc! Pinc! Pffff this coral is harder than stone, have you noticed that before?
	</phase>

	<a id="yes" cond="!fx(pelle)+!fx(brkpel)+!fx(pelle2)+!fx(brkpe2)">Yes</a>
	<a id="nothing" cond="fx(pelle)">Yes</a>
	<a id="repair" cond="fx(brkpel)">Yes</a>
	<a id="nothing2" cond="fx(pelle2)">Yes</a>
	<a id="repair2" cond="fx(brkpe2)">Yes</a>	
	<a id="give" cond="scenario(magnet,8)+!fx(corail)">Great!</a>
	<a id="no">No</a>

	<phase id="yes" next="thanks" effect="pelle">
		Ah, so you already know about that? Here, take this old shovel. I'll lend it to you so you can dig.
		It's in pretty bad condition, so it's likely to break after just one use, but it's a lucky shovel.
		It'll help you dig up the biggest treasures in all of Dinoland! What do you say?
	</phase>

	<phase id="nothing" next="thanks">
		So do you like my shovel? What do you say?
	</phase>

	<phase id="repair" next="thanks" effect="pelle" noeffect="brkpel">
		You've broken my shovel? Give it to me! There you go, I've fixed it! Ah! Hold on, aren't you forgetting something?
	</phase>
	
	<phase id="nothing2" next="thanks">
		So, do you like my shovel with the ergonomic handle? What do you say?
	</phase>

	<phase id="repair2" next="thanks" effect="pelle2" noeffect="brkpe2">
		Ah it's you? So you broke my shovel? Wait there... there you go, i've fixed it!... Hey! Are you not forgetting something?
	</phase>	

	<a id="thanks">Thanks!</a>

	<phase id="thanks">
		You're welcome! Come back whenever your shovel is broken. I'll fix it.
	</phase>

	<phase id="no" next="next">
		Pffff, it's very difficult to dig here, that's why it requires strong men like me to do this job.
	</phase>

	<a id="next">Really?</a>

	<phase id="next" next="next2">
		Yeah! I'm not joking. Check out these muscles! I've even been nominated in the Heavy Miner category at this year's Coral Awards.
	</phase>

	<a id="next2">Are you being serious?</a>

	<phase id="next2" next="next3">
		Yes! Absolutely! I'll have to work very hard if I want to look like my idol...
	</phase>

	<a id="next3">...</a>

	<phase id="next3" next="qui">
		Hello? You're not going to ask me who my idol is?
	</phase>

	<a id="qui">Ermm ... who's your idol?</a>

	<phase id="qui" next="ok">
		Why, the one-and-only Sylverter Staline of course. He's the three-time winner of the Coral Awards in the
		Ultimate Muscles and Retorts That Kill categories. He's so cool, and he always kills the bad guys!
	</phase>

	<a id="ok">He must be really strong!</a>

	<phase id="ok">
		Yes, he's the strongest! Ahh, the good old days. I could talk about them for hours...
		but, it's time to leave. I have work to do! See you later!
		Pinc! Pinc! Pinc!
	</phase>

	<phase id="give" effect="corail">
		Ah! I see you like the Coral too! Here, take this, I'll give you a sample,
		I broke this little piece off earlier!
	</phase>

</d>
