<d place="frcbrt" name="Madam X" gfx="mmex" cond="active(mmex)+(admin()|(mission(fish)+mission(dog)))">

	<phase id="begin" fast="1" next="talk">
		While passing through BrutForce, you come across a woman. She waves and calls you over.
	</phase>

	<a id="talk">Talk To Her</a>

	<phase id="talk" next="talk2">
		Why there you are young Dinoz Master! I've been hearing so much about you.
		Grandpa Joe has been talking about you, he's been saying that you're handling his missions quite well.
	</phase>

	<a id="talk2">...</a>

	<phase id="talk2" next="missions:question">
		As you seem to be so reliable, I'd also like to entrust you with a few missions of my own. Naturally you're free to accept or refuse them as you wish!
	</phase>

	<a id="missions">List of Missions</a>
	<a id="question">But who are you?</a>

	<phase id="question" next="question2">
		Who am I? I'm so sorry my young friend, where are my manners? I should have introduced myself.
	</phase>

	<a id="question2">So who are you?</a>

	<phase id="question2" next="double">
		Well, I can't really say. I'm really sorry, but if the wrong people find out that you know who I am,
		it could get you into trouble! But I want to assure you that you can trust me, therefore I'll let you into a little secret.
	</phase>

	<a id="double">Oh?</a>

	<phase id="double" next="double2">
		Let's see .... I suppose that you've learnt that each skill corresponds to a unique element,
		out of the 5 possible elements. For example, Wrath corresponds to the Fire element and Perception to the Water element.
	</phase>

	<a id="double2">Yes!</a>

	<phase id="double2" next="double3">
		But .... that's not all! Some skills are linked to two elements rather than one!
		They're called double-skills. A double-skill can be earned by studying from either of the two elements
		concerned, but it requires knowledge of specific skills from each element.
	</phase>

	<a id="double3">!!!!</a>

	<phase id="double3" next="learn:already">
		I can understand why you're so surprised, it's a well-guarded secret. However, to be able to learn these skills
		you must first master the Double-Skill. It's a secret skill that only the Drag.... what am I saying, I've already said too much!
	</phase>

	<a id="learn" cond="!skill(multi)">How do I learn it?</a>
	<a id="already" cond="skill(multi)">How do I learn it?</a>

	<phase id="learn" next="learn1:learn2:learn3:learn4:learn5:no">
		It's easy, you only need to do "this" and....
	</phase>

	<a id="learn1" target="dolearn" cond="(skill(waikk)+skill(cocon))|(skill(combus)+skill(zero))">And?</a>
	<a id="learn2" target="dolearn" cond="(skill(kamikz)+skill(kaos))|(skill(venge)+skill(talona))">Ah??</a>
	<a id="learn3" target="dolearn" cond="(skill(resmag)+skill(clone))|(skill(etatpr)+skill(gaia))">Huh???</a>
	<a id="learn4" target="dolearn" cond="(skill(instin)+skill(paumej))|(skill(marecg)+skill(foudre))">Oh!</a>
	<a id="learn5" target="dolearn" cond="(skill(sappe)+skill(formev))|(skill(adrena)+skill(elasti))">What...</a>
	<a id="no">(ouch)</a>

	<phase id="dolearn" skill="multi">
		Yes! It worked! You see, wasn't that easy? Your Dinoz is now master of the Double-Skill, Congratulations!
	</phase>

	<phase id="no">
		No .... it's not working .... if it peaks when I'm doing "that" or if your Dinoz hasn't learned the required skills
		in order for your Dinoz to master the Double-Skill, it won't work. Come back later to try again!
	</phase>

	<phase id="already">
		It seems that you have already mastered it! Aha!
	</phase>

	<phase id="missions" missions="mmex"></phase>

</d>
