<!-- QUETE DE LA PERLE : perle de la fontaine de jouvence -->
<!-- 	+ révélation de l'utilisation du Gant			  -->

<d place="chutes" name="Master Hydargol" gfx="hydargol" cond="admin()|fx(bouee)">

	<phase id="begin" next="talk" fast="1">
		The Mutant Falls are one of the most popular places for Zenzen monks to meditate. That's
		why you can often find them walking around here. They often sit on large waterlily pads,
		and try to meditate for as long as possible ... without being swept away by the current!
		Many monks who fall asleep often fall in and are never seen again.
	</phase>

	<a id="talk">Talk to Master Hydargol</a>

	<phase id="talk" next="hello:help:give:act">
		Hello......
	</phase>

	<a id="hello" target="talk">Hello!</a>
	<a id="help" cond="!fx(nenuph)+!collec(perle)">Can I help you?</a>
	<a id="give" cond="fx(nenuph)+!fx(chutes)">Give the waterlily pads</a>
	<a id="act" cond="collec(perle)">What's up?</a>

	<phase id="help" next="get">
		Ah? Uh ... yes ... can you ... bring me ...Zzzz ... zzz....
	</phase>

	<a id="get">Bring you... ?</a>

	<phase id="get" next="where">
		Ah? Uh ... yes ... bring me ... a... waterlily.....pad.....
	</phase>

	<a id="where">Where can I find one?</a>

	<phase id="where" effect="zenbro">
		Find ... my ... apprentice padamonk ... Zzz ... zzz....
	</phase>

	<phase id="give" noeffect="nenuph" collection="perle">
		Thanks... at last...I'll be able to......meditate at... the Falls!!!!
		I would like to offer you this Pearl as a reward.  It has been added to your collection of items!
	</phase>

	<phase id="act" next="gant">
		Youhouhhh!!! That's great! Look ... I'm levitating!
	</phase>

	<a id="gant" cond="fx(gant)+!fx(chutes)">Show Zors Glove</a>

	<phase id="gant" next="why">
		Oooh!!! You have a Zors Glove, that's incredible!
	</phase>

	<a id="why">Why?</a>

	<phase id="why" next="super">
		Let me explain. The Zors glove has the ability to stop the Falls from flowing.
		This means that, with the help of the waterlily pad, you'll be able to go around the Falls and
		access Grumhel Forest.
	</phase>

	<a id="super">That's great news!</a>

	<phase id="super" next="ok:no">
		Well, if you promise to let me use your Glove from time-to-time, I lend you my waterlily
		pad which will allow you to pass through the Falls ... Do we have a deal?
	</phase>

	<a id="ok">Ok</a>
	<a id="no" target="why">No way</a>

	<phase id="ok" effect="nenuph:chutes">
		Here's your waterlily pad ... Now you'll be able to pass through the Falls. Good luck
		for the rest of your adventure! And take care, the Forest is very dangerous!
	</phase>

</d>

<!-- APPRENTIS -->

<d cond="fx(zenbro)" place="port" name="Apprentice padamonk" gfx="bemol">

	<phase id="begin" next="help">
		Hello! I'm Damper, padamonk of Master Hydargol. I've been sent to fetch these waterlily pads for him.
		The problem is that, I just realised that I get seasick... and I need to take the waterlily pads to the Atlanteid Islands.
		I don't know what to do!!!
	</phase>

	<a id="help">I'm going there too. I can take them with me if you would like?</a>

	<phase id="help" next="get">
		Really, you'll help me?? Thank you so much!
	</phase>

	<a id="get">You're welcome</a>

	<phase id="get" noeffect="zenbro" effect="nenuph">
		I'm so glad that I can count on you! Here, take the waterlily pads. Thank you again!
	</phase>

</d>