<!-- ***************************************************************************** -->
<!-- Nox, Dorogon, habitant de la cité Dorogon ----->

<d place="ville2" name="Nox" gfx="nox" cond="scenario(nimba2,50-)">
	<phase id="begin" next="ramolo" fast="1" frame="stop">
		An imposing Dorogon is watching you.
		Bigger and stronger than all the other inhabitants, he is silently sizing you up.
	</phase>
	
	<a id="ramolo">Hello Master Dorogon.</a>
	
	<phase id="ramolo" next="ok:baston">
		[I'm still searching for an elite warrior against whom I can test my might.]
		[We must be the strongest in the world, and given that the Caushemesh invasion will happen sooner or later, we must be ready!]
		[Pistachio, if you don't put any effort in, you'll be weak your entire life.
		You must be strong if one day you wish to surpass the legacy of your father and become an Archdorogon worthy of the name!]
	</phase>
	
	<a id="ok">(Pistachio, Archdorogon? haha...)</a>
	
	<phase id="ok" frame="stop" fast="1">
		You set off, this Dorogon, unlike the others, is overtly aggressive.
		It's probably best not to bug hime for stories.
	</phase>
	
	<a id="baston" cond="scenario(nimba2,31)">I can try to test your strength!</a>
	
	<phase id="baston" next="bravo" give="ptsage" scenario="nimba2:32" fightgroup="dorou">
		[Congratulations, you managed to make me drop to one knee.]
		[Perhaps the rest of you that live on the surface, will be able to resist the Caushemesh hordes for a while.
		Fortunately enough for you, we won't hang around in coming to help.]
		[In any case, you've definitely earned this point of wisdom.]
	</phase>
	
	<a id="bravo">Thanks very much!</a>
	
	<phase id="bravo" frame="stop" fast="1">
		You head off from the Dorogon, clearly he doesn't have much of a soft spot for the Caushemesh people.
		Is the situation as critical as it seems to be?
		You now have three points of wisdom, just two left to go!
	</phase>
</d>

<d place="ville2" name="Nox" gfx="nox" cond="scenario(nimba2,51+)">
	<phase id="begin" fast="1" frame="stop">
		Hello Dinoz Master.
		I am the Archdorogon Pistachio's new bodyguard, even if my role largely consists of protecting him from himself...
	</phase>
</d>