<!--	QUETE DU PROFESSEUR : bouee & materiel d'escalade
			+ infos sur les différentes zones
			+ infos sur le gant des zors
			+ transforme pierre en totem ashpouk
 -->

<d place="univ" name="Professor Eugene" gfx="eugene">

	<phase id="begin" next="talk" fast="1">
		Once inside the University library, you meet the famous Professor Eugene. He's
		well known for his interest in Dinoz Masters. He often asks you many questions
		in exchange for useful techniques for your Dinoz, along with other important information about Dinoland.
	</phase>

	<a id="talk">Professor Eugene</a>

	<phase id="talk" next="question:nothing:nothing2:learn:learn_water:learn_fire:learn_done">
		Hello young Dinoz Master. So, how is everything going? I remember
		when I was your age, I walked all over Dinoland! Don't hesitate to come back
		if you want any help or clues to any of the mysteries that intrigue you.

		On top of that, I can teach your Dinoz some very useful techniques. I can only make this offer
		if your Dinoz is ready. My lessons are very dangerous and can be fatal if your Dinoz is not ready.
	</phase>

	<a id="question">Ask a question</a>

	<!-- APPRENTISSAGE -->

	<a id="nothing" cond="!level(5)">Learn</a>
	<a id="learn" cond="level(5)+!fx(bouee)+!fx(matesc)">Learn</a>
	<a id="nothing2" cond="!level(7)+(fx(bouee)|fx(matesc))">Learn</a>
	<a id="learn_water" cond="level(7)+fx(matesc)+!fx(bouee)">Learn</a>
	<a id="learn_fire" cond="level(7)+fx(bouee)+!fx(matesc)">Learn</a>
	<a id="learn_done" cond="fx(bouee)+fx(matesc)">Learn</a>

	<phase id="nothing">
		Well then, let's see. Sit your Dinoz down there .... perfect. (he pulls out a small pocket light) ... Let's see your teeth. Say "Ahhhh!" ...  Mmmm ... it seems your Dinoz is still a bit too young ... I can't teach him anything at the moment.
		Come back to me when your Dinoz reaches Level 5.
	</phase>

	<phase id="nothing2">
		Let's see ... (he proceeds to examine your Dinoz ...) It seems that your Dinoz has improved since the last time I saw you. However, he isn't strong enough to learn the second technique ... his body won't be able to handle it. I think we should wait for him to reach level 6 ... Mmmm no, level 7, is safer.
	</phase>

	<phase id="learn" next="water:fire">
		So your Dinoz wants to learn a new technique? Your Dinoz will have to fight a monster. I will only train him if he wins. Which technique would you like me to teach him?
	</phase>

	<a id="water">Swimming with a buoy</a>
	<a id="fire">Climbing</a>

	<phase id="water" next="water_fight:back">
		Very well. If your Dinoz wins this challenge, I'll teach him how to use the Buoy. Your Dinoz will then be able to cross areas of water.
	</phase>

	<phase id="fire" next="fire_fight:back">
		Climbing isn't an easy technique to master, you must be in possession of the Climbing Gear in order to learn it.
		If your Dinoz wins the battle against this monster, I'll provide some equipment and teach him the basics.
		Your Dinoz will then be able to climb the Big All-Hot.
	</phase>

	<a id="water_fight">Fight</a>
	<a id="fire_fight">Fight</a>
	<a id="back" target="learn">Go back</a>

	<phase id="water_fight" fight="ewater" effect="bouee">
		Well done! You were very impressive! As promised, I will give your Dinoz a buoy. Your Dinoz should now be able to access
		the Atlanteid Islands to the south of Dinoland. Good luck, and be careful!
	</phase>

	<phase id="fire_fight" fight="efire" effect="matesc">
		Well done! You were very impressive! As promised, I will give your Dinoz the Climbing Gear. Your Dinoz should now be able to climb up
		the precipitous slopes of the Big All-Hot. The Monsters there are very warm, so be careful when you're climbing!
	</phase>

	<phase id="learn_water" next="water_fight">
		You want the Buoy? First you're going to have to fight this monster!
	</phase>

	<phase id="learn_fire" next="fire_fight">
		You want the Climbing Gear? First you're going to have to fight this monster!
	</phase>

	<phase id="learn_done">
		I have nothing else to teach to your Dinoz. But don't worry, there are people throughout Dinoland
		who will teach him new techniques!
	</phase>

	<!-- QUESTIONS -->

	<phase id="question" next="dinoville:gtc:atlante:stone:gant:noquestion">
		I love questions! What do you want to know,young Dinoz master?
	</phase>

	<a id="dinoville">Dinotown Kingdom</a>
	<a id="atlante" cond="level(8)">Atlanteid Islands</a>
	<a id="gtc" cond="level(5)">Big All-Hot</a>
	<a id="gant" cond="fx(gant)">Zors Glove</a>
	<a id="stone" cond="fx(astone)">This Old Stone?</a>
	<a id="noquestion">Nothing at all</a>
	<a id="menu" target="question">Go back</a>

	<phase id="dinoville" next="menu">
		The Dinotown Kingdom has been destroyed and rebuilt many times during ancient times.
		Today, it's a civilized and developing place, compared with it's wild surroundings.
		That's the reason why Dinotown is a perfect place for a young Dinoz Master such as yourself!

		Make sure to train your Dinoz well before venturing to other regions of Dinoland as the monsters are far more dangerous!
	</phase>

	<phase id="atlante" next="menu">
		A long time ago, there was an island to the south of Dinoland called Jazz island.
		
		Jazz Island was blasted into the air by an underwater eruption and landed on the plateau of a volcanic
		peak 100 meters in the air. However, little by little the peak was eroded by the waves until
		Jazz Island crashed into the ocean, causing a massive tsunami that wiped out a half of Dinoland and
		destroyed most of the ancient human civilizations in the process.
		
		Today, after many centuries, things are starting to get back to normal,
		but a large part of Dinoland is still wild and dangerous.
		Anyway, the Atlanteid Islands are fragments of Jazz Island.
		
		People say that only Sticky Swamp remains in it's natural state.
	</phase>

	<phase id="gtc" next="menu">
		Hey young Dinoz Master, do you see that small triangle up there? It's actually a huge volcano called
		the Big All-Hot. I advise you to go there, you can eat some really tasty merguez, they're always perfectly grilled.

		When I was younger, I studied the ruins of ancient civilizations. Did you know that thousands of years ago
		on the top of the Big All-Hot, there was an entire civilization called Ashpouk?
		And one day, boom! The volcano erupted and the entire civilization was destroyed! Sad isn't it?

		In any case, I advice you to go excavate the ruins. You might find some ancient relics there, and don't forget to taste the merguez.
	</phase>

	<phase id="gant" next="menu">
		The Zors Glove is a very rare item! People say that the Zors Glove must be used at the Mutant Falls
		to access to Grumhel Forest, but no one knows how to use it.
	</phase>

	<phase id="stone" next="stone_yes:stone_no">
		Ohhhhhh!!! This is really interesting, it seems to be the .... mmmmmmmmm ....
		Actually I'm not too sure ... (he starts staring at the stone) ... can you show me this Stone, so I can examine it more closely?
	</phase>

	<a id="stone_yes">Of course, here it is.</a>
	<a id="stone_no" target="question">Hey! Don't touch it!</a>

	<phase id="stone_yes" noeffect="astone" effect="totem">
		Ooooooohhhhh!!! Yes ... It's exactly what I thought ... Look! (he delicately cleans the stone) ... it's an Ashpouk Totem! It's very valuable ... take care of it!
	</phase>

	<phase id="noquestion">
		That's a shame. Don't hesitate to come back from time-to-time to learn more about Dinoland!
	</phase>

</d>
