<d place="skull" name="Skully" gfx="skully" cond="life(10-)+!fx(skull)">

	<phase id="begin" next="arg:bye:shortcut">
		Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh! Your Dinoz seems to be in a bad state!!
	</phase>

	<a id="arg">Argh! A ghost!</a>
	<a id="bye">Run away</a>
	<a id="shortcut" target="missions" cond="admin()">(admin)</a>

	<phase id="arg" next="bye:arg2">
		A ghost? Aaaah! Where?
	</phase>

	<a id="arg2">You!</a>

	<phase id="arg2" next="diff:bye">
		What? Me? Excuse me! A bit of respect please! You won't last long here if you keep saying silly things like that!

		I'm a SKELETON thank you very much! A skeleton yes! I may look a bit dishevelled, but I'm no ghost!!!
	</phase>

	<a id="diff">What's the difference?</a>

	<phase id="diff" next="free:bye">
		First of all, a ghost is dead, and me, I'm just ... a bit tired, I should have rings under my eyes, that's all ...
		a ghost haunts people. Me? I'm free to do what I please!
		... well almost....
	</phase>

	<a id="free">Almost free? What does that mean?</a>

	<phase id="free" next="haunt:bye">
		It's a bit ... mmmm ... complicated ... I have a few technical problems to resolve.
		Firstly, only Dinoz close to death and their masters can see me, secondly
		I can't leave this shady place....
	</phase>

	<a id="haunt">So you do haunt this place?!</a>

	<phase id="haunt" next="do:bye">
		Haunt this place?!? You must be joking! Ooooooooo! Just imagining it
		gives me the creeps! I have much more important things to do!
	</phase>

	<a id="do">Like what?!</a>

	<phase id="do" next="uhm:bye">
		Shhhhh! Keep quiet! Ok, I'll tell you .... I have a LOVER!
		It may seem weird to think that but when I was much younger I had wonderful legs!
	</phase>

	<a id="uhm">Mmmm....</a>

	<phase id="uhm" next="bonne:bye">
		I promise! It doesn't matter anyway, I've got a
		curse that will make you forget everything about me!
	</phase>

	<a id="bonne">A curse?</a>

	<phase id="bonne" next="reset:next:bye">
		Yes! It's like a curse but in fact it's better! I'm protected by the curse. It helps to prevent nightmares and to keep scientists away.
		Because they would examine me all the time. But thanks to the curse, people forget me instantly after having met me!
	</phase>

	<a id="reset" target="forgot">I don't believe you</a>
	<a id="next">It's not very helpful is it?</a>

	<phase id="next" next="help:nohelp:bye">
		Exactly! I can't leave this place, so I have no way of finding my lover, Moulder!
	</phase>

	<a id="nohelp">Who's Moulder?</a>
	<a id="help">Maybe I can help you.</a>

	<phase id="nohelp" next="forgot">
		You can't help me! Leave me alone. I'm going to sit here and think about him, don't forget to forget me!
	</phase>

	<a id="forgot">...</a>

	<phase id="forgot" fast="1">
		You are certain that you were just talking to someone, but you can't remember who or what you were talking about. Very strange, you feel like you've just seen a ghost! No, that's not possible.
	</phase>

	<phase id="help" next="question:accept:maybe">
		Really!? You would do that for me? It's not going to be easy, and every time you see me you'll forget our meeting instantly!
		Are you sure you want to help me???
	</phase>

	<a id="question" target="forgot">I won't forget anything!</a>
	<a id="accept">Yes! Defintely!</a>
	<a id="maybe" target="forgot">Let me think about it</a>

	<phase id="accept" next="missions">
		Help me to find Moulder and I'll handsomely reward you!
	</phase>

	<a id="missions">What should I do now?</a>

	<phase id="missions" missions="skull">
	</phase>

	<phase id="bye" fast="1">
		The scary skeleton looks at you disapprovingly. You turn back and see that she is close to tears,
		but you continue to run away as far away as possible.
	</phase>

</d>

<d place="skull" name="Skully" gfx="skully" cond="fx(skull)+!mission(skuend)">

	<phase id="begin" next="missions">
		Aha! My curse has disappeared! Can you now help me find Moulder!
	</phase>

	<a id="missions">What should I do now?</a>

	<phase id="missions" missions="skull">
	</phase>

</d>

<d place="skull" name="Skully" gfx="skully" cond="mission(skuend)">

	<phase id="begin" next="pda:dinoz">
		Thanks for all your help! Moulder and I now live happily in this magnificient location with a glorious view
		of the sea! We're so happy together! We can't thank you enough!
	</phase>

	<a id="dinoz" cond="!collec(pda)+!dinoz(15)">Don't mention it, you're welcome</a>
	<a id="pda" cond="!collec(pda)+dinoz(1)">Don't mention it, you're welcome</a>

	<phase id="dinoz">
		Don't be so modest! We wouldn't be back together if it wasn't for you and all your help. Come back to me when you have more Dinoz. I'll give you a gift
		that will help you in your future quests!
	</phase>

	<phase id="pda" collection="pda">
		Don't be so modest! We wouldn't be back together if it wasn't for you and all your help! Here this is for you ... take this Planner. It'll help you
		handle many Dinoz. It will be added to your collection of items. Make sure you take care of it!
	</phase>

</d>


<d place="rashpk" name="Moulder" gfx="mouldeur" cond="curmission(skuend,2)">

	<phase id="begin" next="you">
		Mmmm....These Napalm Shrimp smell delicious! They remind me of my wife's cooking!
	</phase>

	<a id="you">Are you Moulder?</a>

	<phase id="you" next="explain">
		Yes I am! Pleased to meet you! Did you know that there are strange burned circles in the ruins? I've studied these phenomenons
		for a long time and have arrived at a conclusion: there are two explanations for these strange marks....
	</phase>

	<a id="explain">So?</a>

	<phase id="explain" next="other">
		They may have been made by strange creatures from outer space who landed in remote places to study
		human kind. It could be that they create these strange burned circles when they return to their own planet!
		The King may be hiding this information because he is plotting with them! Amazing, isn't it?
	</phase>

	<a id="other">And the other explanation?</a>

	<phase id="other" next="ok">
		Mmmmm, the other explanation seems to be far less plausible, but according to the Merguez Seller, the strange burned circles may be caused
		by tourists who set campfires when they visit the ruins. I know! Crazy idea isn't it?
	</phase>

	<a id="ok">....</a>

	<phase id="ok" next="ok2">
		Mmmm....these Napalm Shrimp are delicious! They instantly remind me of my wife! We were so
		in love ... I miss her so much, it hurts even more knowing that she's dead....
	</phase>

	<a id="ok2">What, you too!</a>

	<phase id="ok2" next="skully">
		What? I hope you're joking. I'm still in my youth! Look how smooth my bones are:
		no wrinkles! Ah ah ah ah ah!
	</phase>

	<a id="skully">Skully is searching everywhere for you!</a>

	<phase id="skully" next="exp">
		What? You know Skully?
	</phase>

	<a id="exp">(You explain the full story)</a>

	<phase id="exp" next="end">
		............. Thanks! That means that my suspicions of her cheating were wrong! I've been right not to look for another woman
		even after all these years! I can't thank you enough, you have no idea what this means to me!
	</phase>

	<a id="end">Don't mention it, you're welcome</a>

	<phase id="end" unlock="skuend">
		Don't be stupid! This would never have happened if it wasn't for you! Come with me to meet my wife again. I'm longing to see her again, I can't wait to look into her beautiful eyes!
	</phase>

</d>

