<d place="dcine" name="Spileberk" gfx="spielborg" cond="event(filmfestival)">

	<phase id="begin" next="ouat:how">
		[Welcome to the Dinoville Film festival!]
		[I am Spileberk, director of India-na-na-na-na-na, Dino Park, Letters from Dino Jima, Clan War of the Worlds...]
		[You may not know this, but you can also take part in the film festival simply by creating your own extraordinary adventure.]
		[At the end of the Festival, votes from other Dinoz masters will decide the winner of the Festival.]
	</phase>
	<a id="ouat">How does it work?</a>
	<phase id="ouat" next="how:go">
		[You have until the *15th of November* to create your film, but watch out, once you have published it, you can't change it again!
		Voting will begin at that moment and will continue for one week.]
		[When the votes are counted, the director with the support from most other masters will receive the coveted Golden Film Reel,
		the most coveted trophy amongst cinephiles!]
		[*Warning! If you don't finish on time, you will no longer have access to the work carried out up until that point, and you will lose your film!*]
	</phase>
	<a id="how">How do I make a good film?</a>
	<phase id="how" next="ouat:go">
		[To get off on the right foot, you need a healthy dose of imagination, a decent measure of suspense, a scoop of action, and a splash of adventure, tension and love!]
		[You then need to break your story down into sections, so that you can keep it on track and so that you know exactly where you're going!]
		[You don't want to make it so long that the viewers fall asleep, ten minutes or so is more than enough for a good story!]
		[The last advice I can give you , given that we are still in the era of silent cinema: make sure you don't make any smelling mistokes,
		it's a good idea to get some of your friends from Dinoland to read it over for you!]
		[I'm sure you'll do a great job!]
	</phase>
	<a id="go">Thanks for all your help!</a>
	<phase id="go">
		[So you want to become a filmmaking legend?]
		[Well then, get your lights and your camera and show us what you've got!]
	</phase>
	
</d>