µ<d place="fountj" name="Strange Creature" gfx="alien" cond="scenario(star,0)+(admin()|time(30))+active(starquest)">

	<phase id="begin" next="yes:no">
		. . . . . me . . . lost . . . . . without power . . stars . . . . never . . . . be able to go .... home . . . . help me?
	</phase>

	<a id="yes">Yes, I'll help you</a>
	<a id="no">No way</a>

	<phase id="no" fast="1">
		It's better not to get involved with people who look like that!
	</phase>

	<phase id="yes" next="nothing">
		........thanks..........a lot...........Ah! Finally! My simultaneous translator is fixed!
		Luckily I had some spare strawberry batteries! Thanks for offering your help my friend!
	</phase>

	<a id="nothing">Please, don't mention it.</a>

	<phase id="nothing" next="dom">
		But it's all thanks to you! As I just told you, I have a little technicological problem.
		My (SiAvUaEs) is completely broken, and I can't go back to (PuOsEniLa)!
	</phase>

	<a id="dom">That's very sad!</a>

	<phase id="dom" next="star">
		I need your help to recover some crystals from (TcEtCiNo)...
		Let me think ... how can I describe them? They look like like shining stars!
	</phase>

	<a id="star">Stars?</a>

	<phase id="star" next="how">
		Yes! If you bring me seven stars. I'll be able to finish my journey, and maybe
		reward you with a (CiLoJuAeDa) from my planet!
	</phase>

	<a id="how">And how do I find these stars?</a>

	<phase id="how" next="ah">
		It's relatively easy. All you have to do is complete missions which are listed
		in the Eclectik Tourist Guide. Each time I read out a mission description, you'll have complete it!
	</phase>

	<a id="ah">"Ah"?</a>

	<phase id="ah" scenario="star:1">
		Hmmmm, ..., well! I'm going to get the Tourist Guide. Wait here, I'll be back in a minute....
	</phase>

</d>

<d place="fountj" name="Strange Creature" gfx="alien" cond="scenario(star,1)">

	<phase id="begin" next="et">
		The Guide says: "A megawolf is waiting you in the capital!"
	</phase>

	<a id="et">And?</a>

	<phase id="et">
		And? That's all! You'll have to carry this mission out alone. Sorry to be so eclectic!
	</phase>

</d>

<d place="fountj" name="Strange Creature" gfx="alien" cond="scenario(star,2+)+!scenario(star,8+)">

	<phase id="begin" next="star2:star3:star4:star5:star6:star7">
		Ah! I see that you're progressing with your quest! Let see what the Tourist Guide says next....
	</phase>

	<a id="star2" cond="scenario(star,2)">Listen</a>
	<a id="star3" cond="scenario(star,3)">Listen</a>
	<a id="star4" cond="scenario(star,4)">Listen</a>
	<a id="star5" cond="scenario(star,5)">Listen</a>
	<a id="star6" cond="scenario(star,6)">Listen</a>
	<a id="star7" cond="scenario(star,7)">Listen</a>

	<phase id="star2" next="end">
		The guide says: "The enthusiastic greasy man would appreciate a transported cloud" ... does that mean anything to you?
	</phase>

	<phase id="star3" next="end">
		Tourist Guide, page 879 indent B: "When you get stuck up to the neck, nothing is better than a nice cake". Does that mean anything to you?
	</phase>

	<phase id="star4" next="end">
		The guide says: "The shaddy hole call will serve you" ... Do you have any ideas??
	</phase>

	<phase id="star5" next="end">
		The next one is written in small text. It says: "The old bones like to watch a ... capsicum" , yup ... that's all it says ... I think
	</phase>

	<phase id="star6" next="end">
		Appendix B of the Tourist Guide: "Visit the godman at noon at Pek-1". Mmmmmmm....
	</phase>

	<phase id="star7" next="end">
		The last missing star! The Guide says: "At the country of Saru, you will return from the dead without firework". Sounds dangerous!
	</phase>

	<a id="end">...</a>

	<phase id="end">
		Your language is a bit strange ... I don't understand it!
	</phase>

</d>

<d place="fountj" name="Strange Creature" gfx="alien" cond="scenario(star,8)">

	<phase id="begin" next="ok">
		.... Yeaaaahh!!! Thanks a lot! I'll finally be able to return to (PuOsEniLa)!
		I have to hurry though, as the stars are aligning in the Rochechouart.
	</phase>

	<a id="ok">....</a>

	<phase id="ok" next="give">
		Can you give me the stars. I'll give you a (CiLoJuAeDa) in exchange,
		plus a trinket I found in Dinoland!
	</phase>

	<a id="give">Hand over the 7 stars</a>

	<phase id="give" use="star:7" collection="plume" give="cgold:1" fast="1" scenario="star:9">
		The Stange Creature ran into some kind of a small house, then a lightning struck and the house disappeared. All that remains are
		burned traces on the ground and column of smoke rising up into the sky ... He left you
		one "Gold Napodino" and a strange epic item....
	</phase>


</d>

<d place="rashpk" name="Merguez Seller (Quest)" gfx="merguez" cond="scenario(star,2)+equip(burger)">

	<phase id="begin" next="ok">
		Oh I see that your Dinoz is carrying a cloud burger! Did you know that they're bad for your health?
		Unless you want your Dinoz to become a Sumo?!?
	</phase>

	<a id="ok">...</a>

	<phase id="ok" next="star">
		Throw away your Burger and taste my merguez instead! Take this item as a sign of loyalty. I found it on the ground!
	</phase>

	<a id="star">Ah?</a>

	<phase id="star" fast="1" give="star" scenario="star:3">
		Great! The merguez seller has given you one of the seven magic stars!
	</phase>

</d>

<d place="skull" name="Skully (Quest)" gfx="skully" cond="scenario(star,5)+equip(ppoiv)">

	<phase id="begin" next="ok">
		Oh oh!! What do we have here!!! It's a magnificent "Capsicum annuum"! What colours, what odours, it's absolutely beau-ti-ful!
	</phase>

	<a id="ok">.....</a>

	<phase id="ok" next="star">
		Thank you so much! In exchange, I'm going
		to give you this item. I found it while searching for a lost bone! Take it!
	</phase>

	<a id="star">Ah?</a>

	<phase id="star" fast="1" give="star" scenario="star:6">
		Congratulations! Thanks to Skully, you've found the 5th magic star! You only have 2 more to find!
	</phase>

</d>

<d place="baobob" name="Bao Bob (Quest)" gfx="baobob" cond="scenario(star,6)+(admin()|hour(5)|hour(6)|hour(7))">

	<phase id="begin" next="ok">
		What are you doing in my house at this time in the morning?
	</phase>

	<a id="ok">I'm looking for something......</a>

	<phase id="ok" next="star">
		Sorry, I'm not fully awake yet. I had no idea. Here, take this, I've been keeping it for you.
		I hope it won't cause you any problems...
	</phase>

	<a id="star">????</a>

	<phase id="star" fast="1" give="star" scenario="star:7">
		Bao Bob has entrusted you with the 6th magic star! Only one left!!!
	</phase>

</d>
