<missions>

	<m group="skull" id="skul1" name="Prologue">
		<begin>
			Years ago when we were living together, Moulder was affected by my curse. He forgot me instantly. It's not my fault, I have no way of controlling the curse.
			After he forgot me, Moulder moved far, far away, the ruffian! I'm sure he's still in contact
			with his nephew Little Joe. Go and see him, make sure to keep me informed!
		</begin>
		<goto v="papy" hide="1"/>
		<talk v="Grandpa Little Joe" gfx="papy">
			Uncle Moulder? It's been a long time since I've heard from him.
			If you want to know more, bring me three Goblin Merguez from the Big All-Hot!
		</talk>
		<use v="mergz" n="3"/>
		<talk v="Grandpa Little Joe" gfx="papy">
			Thanks! (munch, munch) all I know is that Uncle Moulder loved his
			wife. He engraved a message for her on the Fountain of Youth.
		</talk>
		<goto v="fountj"/>
		<action v="Read the Message">
			On one of the engravings on the Fountain of Youth, you read the following message:
			"I'll be waiting for you at the place we first met"
		</action>
		<end>
			Thanks. This information is priceless. My dear Moulder can't be far away, we'll be together again soon!
		</end>
		<xp v="10"/>
	</m>

	<m group="skull" id="skul2" name="On Moulder's Trail" cond="mission(skul1)">
		<begin>
			"I'll be waiting for you at the place we first met" Oh oh oh oh! My Moulder is so romantic!
			I hope he's still waiting there for me! Go quickly to the magnificient place filled
			with the odour of waterillies where we first met and bring me back my love!
		</begin>
		<goto v="marais" hide="1"/>
		<talk v="A Stuck Tourist">
			I'm sick of this sh... Swamp!!!!! It's the third time our Motor-Home has got stuck here, what a dumb idea to come on VACATION IN A SWAMP!!! What? Have I seen someone called Moulder? Ah! Yes, he was going to an Anonymous Eeloz Association meeting! Be careful is you decide to go too, they can be very touchy....
		</talk>
		<actfight act="A.E.A. Assembly" monsters="anguil:anguil">
			<begin>As you are approaching, some Eeloz notice your Dinoz and attack!</begin>
			<win>After defeating the Eeloz, you notice some steep tracks heading towards the west....</win>
		</actfight>
		<goto v="chutes" hide="1"/>
		<talk v="Fisherman">
			This is a good place to fish. Fish come here to see the levitating monks ... A guy named Moulder?
			I know him well: He went to Piranhoz Bay to go fishing. Take care man, those guys bite.
		</talk>
		<actfight act="Piranhoz Bay" monsters="pira:pira:pira:pira:pira:pira">
			<begin>
				After entering the bay, many Piranhoz rush to bite you. Who would want to fish here???</begin>
			<win>Once you've defeated the Piranhoz, you take a look around. If Moulder was fishing here, he's certainly not here anymore.</win>
		</actfight>
		<talk v="Fisherman">
			Moulder? He left, he told me he was going back to wait for his wife at the Swamp. Poor guy, he hasn't seen her in years. If I were him I'd be happy about that! Ha Ha!
		</talk>
		<goto v="marais"/>
		<action v="Sign">
			A sign seems to have been placed near a bed of waterlilies. The sign reads:
			"I'm sick of these mosquitos, meet me where I declared my love for you. Moulder x."
		</action>
		<end>
			Oh! My dear Moulder! I feel closer to you than ever!
		</end>
		<xp v="20"/>
		<gold v="1000"/>
	</m>

	<m group="skull" id="skul3" name="Miss Bao" cond="mission(skul2)">
		<begin>
			Oh no! I've just realised something that could be a problem. Even if I find Moulder, he'll forget meeting me
			again and will go somewhere else to wait for me. You must find a solution before
			I see Moulder. Go and see Miss Bao, she should have a solution!
		</begin>
		<goto v="baobob"/>
		<talk v="Miss Bao???" gfx="baobob">
			What??? Miss Bao?? No ... don't you know who I am? .......... If you're looking for my sister,
			she's with the grandson of the ArchDorogon: "The Venerable" as he likes to be called
			nowadays. If his father finds out that he likes to be called that, there'll be trouble.
		</talk>
		<goto v="vener"/>
		<talk v="Miss Bao" gfx="baobabe">
			What??? Miss Bao?? It's been years since anybody has called me that.
			Please call me by my first name young man, Babe.
		</talk>
		<talk v="Bao Babe" gfx="baobabe">
			If you want my advice, I'm afraid you're going to have to wait for a while. I need to finish my game of Draughts with the ArchDorogon's grandson.
			His grandfather made me promise to visit his grandson from time to time to keep him company. Why don't you go and hunt some goblins whilst you wait?
		</talk>
		<kill v="goblin" n="10" name="Hunt Goblins"/>
		<talk v="Bao Babe" gfx="baobabe">
			Finished! I beat him hands down. Hi hi hi! I love to make him lose his temper, he's so
			cute when his nostrils flare and start to blow vapour! You said you needed some advice?
		</talk>
		<talk v="Bao Babe" gfx="baobabe">
			Right. The solution to this kind of problem is really simple: Moulder must keep a piece of Skully with
			him at all times so that he never forgets her. See you later young man!
		</talk>
		<end>
			Oh! Here's a nice solution for my problem! Here, take this, now you'll never forget
			the way to the cemetary, nor your dear Skully!
		</end>
		<xp v="10"/>
		<gold v="500"/>
		<fx v="skull"/>
	</m>

	<m group="skull" id="skul4" name="The Annoying Tourists" cond="mission(skul3)">
		<begin>
			"Meet me where I declared my love for you" Oh oh oh oh! My dear Moulder has
			a heart of gold! I'll never forget the place where he
			took us, while we were still young. Nor the moment
			he gave me a well grilled merguez and asked me if I would marry him!
		</begin>
		<goto v="rashpk" hide="1"/>
		<talk v="Merguez Seller" gfx="merguez">
			A strange customer? Yeah, there was a thin-looking guy who was here a while ago,
			he was letting out a lot of sighs. I remember he was on his way to the ruins.
			Be careful! There are some strange tourists around.
		</talk>
		<actfight act="Visit the Ruins" monsters="baraba:bamboo">
			<begin m="baraba">
				May the Bambooz power be with me! Come on!
			</begin>
			<win>Before collapsing, Barababor whispers the following words: "We've captured your friend: he will be taken to our native steppes by boat, where he will be sold into slavery!"</win>
		</actfight>
		<goto v="port"/>
		<action v="Search for the strange boat">
			After searching for a while, you finally find a strange-looking boat that matches your description.
		</action>
		<actfight act="Board the Boat" bg="dome" monsters="baratr:bamboo">
			<begin m="baratr">
				May the Bambooz power be with me! I will avenge my brother!!!
			</begin>
			<win>After defeating the bandits, you free a hostage who was tied-up in the boat....</win>
		</actfight>
		<talk v="Freed Man">
			Thhh Thhaannkksss!! I hahahave hahad fefefear you know! Moulder?? Nono, my nananame is Jean-Claude.
			I am a friefriend of the mermerguez seller! Ththanks anayway fofor your help!
		</talk>
		<goto v="rashpk" hide="1"/>
		<talk v="Merguez Seller" gfx="merguez">
			You saved Jean-Claude? Ah!! Thanks a lot. Those steppes bandits ruined the Ruins' tourist industry
			I don't know how to thank you! Moulder? He promised to come back if I prepared him some Napalm shrimps, but I don't know the recipe.
		</talk>
		<end>I can feel Moulder coming closer, thanks a lot for your help my young friend!</end>
		<xp v="40"/>
		<gold v="2000"/>
	</m>

	<m group="skull" id="skul5" name="Napalm Shrimp" cond="mission(skul4)">
		<begin>
			"Napalm Shrimp"? Oh! That brings back sweet memories, what a delicious dish!
			You'll have to bring me specific ingredients so that I can properly prepare it.
		</begin>
		<talk v="Skully" gfx="skully">
			Well, first of all, I need some shrimp. You can find some
			at the Underwater Dome Market! Go quickly!
		</talk>
		<goto v="dome"/>
		<talk v="Shrimp Merchant">
			I'm sorry but following recent fraudulent transactions, I no longer accept gold coins as
			payment for my shrimp. You'll have to bring me 3 Treasury Notes....
		</talk>
		<use v="tix" n="3"/>
		<talk v="Shrimp Merchant">
			Thanks, here are your shrimp! Bon appetit!
		</talk>
		<goto v="skull"/>
		<talk v="Skully" gfx="skully">
			Oh oh oh! Ma-gni-fi-cient! These shrimp are so fresh! Now that we've got some shrimp, we need to gather the next ingredient.
			Some Napalm. To make it, we need some good quality lava.
		</talk>
		<goto v="fosslv"/>
		<talk v="Soft Shaman" gfx="shaman">
			Some Napalm? Mmmm ... you'll need to make a mixture of half-lava, half-flamelets.
			We have loads of lava here, so all you need to get are 5 boxes of Flamelets in order to prepare the mixture.
		</talk>
		<use v="flamch" n="5"/>
		<talk v="Soft Shaman" gfx="shaman">
			Glou glou! Here you are, some low density Napalm is ready and waiting for you.
		</talk>
		<goto v="skull"/>
		<talk v="Skully" gfx="skully">
			Oh! Superb Napalm! But the recipe can't be completed without adding
			a vitally important ingredient. Some fatty Korgon's hair! You can often find some
			near the Big All-Hot, but make sure you don't end up stealing someone's dinner or else you'll live to regret it!
		</talk>
		<goto v="vener" title="Search for a Korgon"/>
		<actfight act="Search for a Korgon" monsters="korgon">
			<begin m="korgon">Kwwiiiiiiik !</begin>
			<win>You've captured a fatty Korgon. Let's hope it wasn't someone else's dinner!</win>
		</actfight>
		<goto v="skull"/>
		<talk v="Skully" gfx="skully">
			Stir stir! Here we are! A magnificient dish of Napalm Shrimp!
		</talk>
		<end>
			Thanks for your help! I can't wait to see my dear Moulder again!
		</end>
		<xp v="30"/>
		<gold v="5000"/>
	</m>

	<m group="skull" id="skuend" name="The Reunion" cond="mission(skul5)">
		<begin>
			Your mission has reached it's conclusion. Take the Napalm Shrimp to my dear Moulder.
			He will recognise my cooking and will come back to me immediately! Oh oh oh! I can't wait for him to return!
		</begin>
		<goto v="rashpk"/>
		<talk v="Merguez Seller" gfx="merguez">
			Ooooohh!! So these are the famous Napalm Shrimp?!? Let's see ... mmmm ... it's missing a bit of fat but
			it's still incredibly succulent. Without a doubt Moulder sill arrive soon. Ahhhh! Look who's coming!
		</talk>
		<lock/>
		<end>
			Ooooooooooooooohhh! He's back, he's back! My dear Moulder is back!!! Thank you so much for all your help young man!!
		</end>
		<xp v="10"/>
	</m>

</missions>