<!-- ***************************************************************************** -->
<!--
set de mission de l’ermite, uniquement dispo si le dinoz a atteint le niveau 60 :
-apporter de la mousse de la forêt pour soulager le dos de l’ermite
-un ingrédient commun de chaque zone
-attendre 2h sans fermer la fenêtre web (pour les gros naifs)
-combattre un monstre de niveau 60
-?
-->

<missions>

	<m group="rhubar" id="rhub1" name="ET Foam home?" cond="level(30)">
		<begin>My bones ache, they creak, altogether quite unpleasant really. Could you go and get some moss from the hills in the Grumhel Forest.
		If you could also pick me up some ice from the Deep Gorges that'd be great... I don't mean to inconvenience you!</begin>
		<goto v="collin"/>
		<action v="collect some moss">
			You've collected some moss from the dark trees.
		</action>
		<goto v="gorges"/>
		<action v="extract some ice">You find a pick on the fground and start hacking away at the ice.</action>
		<actfight act="fight the adult dwarf Archlion" monsters="arcadu">
			<begin m="arcadu">
				The noise spreads everywhere, amplified by the caverns in the grotto. The echo attracts the attention of an old acquaintance.
			</begin>
			<win>
				The Archlion has learned its lesson, you can continue to extract the ice in peace.
			</win>
		</actfight>
		<end>
			Aaaah, I feel so much better now, it's a shame the moss dries out and becomes useless so quickly.
			Thankyou, finally my joints get some rest...
			You may go and choose your reward from the treasure room behind me.
		</end>
		<item v="tix" n="20"/>
		<ingr v="art1" n="1"/>
		<ingr v="art2"n="1"/>
	</m>
	
	<m group="rhubar" id="rhub2" name="A little drop of ether?" cond="mission(rhub1)+level(40)">
		<begin>My ectoplasmiic energy is weakening by the century now, I can't convey any wisdom any more...
		As you have travelled beyond the Steppes, could you bring me back some ether, that substance lets me recharge my batteries.</begin>
		<goto v="cextra"/>
		<action v="Utiliser l'extracteur">You begin extracting some ether.</action>
		<actfight act="fight the Serpether" monsters="serpe">
			<begin m="serpe">
				The extraction has awakened an old friend... however, you absolutely must get rid of him if you ever want to get back to the extraction.
			</begin>
			<win>
				The extraction process is complete, all that remains is to return to Rhubabao'riley...
			</win>
		</actfight>
		<end>That should allow me to keep going for a while longer. Thank you kindly. You may select your reward from the treasure room.</end>
		<item v="tix" n="30"/>
		<ingr v="art3" n="1"/>
	</m>
	
	<m group="rhubar" id="rhub3" name="Lodestone Shard" cond="mission(rhub2)+collec(magnet)+level(50)">
		<begin>The ether you brought me runs out so quickly, I'll need a lodestone shard to fossilize it.
		I have the feeling that you have one, but it won't be charged enough to do the job. Could you recharge it and bring it here?</begin>
		<goto v="spylon"/>
		<action v="place the lodestone shard">
			You have placed the shard on an plinth which is constantly struck by lightning.
			All we have to do now is wait...
		</action>
		<actfight act="fight the Behemotin" monsters="behemu">
			<begin m="behemu">
				You thought as much, it never rains but it pours! It was written that you'd have to face the 3rd Colossus again...
			</begin>
			<win>
				Hopefully it'll leave you alone from now on.
			</win>
		</actfight>
		<goto v="temple"/>
		<action v="Fossilize the ether">Upon approaching the ether shard, it retracts and hardens. Mission accomplished!</action>
		<end>
			Thank you. The ether should no longer evaporate thanks to you. I can now concentrate on your initiation.
			You can go and find your reward in the treasure room.
		</end>
		<ingr v="artr1" n="1"/>
		<ingr v="artr2" n="1"/>
	</m>
	
	<m group="rhubar" id="rhub4" name="Out here in the fields..." cond="mission(rhub3)+level(50)">
		<begin>Now my comfort has been assured... it is time for you to prove to me that you have indeed explored Dinoland in its entirety.
		bring me an object from each world you have visited, I'll use them to learn more about what has happend in the last centuries.</begin>
		<use v="irma" n="1"></use>
		<use v="tartev" n="1"></use>
		<use v="ration" n="1"></use>
		<use v="mergz" n="1"></use>
		<use v="hlmsos" n="1"></use>
		<use v="monoch" n="1"></use>
		<use v="danger" n="1"></use>
		<use v="odemon" n="1"></use>
		<use v="cendre" n="1"></use>
		<use v="riz" n="1"></use>
		<end>You have provided me with many objects. I am now able to reward you with an object which I have guarded closely for many centuries.</end>
		<ingr v="dgrain" n="1"/>
	</m>
	
	<m group="rhubar" id="rhub5" name="Meditation" cond="mission(rhub4)+level(50)">
		<begin>it is time to prepare for the ritual. You must now stand still for 10 hours...
		You must not close your web browser, nor must you close it, otherwise you muste start again.</begin>
		<goto v="temple"/>
		<action wait="10" v="begin meditating">You begin your meditation... STOP MOVING!</action>
		<end>Well done, you have achieved inner peace... Did you really not close your browser? You really didn't have to! Hahahaha!</end>
		<xp v="80"/>
	</m>
	
	<m group="rhubar" id="rhuba" name="Spiritual Combat" cond="mission(rhub5)+level(50)">
		<begin>Now you have had the time to meditate, you will soon have completed your preparation.
		The ultimate test is all that remains, I will use my power to create a projection of my body from years past.</begin>
		<goto v="temple"/>
		<actfight act="fight the Spirit of Rhubabao'riley" monsters="rhubar">
			<begin m="rhubar">
				Prepare yourself for my assaults. Do you have the strength?
			</begin>
			<win>
				Well done. You have defeated me. You are worthy of receiving my ultimate reward.
			</win>
		</actfight>
		<end>Congratulations, your initiation is complete.</end>
		<item v="tix" n="50"/>
	</m>
	
</missions>
