<buildings>
	<!-- NEXT : 1080 -->

	<!-- *** ATELIER *** -->
	<b key="command" name="Workshop" icon="small_refine">
		The advancement of a town depends on the construction of a shabby workshop full of nondescript clutter. It allows resources to be converted and is a pre-requisite for the construction of other more advanced buildings.
	</b>
	
	<b key="butcher" name="Butcher" icon="item_meat">
		Here you can transform your little companions (dogs, cats, snakes...) into rations. Just think...some crazy people prefer beef!
	</b>

	<b key="crema" name="Cremato-Cue" icon="item_hmeat">
		OK, do we all know what a crematorium is? Do we all also know what a barbecue is? Well then, it's easy to guess what purpose a Cremato-Cue serves. In any case, it means we don't die of starvation...well, some of us!
	</b>

	<b key="defOptim" name="Defensive Focus" icon="item_meca_parts">
		Establishes an ingenious system for optimising the use of defensive materials (steel plate, etc.). This system increases the points value of each defensive object placed in the bank.
	</b>

	<b key="factory" name="Factory" icon="small_factory">
		This upgraded version of the workshop reduces the cost of all conversions carried out in the workshop by 1 AP.
	</b>
	
	<b key="turret" name="Cannon Mounds" icon="small_dig">
		Multiple mounds of earth, reinforced with wooden beams. These are a pre-requisite for constructing powerful defence turrets... 
	</b>

	<b key="rockCanon" name="Rock Cannon" icon="small_canon">
		An automatic turret which launches rocks towards the town gates at high velocity! It is activated at midnight and fires continuously for several minutes (if you were counting on sleeping in silence, you're going to be disappointed)!
	</b>
	
	<b key="crusher" name="Plate Gun" icon="small_canon">
		The Plate Gun fires heavy shards of steel plate straight towards the battlefield. It is butchery the likes of which you hope to never see again, but it is undeniably effective...
	</b>
	
	<b key="brutalCanon" name="Brutal Cannon" icon="small_canon">
		A machine to die for, literally. It needs to be reloaded every day.
	</b>

	<b key="railgun" name="Railgun" icon="small_canon">
		A powerful piece of equipment which uses compressed air to fire balls of bent nails and other rusty metal. Perfect for making holes the size of a fist in whatever (or whomever) you like...
	</b>

	<b key="woodTurret" name="War Mill" icon="item_wood_beam">
		Large wooden beams fixed to a rotating axle. It spins, really quickly.
	</b>

	<b key="hanger" mod="FRAGILE_HANGER" name="Gallows" icon="r_dhang">
		A cracking gallows for hanging undesirable types when you'd rather go a little further than just banishing them from the community... Please note: given the poor standard of construction, the gallows can only be used ONCE, for ONE hanging: they must be rebuilt before they can be used again.
	</b>
	
	<b key="hanger_solid" mod="SOLID_HANGER" name="Gallows" icon="r_dhang">
		A cracking gallows for hanging undesirable types when you'd rather go a little further than just banishing them from the community... True craftsmanship is what your're looking at here - this gallows isn't going anywhere.
	</b>
	
	<b key="eastercross" mod="FRAGILE_HANGER" name="Choco Cross" icon="small_eastercross">
		A cross made entirely from chocolate which is ideal for dealing with undesirable types when you'd rather go a little further than just banishing them from the community... Please note: given the poor standard of construction, the cross can only be used ONCE and must be rebuilt before it can be used again.
	</b>
	
	<b key="eastercross" mod="SOLID_HANGER" name="Choco Cross" icon="small_eastercross">
		A cracking made entirely of chocolate which is ideal for dealing with undesirable types when you'd rather go a little further than just banishing them from the community...
	</b>
	
	<b key="buildingRegistry" name="Building Registry" icon="item_rp_book2">
		With a little organisation and a solid table, it is possible to keep a detailed account of what is going on in the construction sites.
	</b>
	
	<b key="architectoire" name="Architect's Study" icon="small_refine">
		When intelligent citizens meet in the evenings around the fire, great things are invented. Well, on the condition that they've built an Architecture Study. This building gives the town a (common) construction blueprint every day.
	</b>
	
	<b key="grazor" name="Screaming Saws" icon="small_saw">
		Massive circular saws built outside which are activated by a clever system involving elastic bands and a cardboard tube... The noise made by the saws rotating is reminiscent of human screams...
	</b>

	<b key="abattoir" name="Abbatoir" icon="small_slaughterhouse">
		An abattoir installed just in front of the town gates, and the entrance is facing the World Beyond. The problem generally lies in finding a volunteer every night to stand in it, waving their arms to entice the zombies in.
	</b>

	<b key="support" name="Defensive Thinktank" icon="item_shield">
		A major re-structuring of our defences to get the very best out of them (total town defences are increased by +10%).
	</b>
	
	<b key="woodCafet" name="Small Café" icon="small_cafet">
		When it's a long time until meal time... There's nothing like a solid plank of wood and some stale bread.
	</b>
	
	<b key="lockedGrave" name="Small Cemetary" icon="small_cemetery">
		Bring out your dead! For once, they're going to be useful. Use them to summarily improve our defences. Each dead citizen brought to the cemetary gives +10 defence points to the town. Note: How and where the victim died makes no nevermind...
	</b>
	
	<b key="springCoffin" name="Coffin Catapult" icon="small_coffin">
		Between two corpses, the one that's moving has the best chance of eating you, trick the enemy by catapulting your corpses into the carnivorous crowd of shuffling scum! Each body earns +20 defence points instead of +10.
	</b>
	
	<b key="centralCafet" name="Central Cafeteria" icon="small_cafet">
		The canteen increases the production of "kitchens" built by your town's Heroes.
	</b>
	
	<b key="centralLab" name="Central Laboratory" icon="item_acid">
		The laboratory increases the production of "personal laboratories" built by your town's Heroes.
	</b>
	
	<b key="henhouse" name="Henhouse" icon="small_chicken">
		If you forgot some time ago what a fried mushroom omelette with bacon and herbs tastes like, this building will be of no use to you. Well, on the plus side you'll get some eggs. If you have your heart set on mushrooms, you'd best go and talk to the zombies...
	</b>

	<b key="infirmary" name="Infirmery" icon="small_infirmary">
		In the event of minor accidents or major trauma, the infirmery will welcome you with open arms. Well, on the condition that you're able to carry out any procedures yourself, as the facility doesn't come with medical personnel.
	</b>
	
	<b key="citizen" name="Builders' Merchant" icon="small_strategy">
		This major building provides the means to build more advanced houses.
	</b>
	
	<b key="roundSection" name="Community Involvement" icon="small_strategy">
		The goal of this ambitious urban project is to better incorporate the defences of citizens' homes into the town's defences. With this construction, 80% of personal defences will count towards the town's total, instead of the usual 40%.
	</b>
	
	<!-- *** TOUR DE GUET *** --->
		
	<b key="tower" name="Watchtower" icon="item_tagger">
		This tower, situated near the gates, gives an estimation of the magnitude of the forthcoming attack, allowing the citizens to be better prepared. It also unlocks all construction projects linked to emergency situations.
	</b>
	
	<b key="betterMap" name="Upgraded Map" icon="item_electro">
		This simple electronic gadget increases the level of detail visible on the map of the World Beyond: the exact number of zombies in each zone can be clearly seen. Invaluable if you don't want to wander mindlessly into feeding time at the zombie zoo... 
	</b>

	<b key="catapult" name="Catapult" icon="item_courroie">
		The catapult is a special machine which allows you fire all kinds of things into the World Beyond: very useful for preparing the ground for faraway expeditions!
	</b>

	<b key="catapult2" name="Upgraded Catapult" icon="item_courroie">
		This upgrade improves the catapult by reducing the number of action points needed to launch items into the World Beyond.
	</b>
	
	<b key="tempDefBase" name="Emergency Supplies" icon="status_terror">
		To prepare for any eventuality, it is sometimes necessary to build emergency defences which are not destined to last more than one attack. The Emergency Supplies system fulfils this need. Be sure not to waste resources hastily building temporary structures all over the camp!
	</b>
	
	<b key="urgentDefs2" name="Spikes" icon="small_trap">
		Installing spiked poles around the town gives some extra defences at minimal cost, but they might just make the difference some nights...
	</b>
	
	<b key="bomb" name="Bomb Factory" icon="small_tnt">
		Dynamite, zombies, blood.
	</b>
	
	<b key="guerilla" name="Guerilla Traps" icon="small_trap">
		Setting a variety traps all over the place is a great way to take out large numbers of attacking zombies.
	</b>
	
	<b key="trap" name="Pits" icon="small_trap">
		 This trap won't kill the zombies, but it will stop them in their tracks!
	</b>
	
	<b key="urgentDefs1" name="Wood Plating" icon="item_wood_plate">
		In case of emergency, it is often possible to make it through one more night by patching up the town walls with wood plating.
	</b>
	
	<b key="panic" name="Abject Panic" icon="status_terror">
		If the situation gets really desperate, you can decide to scream and panic. The advantage of this is that if all the survivors do it, this will disorientate the zombies (who really don't need that kind of stress) and earns you sime virtual defence points... Yeah, it's a load of nonsense.
	</b>
	
	<b key="bamba" name="Frat House" icon="small_bamba">
		Partying is the best way to forget what's going on outside, thankfully the zombies are there to ensure that it doesn't get out of hand.
	</b>

	<b key="dump" name="Rubbish Heap" icon="small_dig">
		When the proverbial hits the fan, and there's nothing else for it, just pile up everything that comes to hand, and pray that it slows the zombie horde down... The good thing is that you can build some really effective traps into it!
	</b>

	<b key="dumpTrap" name="Mount Killaman-Jaro" icon="small_dig">
		Once you have built a huge pile of rubbish, it is easy to cover it in skewers that are as rusty as they are deadly!
	</b>
	
	<b key="scanner" name="Scanner" icon="item_tagger">
		This homemade scanner, if used correctly, makes it twice as easy to obtain an estimation of the magnitude of the forthcoming attack (only requires half as many citizens to use it to obtain a solid estimate)! It is essential if the town is to be run efficiently.
	</b>

	<b key="nextDay" name="Predictor" icon="item_tagger">
		The predictor is a calculator of sorts, which estimates the magnitude of and works out details relating to the attack. In particular, it gives an estimation of TOMORROW'S attack!
	</b>

	<b key="regen" name="Searchtower" icon="small_gather">
		Each day, the search tower allows objects to be found in zones which were previously deemed "depleted". It detects unusual meteorological phenomena occurring outside and notes which area has been affected in the Chronicle.
	</b>
	
	<b key="watchmen" name="Guard Tower" icon="small_watchmen">
		Building a big, beautiful tower and walkway really makes Hero guardians happy. This construction gives +10 defence points per Guardian in town and allows them to earn even more defence points by exchanging them for AP.
	</b>
	
	<b key="roundPath" name="Battlements" icon="small_round_path">
		Are you sick of standing in the dust drenched in zombie guts? Tired of tripping over the severed limbs of the zeds you took out? Maybe it's time to rise above the apocalypse and survey the hordes from on high! The costruction of the Battlements will allow you to stand watch over the town at night, while getting a little closer to heaven.
	</b>
	
	<b key="scouts" name="Crows' Nest" icon="small_watchmen">
		Not so much a tower as a really really long pole of which scouts can climb to the top to discover a building in the World Beyond (Once per day, per Hero).
	</b>

	<!-- *** DÉFENSES *** -->
	<b key="wall1" name="Wall Upgrade v1" icon="small_wallimprove">
		Significantly increases the town's defences.
	</b>

	<b key="barbed" name="Barbed Wire" icon="small_barbed">
		It's even a little more basic than you might imagine - we've run out of wire...
	</b>
	
	<b key="meat" name="Bait" icon="small_meatbarbed">
		A lump of meat attached to a hook should distract at least a few zombies...
	</b>
	
	<b key="barrer" name="Wooden Fencing" icon="small_fence">
		Wooden fences surrounding the town should (in theory)... slow down the zombie hordes significantly during the attack...
	</b>
	
	<b key="dig" name="Great Pit" icon="small_gather">
		The Great Pit is a very effective defensive measure: a big hole surrounding the town. Also known as "the Brad", it is very practical in the long term, as it can be filled with all sorts of things to make it even more effective!
	</b>

	<b key="waterHole" name="Great Moat" icon="small_waterhole">
		Another upgrade for the Great Pit: fill it with water...
	</b>

	<b key="spears" name="Spiked Pit" icon="small_spears">
		One way to improve the Great Pit: fill it with sharpened wooden spikes, commonly known as "Brad the Impaler".
	</b>

	<b key="razor" name="Grater" icon="item_plate">
		Simple concept: sharp pieces of rusty metal fixed all along the tops of the town's walls to make a kind of zombie grater.
	</b>
	
	<b key="holes" name="Old-school traps" icon="small_gather">
		Lots of holes surrounding the town which have been covered with branches. Now you just need to wait for something to fall into them...
	</b>
	
	<b key="fence" name="Small Fence" icon="small_fence">
		Significantly increases the town's defences.
	</b>

	<b key="wallAdv" name="Wall Upgrade v2" icon="small_wallimprove">
		It may be too much for tonight's defences, but building a better wall allows for the addition of numerous upgrades 
	</b>
	
	<b key="megaWall" name="Überwall" icon="item_plate">
		What is better than a wall? ... A big wall.
	</b>

	<b key="wallSpears" name="Spiked Wall" icon="item_plate">
		A load of metal spikes on the ramparts can make for some zombie kebabs around nightfall...
	</b>
	
	<b key="wallEvo" name="Evolutive Wall" icon="item_home_def" hasLevels="1">
		By adding an iron frame to the walls, it'll be easy to improve them each day, and without much effort!
	</b>
	
	<b key="poutres" name="Metal Patches" icon="item_plate">
		Metallic supports to reinforce the weaker parts of the wall.
	</b>

	<b key="second" name="Inner Wall" icon="item_plate">
		A wall within the existing wall provides an additional layer of protection against the nocturnal hordes...
	</b>

	<b key="third" name="Third Wall" icon="item_plate">
		A third wall within the existing walls provides an additional layer of protection against the nocturnal hordes...
	</b>

	<b key="concrete" name="Concrete Reinforcement" icon="small_wallimprove">
		A concrete wall within the existing walls provides an additional layer of protection against the nocturnal hordes...
	</b>

	<b key="groundRazor" name="Zombie Grater" icon="small_grater">
		Cover a large area of the ground in shards of sharpened metal and you get the world's largest cheese grater.
	</b>

	<b key="soapWall" name="Slip 'n' Slide" icon="small_wallimprove">
		Why did nobody think of this before? Instead of wasting your time on personal hygiene, use your soap to make the town walls slippy. Combined with the zombie grater, it's ideal, except for the "noise".
	</b>

	<b key="waterSpray" name="Vaporiser" icon="small_waterspray">
		A small hydraulic device designed to spray water vapour (and amusing chemicals too).
	</b>

	<b key="acidSpray" name="Acid Spray" icon="small_acidspray">
		This certainly isn't going to improve the looks of the zombies at the gates.
	</b>
	
	<b key="gazSpray" name="Gas Gun" icon="small_gazspray">
		Many choose to forget this, but zombies have brains of their own. Sometimes two, if they're lucky. This is handy: the concentrate projected by this gun has an astonishing capacity for turning brains to sludge.
	</b>
	
	<b key="def1" name="Armour Plating" icon="item_plate">
		A basic defensive device, but nonetheless one which you'll be happy to have when your ex-neighbour Kevo tries to snack on your delicious frontal lobe this evening.
	</b>
	
	<b key="def2" name="Armour Plating v2" icon="item_plate">
		It's not particularly advanced, but it does the job: makes you less likely to die.
	</b>

	<b key="def3" name="Armour Plating v3" icon="item_plate">
		Basic, but thick. Can't ask for much more really.
	</b>

	<b key="def4" name="Plywood" icon="item_plate">
		Plywood. You only picked up the thing because you had nothing better to do. You know it's useless, but you did it anyway. Let's go...
	</b>
	
	<b key="def5" name="Extrawall" icon="item_plate">
		It certainly wasn't a genius who came up with this construction project, but in the end everyone agreed that another big wall is never a bad thing.
	</b>
	
	<!-- *** EAU *** -->
	<b key="pump" name="Pump" icon="small_water" >
		The pump unlocks all the construction projects involving water. It also increases the well's underground reserves considerably.
	</b>

	<b key="breakthrough" name="Water Catcher" icon="item_tube">
		When it comes to water, every drop counts. This construction adds +2 rations to the well and can be rebuilt every day.
	</b>
	
	<b key="aquaTurret" name="Water Turrets" icon="item_tube">
		This revolutionary defensive device fires powerful jets of water vapor into the ranks of zombies approaching our walls. With some additional adjustments, this will be an exceptionally powerful defence!
	</b>

	<b key="rainCanon" name="Mist Spray" icon="small_watercanon">
		A nice fine mist to water the beds of zombies growing near the gates
	</b>
	
	<b key="wellBoost" name="Drilling Rig" icon="small_water">
		A home made drilling rig which allows the well to be extended deeper into the ground, therefore significantly increasing available reserves...
	</b>
	
	<b key="eden" name="Eden Project" icon="small_eden">
		This is the last resort when there is no more water: rupture the water table with dynamite to extend the town's reserves.
	</b>
	
	<b key="hydro" name="Water Purifier" icon="item_jerrycan">
		Converts water from Jerrycans found in the desert into drinkable water. (regular)
	</b>

	<b key="filter" name="Water Filter" icon="item_jerrycan">
		Significantly increases the output of the purifier (high performance).
	</b>
	
	<b key="mines" name="Mines" icon="item_bgrenade">
		Rocket powder, detonators and clean water are all you need to make a big pile of putrefied flesh pulp. A powerful defence, but it can only be used once.
	</b>

	<b key="garden" name="Vegetable Plot" icon="item_vegetable_tasty">
		The vegetable plot can be used to grow vegetables that aren't overly mouldy and fruit that starts to rot before it gets ripe. In short, basic rations, if we're not being too fussy...
	</b>

	<b key="grapefruit" name="Grapeboom" icon="item_bgrenade">
		This is a major scientific breakthrough: by planting sticks of dynamite and watering them carefully, you can grow grenades!
	</b>

	<b key="fertilizer" name="Fertilizer" icon="item_digger">
		Significantly increases the yield of the vegetable plot.
	</b>
	
	<b key="appletree" name="Apple Tree" icon="small_appletree">
		An apple tree which looks more like a half-dead scrawny shrub but produces beautiful blue apples. Euh, hang on.. What?
	</b>
	
	<b key="waterNetwork" name="Hydraulic Network" icon="item_firework_tube">
		Thanks to this network of pipes, you can build powerful water-based defences. Furthermore, this system adds a little extra water to the well.
	</b>
	
	<b key="autoWater" name="Automatic Sprinkler" icon="small_sprinkler">
		Traditionally used in a garden, they also serve as a deadly defence against the Hordes... They kill lots of zombies, but just be sure to store plenty of water beforehand.
	</b>
	
	<b key="press" name="Saniflow Macerator" icon="small_grinder">
		Two huge slabs around the entrance way and a powerful piston system: when they are activated, they instantly crush anything in the way!
	</b>
	
	<b key="vapo" name="Boiling Fog" icon="small_waterspray">
		This machine takes a negligible amount of clean water, and sprays it out as fine boiling vapour. Originally used to clean the town's streets, it is nonetheless ideal for melting your decomposing cohorts who come to visit every night.
	</b>

	<b key="showers" name="Shower" icon="small_shower">
		No, really, I'm being serious now, that... that... smell is properly unbearable. Take a shower. Now.
	</b>
	
	<b key="gutters" name="Sluice" icon="small_shower">
		The town's waste water can still be used: all you need to do is to connect every citizen's toilet to a cunning network of pipes and toboggans, and open the sluices at midnight. Just to check, everyone has their tent set up correctly, right?
	</b>

	<b key="waterfall" name="Decon Shower" icon="small_shower">
		At the start, this was supposed to be a decontamination system. Upon use, however, it was seen to be an effective weapon against our pestilential friends. By adding a squirt of coconut shower gel, you can even perfume the rotting corpses you're responsible for.
	</b>

	<b key="waterDetector" name="Divining Rods" icon="small_waterdetect">
		For once, cutting-edge technology does something other than knock off vast quantities of zombies... This construction adds +100 water rations to the well.
	</b>
	
	<b key="deepRocket" name="Divining Rocket" icon="small_rocketperf">
		A home-made rocket launcher fired into the ground: think about it! As the story goes, the inventor of this construction project was trying to invent the "rocket-jump". All he did was to re-invent "the crater". Nonetheless, this construction adds +60 water rations to the well.
	</b>

	<!-- *** PROJETS INSENSÉS *** -->

	<b key="fondations" name="Foundations" icon="small_building">
		Foundations allow "Extreme Projects" to be completed (projects which take a long time to complete, but which have very powerful results).
	</b>

	<b key="move" name="The Big Rebuild" icon="small_moving">
		This Extreme Project seeks to improve the town's defences by restructuring the entire town. Lock down the houses, block the roads, install turrets on all the roofs... That's the Big Rebuild!
	</b>

	<b key="scarecrow" name="Scarecrows" icon="small_scarecrow">
		This field of scarecrows would work even better with citizens' clothing, but that would require turning your town into a nudist colony.
	</b>
	
	<b key="meatCage" name="Meat Locker" icon="small_fleshcage">
		Popular justice in all its glory! When a citizen is shunned they can be sent to the cage, which is judiciously located in plain sight, in front of the gates to the town. Their wailing and crying makes a great lure at midnight. Each shunned citizen sent to the cage earns temporary defence points for the town.
	</b>
	
	<b key="publicDump" name="Garbage Dump" icon="small_trash">
		The cornerstone of every great town: a huge stinking dump all around the town. Admittedly, it's not very aesthetically pleasing, but it allows you to convert everyday objects into effective temporary defences (for one night only).
	</b>
	
	<b key="freeDump" name="Free Dump" icon="small_trashclean">
		Reduces the cost of using the dump to 0 AP. Make sure not to build this if you still have some potential scoundrels in town...
	</b>
	
	<b key="humidDump" name="Dump Upgrade" icon="small_trash">
		Increases the yield of any object thrown in the dump by +1 temporary defence point.
	</b>
	
	<b key="armouredDump" name="Defence Dump" icon="small_trash">
		Increases the yield of any defensive objects thrown in the dump.
	</b>
	
	<b key="weaponDump" name="Weapons Dump" icon="small_trash">
		Allows the destruction of weapons at the dump.
	</b>
	
	<b key="foodDump" name="Food Dump" icon="small_trash">
		Allows the destruction of food at the dump.
	</b>
	
	<b key="woodDump" name="Wood Dump" icon="small_trash">
		Allows the destruction of wood at the dump.
	</b>
	
	<b key="metalDump" name="Metal Dump" icon="small_trash">
		Allows the destruction of metal at the dump.
	</b>
	
	<b key="animalDump" name="Animal Dump" icon="small_howlingbait">
		Allows the massacre of innocent animals at the dump.
	</b>
	
	<b key="headlight" name="Lighthouse" icon="small_lighthouse">
		This beautiful big lighthouse will illuminate those long winter nights (is it any good in the summer?). All citizens will see their chances of surviving a camping trip improve.
	</b>
	
	<b key="fortified" name="Fortifications" icon="small_city_up">
		On the rare occasion a construction project benefits citizens directly, we won't complain. All citizens' houses will gain +4 defence points.
	</b>
	
	<b key="joyFire" name="Bonfire" icon="small_score">
		A large bonfire, set on the outskirts of the town to lead the zombies away from our flimsy houses.
	</b>
	
	<b key="popCourt" name="People's Court" icon="small_court">
		It's a well known fact that Heroes are always correct. Furthermore, to further cement this truth, any complaints registered against other citizens will count twice.
	</b>
	
	<b key="slaveryOffice" name="Ministry of Slavery" icon="small_slave">
		The Ministry for Slavers have stated that shunned citizens are allowed to work on construction projects. Furthermore, each AP they invest will contribute an additional 50% bonus to the construction site (eg: 6 AP invested by a shunned citizen, 9 AP are invested in the project).
	</b>
	
	<b key="megaPump" name="Mechanical Pump" icon="small_derrick">
		An extreme project which allows large quantities of water to be extracted from the deepest groundwater! This project adds +50 water rations to the well.
	</b>
	
	<b key="betterPump" name="No Holes Barred" icon="small_derrick">
		Because the drilling rig obviously cannot break though all rocks, it is sometimes necessary to send small animals strapped with dynamite down the holes. This project adds +150 water rations to the well.
	</b>
	
	<b key="fakeCity" name="False Town" icon="small_falsecity">
		It's a well known fact that zombies are a bit simple. If you construct a false second town, some of the attacking horde will try to attack it...
	</b>
	
	<b key="robinet" name="Faucet" icon="small_valve">
		Thanks to this small tap fixed to the well, any water wasted by the filtration system can be recovered (doesn't require any additional water to be taken from the well). You can use this water to refill all water-based weapons (bombs, pistol, etc...) for FREE !
	</b>

	<b key="cinema" name="Cinema" icon="small_cinema">
		They're showing Dawn of the Dead for the 636th time, you almost certainly missed the role played by one of the extras the last time you saw it, so watching it one more time won't hurt.
		With a little luck, it migth even make you laugh.
	</b>
	
	<b key="balooning" name="Hot Air Balloon" icon="small_balloon">
		A large, round balloon floating in the sky, but just for as long as it takes for a "volunteer" citizen to take a note of everything he sees around the town. This building allows you to reveal everything hidden in the World Beyond.
	</b>
	
	<b key="maze" name="Labyrinth" icon="small_labyrinth">
		It's a well known fact that zombies are a bit simple. So what better than a maze in front of the gates to lose a few of the horde during the attack? It's really effective, but from now on, any citizen wishing to enter the town will need 1 AP to do so.
	</b>
	
	<b key="lastchance" name="All or Nothing" icon="small_lastchance">
		Welcome to the last chance saloon! All objects in the bank will be destroyed and each one will provide 1 defence point.
	</b>
		
	<b key="rockets" name="Air Strike" icon="small_rocket">
		Four magnificent rockets are launched at key targets around the town (north, south, east and west), killing all zombies found nearby in the World Beyond!
	</b>
	
	<b key="fireworks" name="Firework Foray" icon="small_fireworks">
		There's nothing quite like a solid firework display to pass the long nights in the desert. This miniature version basically involves pointing the firing tubes at the areas surrounding the town and launching fireworks into the horde at midnight..
	</b>

	<b key="altar" name="Altar" icon="small_redemption">
		Just because the Crow is good and just, this shrine in its honour liberates all citizens that have been shunned from the town.
	</b>
	
	<!-- *** MERVEILLES *** -->
		
	<b key="wonder_pmv" name="Giant BRD" icon="small_pmvbig">
		An frighteningly BRD on which the names of all the town residents are engraved. Pointing majestically towards the sky like... euh... A BRD. Nobody knows why, but someone has engraved, "Propriété de la Nuit Profonde" on the base. This wonder shines by the light of its uselessness alone: its construction earns a rare distinction for all the citizens still in town.
	</b>

	<b key="wonder_crow" name="Crow Statue" icon="small_crow">
		Glory to the Crow! Glory be to their lenience and benevolence! Deliver us from spam and pardon our trolling as we forgive those who have trolled against us. This wonder shines by the light of its uselessness alone: its construction earns a rare distinction for all the citizens still in town.
	</b>
	
	<b key="wonder_wheel" name="Wonder Wheel" icon="small_wheel">
		It is indeed a vast and beautiful creation, you've also sunk the best part of our resources into the damn thing, but for some reason you're proud of it. This wonder shines by the light of its uselessness alone: its construction earns a rare distinction for all the citizens still in town.
	</b>
	
	<b key="wonder_castle" name="Giant Sandcastle" icon="small_castle">
		If there's one thing we're not short of here, it's sand. This wonder shines by the light of its uselessness alone: its construction earns a rare distinction for all the citizens still in town.
	</b>
	
	<!-- *** PORTE *** -->

	<b key="doorLock" name="Portal Lock" icon="small_door_closed">
		A somewhat old-fashioned device which stops the gates being opened during the 20 minutes immediately before the attack. The gates still have to be closed manually.
	</b>

	<b key="doorPlate" name="Reinforced Gates" icon="item_plate">
		Heavy steel plate fixed to the town gates to add extra zombie-proofing!
	</b>
		
	<b key="bigDoor" name="Automatic Piston Lock" icon="small_door_closed">
		This system uses powerful motorised pistons to automatically close the gates and prevent them from opening again half an hour before the attack.
	</b>

	<b key="autoDoor" name="Last-minute Lock" icon="small_door_closed">
		The gates close automatically at 22h59 instead of 22h30.
	</b>
	
	<b key="airing" name="Ventilation System" icon="small_ventilation">
		This secret passage allows Heroes to enter and leave the town without using the gates!
	</b>
	
	<b key="reactor" name="Reactor" icon="small_arma">
		This terrifying building came from a soviet submarine and sends powerful bolts of electricity arcing around the town with a deafening crackle. The only "hitch" is that it has to be repaired daily. If it is destroyed, the town and its surroundings are instantly vaporized, wiping everything off the map (where you'll be). The label reads: soviet design, assembled in « вшивый ».
	</b>
	
	<b key="spa4souls" name="Hammam" icon="small_spa4souls" mod="SHAMAN_SOULS">
		A place of relaxation and contemplation perfectly suited for the transition of lost souls to the other side.
	</b>
	
	<!-- *** VEILLEURS *** -->

	<b key="tourello" name="Shooting Gallery" icon="small_tourello" mod="GUARDIAN">
		A fairground shooting alley, not the most mobile of affairs, it always goes down a storm on the ramparts, guaranteed to put a smile on a watchman's face. It gives a +20% bonus to all water weapons used in a night's watch
	</b>
	
	<b key="catapult3" name="Small Trebuchet" icon="small_catapult3" mod="GUARDIAN">
		This beast-launcher lets you catapult your animal companions a considerable distance so that they can cause even more distress to the attacking horde. Furthermore, the noises made by wingless animals flying at speed is highly entertaining, which will help your fellow watchmen to relax a little.
	</b>
	
	<b key="armor" name="Miniature Armory" icon="small_armor" mod="GUARDIAN">
		This armory is a genuine top trump for watchmen. By building it, every weapon used during the night's watcjh will have its effectiveness boosted by 20%!
	</b>
	
	<b key="ikea" name="Swedish Workshop" icon="small_ikea" mod="GUARDIAN">
		This small store allows all furniture being used on the night's watch to become 20% more effective. Ah the Swedes... DIY masters of the universe!
	</b>

</buildings>

