<help>

<h id="intro" title="Die2Nite?">
	<p><strong>Die2Nite is a game of survival set in a hostile world inhabited by the living dead.</strong></p>

	<p>
		The players (or citizens) are divided into groups and are allocated a small town where they must organise themselves each day in such a way as to survive as long as possible against these beings. <strong>The last remaining survivor will become the Hero of the town</strong>.
	</p>

	<h2>Objective n°1: Explore and equip</h2>
	<img src="/gfx/screen/intro_equip.gif" alt="" class="art"/>
	<p>
		During the day, citizens can leave the relative safety of the town to explore the desolate wastelands of the<strong> World Beyond</strong> to find weapons, materials and food.
	</p>

	<h2>Objective n°2: Defend against the hordes</h2>
	<img src="/gfx/screen/intro_fight.gif" alt="" class="art artRight"/>
	<p>
		Every day at 23h00 (server time), the hordes of living-dead attack the town! Objects found during the day can be used to build defences and protect your home.
	</p>

	<h2>Objective n°3: Help one another and survive...</h2>
	<img src="/gfx/screen/intro_help.gif" alt="" class="art"/>
	<p>
		Objects and materials found by the citizens can be shared. Maybe your neighbour found the screw you need to fix your chainsaw? Your survival depends on your ability to organise yourself and make the most of the community's resources...
	</p>

	<h2>What should I be doing each day?</h2>
	<p>
		There are several tasks to carry out each day in Die2Nite.
	</p>
	<ul>
	<li><strong>Read the newspaper</strong>: It will give you a rundown of yesterday's events!</li>
	<li><strong>Collect your water ration from the well</strong>: You can't live without it.</li>
	<li><strong>Explore the World Beyond</strong>: Go scavenging in the desert and bring back any useful objects.</li>
	<li><strong>Participate in construction projects</strong>: Join in discussions and cast your vote on construction projects and building upgrades.</li>
	<li><strong>Get active on the town forum</strong>: organise yourselves and survive.</li>
	</ul>
</h>


<h id="outer" title="The World Beyond">
	<img src="/gfx/screen/outer.gif" alt="" class="art"/>
	<p>
	<strong>The World beyond is the desert which surrounds the town and stretches as far as the eye can see. Paradoxically, it is a place which is dangerous but at the same time essential for survival.</strong>
	</p>

	<p>
		If the humans shut themselves away in their town, they will soon be overrun by zombie hordes and perish. They must gather items to improve their daily life and defend themselves. It is essential to go outside the town to find these objects and materials.
	</p>

	<h2>How to get to the World Beyond?</h2>
	<p>
		To visit the World Beyond, go to the <strong>Town Gates</strong> section... open the gates and proceed with extreme caution! Remember the following 3 rules:
	</p>
	<ul>
	<li>Take <strong>food</strong> or <strong>water</strong> with you.</li>
	<li>Always ensure you are back inside the gates <strong>before 23h00 (server time)</strong> (or you will be devoured by the Hordes...)</li>
	<li>Close the town gates before 23h00 (server time), or the zombies will rush into the town and wreak havoc on the citizens...</li>
	</ul>
</h>


<h id="move" title="Getting around" icon="small_move" sub="1">
	<h2>Action Points and Exhaustion</h2>
	<p>
	You can move around the World Beyond for as long as you have  <strong><img src="/gfx/loc/::LANG::/small_pa.gif" alt=""/> Action Points</strong> remaining: each movement costs 1 action point. When you reach 0 points, you will become <img src="/gfx/icons/status_tired.gif" alt=""/> <strong>exhausted</strong> and will no longer be able to move.
	</p>
	<img src="/gfx/loc/::LANG::/moves.gif" alt="" class="art"/>
	<p>Your action points are shown at the top of the page, near the Help button. You can <strong>alleviate exhaustion</strong> and <strong>recover your action points</strong> in several ways:
	</p>
	<div class="clear"></div>
	<ul>
		<li><img src="/gfx/icons/item_water.gif" alt=""/> drinking water (Once per day)</li>
		<li><img src="/gfx/icons/item_undef.gif" alt=""/> eating (Once per day)</li>
		<li><img src="/gfx/icons/item_drug.gif" alt=""/> taking drugs (Unlimited, but beware: It's very easy to get hooked!)</li>
	</ul>

	<div class="clear"></div>
	<p>
	There are other more unusual (and sometimes dangerous!) methods but you'll have to discover them for yourself...
	</p>

	<h2>Run out of action points?</h2>
	<p>
	Pray that a citizen passes by and leaves you a little something to get you going again... If you're in doubt, call for help on the forum (the link is at the top left of the page)
	</p>
	[mod follow] 
	<p>
	If you can't stay connected while you wait for another player to pass by, try using the <a href="/#help?id=escort">Escort Mode </a> button!
	</p>
	[/mod]
	<p class="ambiant">
		The time for the Horde to attack is nigh... You have cried in vain on the intercom: nobody has come to save you... Your short life starts to flash before your eyes... Who knows, maybe tomorrow you'll wake up craving human flesh...
	</p>
</h>


<h id="map" title="Map" icon="item_map" sub="1">
	<div class="noJustify">
		<h2>Local view</h2>
		<img src="/gfx/loc/::LANG::/map.gif" alt="" class="art"/>
		<p>
			<strong>Once you pass through the town gates, this map becomes your only means of navigation in the World Beyond.</strong>
		</p>
		<p>
		Click on the arrows <strong>[1]</strong>, to move in your chosen direction.
		</p>
		<p>
			The Map button <strong>[2]</strong> allows you to see the area surrounding the town, and what has been discovered.
		</p>

		<h2>World Map</h2>
		<img src="/gfx/loc/::LANG::/map2.gif" alt="" class="art"/>
		<p>
			The bright green square <strong>[1]</strong> indicates your position
		</p>
		<p>
			Zones coloured orange, red or blue <strong>[2]</strong> indicate the presence of zombies. Be extremely careful if you venture into these sectors alone!
		</p>
		<p>
			The Tags button <strong>[3]</strong> allows you to view the markers which have been placed on the map by other players (or yourself). This allows players to highlight dangerous zones, or zones containing important objects etc.
		</p>
		<p>
			The Global button <strong>[4]</strong> allows you to see as much of the world as has been explored by <strong>the citizens of the town</strong>(and not just what you have discovered on your expeditions).
		</p>
		<p>
			Finally, the Expeditions button <strong>[5]</strong> allows you to display any expeditions planned by any citizen.
		</p>
		<div class="clear"></div>
		<h2>Types of zone</h2>
		<ul>
			<li>
				<img src="/gfx/screen/map_unknown.gif" alt=""/>
				An unknown sector, you have never set foot here personally. In Global mode, these sectors have never been visited by anyone.
			</li>
			<li>
				<img src="/gfx/screen/map_nvt.gif" alt=""/>
				A sector which has been visited over the last few days, but not today. <strong>what you don't know though, is if there are still any zombies there...</strong>
			</li>
			<li>
				<img src="/gfx/screen/map_town.gif" alt=""/>
				The Town: if you want to stay alive, you have to make it back here or find another solution.
			</li>
			<li>
				<img src="/gfx/screen/map_building.gif" alt=""/>
				This square indicates the presence of a building or a ruin to explore. Buildings generally contain the best objects!
			</li>
		</ul>
	</div>
</h>


<h id="explore" title="Exploring and Scavenging" icon="small_gather" sub="1">
	<h2>Searching a zone</h2>
	<p>
		It is possible to start scavenging in any given zone. Scavenging allows you to discover objects which can either be used where you are or be taken back to the town. <strong>You can only search each zone once per day.</strong>
	</p>

	<h2>Auto-Search</h2>
	<p>
		As soon as you have searched a zone, you immediately activate <strong>Auto-Search</strong> mode. From that point, if you stay in that zone, you will automatically search the zone<strong> every 2 hours</strong>.
	You don't need to keep your browser on the page, you can simply come back later and see what you have found.
	</p>
	<p>
	Warning! If you <strong>leave the zone</strong>, your automatic search will be interrupted and cannot be resumed in that zone for the remainder of the day...<em>You can always start again in a more distant zone...</em>
	</p>

	<div class="clear"></div>

	<h2>Outside buildings</h2>
	<p>
		When travelling through the World Beyond, you will discover buried buildings. These must be excavated before they can be explored.
		These ruins are overflowing with special, rare and sometimes dangerous objects. Perhaps they could save the citizens from certain death?
	</p>
</h>


<h id="depleted" title="Depleted zones" icon="small_broken" sub="1">
	<p>
		Once a desert zone has been searched several times, it can become "depleted" which means that no more useful objects can be found there. At best, poor quality materials (wood and metal) will be found.
	</p>
	<p>
		<strong>However, for several weeks now, we have observed strange meteorological phenomena occuring during the night in the World Beyond...</strong>
	</p>
	<h2>Meteorological Anomalies</h2>
	<p>
		Violent sandstorms rage in the World Beyond around 23h00 (server time). No rational explanation for these phenomena has been found at this time.
	</p>
	<p>
		<strong>The good news is that in affected regions, these storms can uncover new objects even in zones which were previously considered depleted.</strong>
	</p>
	<p>
		To find these zones, you will need to build a <strong>Search Tower</strong> (construction site). Furthermore, upgrading the Search Tower improves the chances that affected zones will regenerate.
	</p>
</h>

<h id="dom" title="Control Points" icon="small_dom_equal" sub="1">
	<img src="/gfx/loc/::LANG::/dom.gif" alt="" class="art"/>
	<p>
		Control points let you know if a zone is dangerous or not. They are displayed just below the map and work as follows:

	</p>
<div class="clear"></div>
	<ul>
		<li>Each <img src="/gfx/icons/small_human.gif" alt=""/> <strong>citizen</strong> present in the zone counts for <strong>::UserControl:: points</strong>.</li>
		<li>Each <img src="/gfx/icons/small_zombie.gif" alt=""/> <strong>zombie</strong> present in the zone counts for <strong>1 point</strong>.
			<ul>
				<li>Certain advantages from this profession, from experiences or from objects permit the increase or reduction of the control points of a human being.</li>
			</ul>
		</li>
	</ul>
	<div class="clear"></div>
	<p class="help">
	<strong>If the zombies have more control points than the citizens, the zone is dangerous and you will be trapped!</strong>
	</p>

	<h2>What is a "dangerous" zone?</h2>
	<p>
		A zone is dangerous when you are outnumbered by zombies and you can't leave. It goes without saying that at 23h00 (server time), it's going to be zombie party time...
	</p>
	<h2>Flight</h2>
	<img src="/gfx/art/feist.gif" alt="" class="art"/>
	<p>
		When you are trapped, there are several solutions:
	</p>
	<ul>
		<li>
	You can flee, forcing your way past the zombies, but you risk a <a href="/#help?id=status"><strong><img src="/gfx/icons/status_wound.gif" alt=""/> serious wound</strong></a>
	</li>
	<li>Take on the zombies in hand to hand combat and try to kill them one at a time... However, each attempt costs 1<img src="/gfx/loc/::LANG::/small_pa.gif" alt=""/> and has a minimal chance of success.</li>
	<li>use weapons to eliminate zombies and restore order to the zone... if you have any! (See the rules for control points above).</li>
	<li>
		call for help on the forum, asking another player to come to your location and add "human points" to the zone. Control will hopefully then be regained by the humans, allowing you precious time to escape.
	</li>
	<li>there are other ways of escaping a zone when you're trapped by zombies, but it's up to you to figure them out.</li>
	</ul>
	<div class="clear"></div>

	<h2>Loss of control (Countdown timer)</h2>
	<img src="/gfx/loc/::LANG::/domTimer.gif" alt="" class="art"/>
	<p>
		If the zone is controlled by humans (their score is higher than that of the zombies) and control is subsequently lost (for example by a player leaving the zone), all the remaining players will be <strong>trapped after 30 minutes</strong>.
	</p>
	<p>
		If this happens, you will have 30 minutes (and not a second more) to:
	</p>
<ul>
<li>flee!</li>
<li>regain control of the zone.</li>
</ul>

</h>

<h id="escort" title="Escort Mode" icon="small_move" sub="1" mod="FOLLOW">

	<p>
		When you are in the World Beyond, <strong>you can activate "escort mode" at any time, by clicking the "wait for an escort" button at the bottom right of the user interface.</strong>
	</p>
	<p>
		In escort mode, a <strong>Hero citizen</strong> will be able to partially take control of your character. This means they will be able to:
	</p>
	<ul>
	<li>make you move around the map, using your action points.</li>
	<li>make you search a zone.</li>
	<li>make you drink a ration of water from your rucksack.</li>
	<li>make you eat an item from your rucksack.</li>
	<li>make you enter the town (if you are at the gates).</li>
	[mod follow_full]
	<li>make you pick up or drop an object, but only if you have authorised this action (by checking the box),</li>
	[/mod]
	<li>leave you to rot:(</li>
	</ul>


	<h2>Rescues in the World Beyond</h2>
	<p>
		If you only wish to be helped, and not marched around the World Beyond, you can select this option after having activated escort mode. Simply select: "Take me home, country roads...". (this option is activated by default)
	</p>
	<p>
		<strong>This option restricts the escort from taking you on a grand tour, instead, he can only lead you towards the town..</strong>
	</p>

</h>

<h id="fight" title="Fighting the Hordes in the World Beyond" icon="item_cutcut" sub="1">

	<h2>How do you kill a zombie?</h2>
	<img src="gfx/art/pip/hero.gif" alt="" class="pip"/>
	<p>
		Techniques vary from one citizen to the next. Everyone agrees that <strong>fresh water</strong> is a great weapon for destroying them. To be effective, however, it must be used to fill plastic bags thus making <img src="/gfx/icons/item_grenade.gif" alt=""/> Water Bombs.
	</p>
	<h2>Alternatives</h2>
	<p>
		If you feel so inclined, you could also try:
	</p>
	<ul>
		<li><img src="/gfx/icons/item_staff.gif" alt=""/> a big wooden stick... it's not great, admittedly</li>
		<li><img src="/gfx/icons/item_watergun_empty.gif" alt=""/> a water pistol! Job done!</li>
		<li><img src="/gfx/icons/item_pet_dog.gif" alt=""/> a well-trained pet </li>
		<li><img src="/gfx/icons/item_chainsaw.gif" alt=""/> other fun toys...</li>
	</ul>

	<p>
		If you're in too deep, and there's no other option,<a href="/#help?id=dom">flee</a>...
	</p>

</h>


<h id="night" title="La nuit" icon="r_doutsd" sub="1" mod="NIGHTMODS">
	<img src="/gfx/art/night.png" alt="" class="art"/>
	<p>
		The nights are cold in the world of Die2Nite. Really cold and rarely a good omen of what is to come. Certain rules and actions change during these hours of solitude...
	</p>
	<div class="clear"></div>
	<p>The following changes come into effect during the night:</p>
	<ul>
		<li>the special ability <i>Break free</i> has an increased chance of success,</li>
		<li>campers have a better chance of finding a hiding place,</li>
		<li>scouts have an even smaller chance of being discovered: the night is your ally,</li>
		<li>citizens can attempt to steal objects from the bank: there is a chance they won't be identified in the register, <sup>1</sup></li>
		<li>Searches are less likely to be successful (buildings included). <sup>1</sup></li>
	</ul>

	<em>
		<sup>1</sup>: These rules only apply in maps marked "Distant Lands".
	</em>

</h>


<h id="camp" title="Extreme camping" icon="small_camp" sub="1" mod="CAMP">
	<img src="/gfx/art/nightCamping.png" alt="" class="art"/>
	<p>
		<strong>Extreme camping is the risky, but potentially rewarding strategy of hiding in the World Beyond during the attack at 23h00 (server time).</strong>
	</p>
	<p>
		The way it works is simple: find yourself a decent hiding place in the desert, perform 3 hail marys and 2 hello dollys and wait for the attack to be over...
	</p>
	<div class="clear"></div>
	<p>
		This strategy offers several advantages:
	</p>
	<ul>
		<li>
			<strong>survive outside if the town gates have been closed</strong>: it happens!
			Make sure to explain to your little friends exactly how much you enjoyed their joke, if you survive...
		</li>
		<li>
			<strong>lead an extended expedition</strong>: you can make a 2 day expedition to the furthest corners of the map, maybe even longer!
		</li>
		<li>
			<strong>receive a scavenging bonus</strong>: if you are in the World Beyond during the nightly storms,
			you will receive a bonus which improves your scavenging success rate the following day (increases the chances of finding something). 
			Extreme camping allows you to make the most of your situation to observe the winds and study the movement of the dunes and to discover interesting zones to explore.
		</li>
		<li>
			<strong>distinction</strong>: It's not just anyone who can survive a night in the World Beyond!
		</li>
		<li>
			<strong>another rare distinction</strong>: for each night you manage to survive after the town has been destroyed, you will receive another rare distinction (see the following chapter: <i>"Distinction: Zen Camper"</i>).
		</li>
	</ul>

	<h2>How do I go camping?</h2>
	<p>
		<strong>You cannot camp in a <i>Small town</i>!</strong><br />
		Clicking the link <strong>"Inspect the area"</strong> will give the following options:
	</p>
	<ul>
		<li>
			<strong>improve the site</strong>: you rearrange debris and dead branches, and look for a hole to hide in. Anything to even <i>slightly</i> improve your chances of survival should you eventually choose to spend the night here. <strong>These improvements benefit all citizens in that zone, and remain for days to come. However, the standard of the improvements will decrease every night at 23h00 (server time) (damage caused by the zombie attack). </strong>
		</li>
		<li>
			<strong>hide</strong>: you settle down for the night. You will not be able to carry out any tasks unless you leave your hiding place.
		</li>
		<li>
			<strong>search for a tomb</strong>: You dig yourself in as best you can, using whatever you can find lying around to conceal your presence.
			Finding a tomb affords a better bonus than improving the site. If you select this, you will immediately go into hiding. You will lose this bonus if you leave your hiding place.
		</li>
		<li>
			<strong>using defensive objects</strong>: certain objects permit you to significantly improve your chosen campsite. Using these objects requires 1 <img src="/gfx/loc/::LANG::/small_pa.gif" alt=""/>.
		</li>
		<li>there are other ways of increasing your chances of survial while camping related to professions, objects and areas. It's up to you to figure them out.</li>
	</ul>
	<p>
		<strong>It is impossible to camp at the town gates</strong>. This is the area in which all the zombies arrive at 23h00 (server time): by definition this is the worst choice possible!
	</p>
	<p class="critical">
		The increased likelihood of survival brought about by carrying out all possible improvements to the site (objects, minor improvements and searching for a tomb) are capped. After a certain point, you will not be able to further increase your chances of survival.
	</p>

	<h2>Be honest with me Doc, what are my chances?</h2>
	<p>
		Your chancs of survival are calculated <strong>as soon as you click "<i>hide</i>" or "<i>search for a tomb</i>"</strong>. If the situation in the zone subsequently improves or deteriorates, your chances of survival will not be affected. For example: 
		<p><em>
			You decide to hide in a zone which is controlled by 6 zombies (you will receive a penalty which will reduce your chances of survival).
			A citizen arrives after you and kills all the zombies. Your chances of survival will not be improved. Basically, you must choose your hiding place as the situation currently stands (surrounded by zombies). To take advantage of an improved situation, you must leave your hiding place and hide again.
		</em></p>
	</p>

	<p>
		Your chances of survival depend on several factors:
	</p>
	<ul>
		<li>the presence of zombies in the area (penalty, reduced if you are a scout or camouflaged),</li>
		<li>presence of other citizens already hiding there <strong>before you</strong> (penalty); one citizen is less likely to be discovered than 5...</li>
		<li>presence of an accessible building (bonus or penalty depending on the type of building),</li>
		<li>presence of an <strong>unexcavated</strong> building (bonus),</li>
		<li><strong>devastated</strong> town (significant penalty),</li>
		<li>distance from the town: the further you are from the town when the attack begins, the better!</li>
		<li>special equipment (bonus),</li>
		[mod nightmods]<li>time of day: it is better to hide at night than in daylight,</li>[/mod]
		[mod hardcore]<li>Hardcore: it is very difficult to camp in a Hardcore town,</li>[/mod]
		<li>the number of nights you have spent in the World Beyond during this game (your first time is safe, the second less so, and the third less again, etc...</li>
	</ul>
	<div class="critical">
		<strong>WARNING</strong>: your chances of survival are capped at 90%! no matter what you do, there will always be a chance (however minimal) of dying in the World Beyond.
		[mod job_hunter]
		<p>
			Please note that the <strong>Survivalist</strong> character is particularly adept at camping:
			<strong>their chances of survival are not capped at 90%.</strong>
		</p>
		[/mod]
	</div>
	<h2>How do events unfold at 23h00 (server time)?</h2>
	<p>
		At 23h00 (server time) you must be in your hiding place! According to your survival chances (as explained above), you will survive or be eaten alive.
	</p>
	<p>
		If you survive, <strong>you will regain your <img src="/gfx/loc/::LANG::/small_pa.gif" alt=""/> and be awarded various rewards.</strong>
	</p>
	<p>
		At 23h00 (server time), the zombies are particularly violent: any improvements you have made to your campsite will be less effective the following day.
	</p>
	<p>
		<strong>Warning: </strong> if you make it through a night in the desert, you will no longer be hidden. You will need to 'hide' <strong>again</strong> if you wish to spend another night outside...
	</p>
	<p>
		If the town is abandoned (if all the citizens have left it in favour of camping in the desert), the town will be considered <a href="/#help?id=devast">devastated</a>	
	</p>

	<h2>Distinction: "Zen Camper"</h2>
	<p>
		For each night survived after the town has been <a href="/#help?id=devast">devastated</a>,
		campers will receive a <strong>special rare distinction</strong>.
	</p>
	<p>
		In any case, the town must have survived for <strong>a minimum of ::LastCampsRewardDay:: complete days</strong> for this distinction to be awarded.
	</p>

</h>

<h id="explo" title="Ruin exploration" icon="small_exploration" sub="1" mod="EXPLORATION">
	<img src="/gfx/screen/explo1.gif" alt="" class="art"/>
	<p>
		<strong>Advanced explorations allow citizens to visit forgotten ruins in the World Beyond to search them for resources and plans to help you survive for as long as possible.</strong>
	</p>
	<p>
		Once you have found a special building, you will be given the choice of entering the building or not, <strong>but remember - a wounded or terrified citizen cannot enter such claustrophobic areas.</strong>
		These places are swarming with zombies, you'll need to find a way to get rid of these creatures to make the most of your discovery.
	</p>
	<br/>
	<p>
		<em>When you are exploring, you will only find resources in rooms, only resources dropped by other players will be found on the ground in the corridors.
		Sometimes you will come across locked doors which will require a certain key to open them, but you'll notice the former residents quite often abandoned their keys in their haste to get out, all you need to do is find the right ones.</em>
	</p>
	<img src="/gfx/screen/explo2.gif" alt="" class="art artRight"/>
	<p>
		As you know, nothing is ever simple here, the air filling these buildings which have been abandoned for so long is saturated with a toxic substance which stops you from staying in the building for too long.
	</p>
	<p>
		<strong>An oxygen meter lets you keep an eye on how much time you have remaining to search the building before you die horrifically from ingesting the toxic air.</strong>
		it is imperative that you get out of the winding corridors before time runs out or you will be seriously wounded and you will lose any and all objects you found on your trip.
		There is only one entrance to these buildings, which also means it's your only way out Einstein.
		Don't get greedy and take unnecessary risks by venturing too far inside these labyrinths...
	</p>
	<p><strong>Here are the rules you'll need to live by when in zombie territory if you ever want to see your cherished shack again:</strong>
		<ul>
			<li>Due to the cramped nature of these buildings, <strong>only one citizen can enter a building at a given time.</strong> Once a citizen has left, another may take their place.</li>
			<li>Due to the high levels of exposure to toxic substances during explorations, <strong>a citizen will only be able to enter a building once per day</strong>, subsequent exposure could lead to an agonizing death.</li>
			<li>To escape the zombies populating these areas, aside from using offensive objects, bad breath and colourful language, <strong>you can choose to "Flee"</strong> which allows you to escape but uses up some of your oxygen. However, if you retrace your steps, you will come across the same number of zombies as before.</li>
			<li>The noise made by adventurers in the World Beyond means that <strong>some zombies enter the building every day.</strong> The best idea is to search the zone thoroughly as quickly as possible, before the area becomes infested.</li>
			<li>Nobody can come to help you in these nightmarish places, which means that control points have no meaning here, so you should be as organized as possible to get the most benefit from these buildings.</li>
			<li>Watch the clock - if you find yourself inside a building at 23h00 (server time), you have as much chance of surviving as a <img src="gfx/icons/item_meat.gif" alt=""/> juicy steak in the town square!</li>
		</ul>
	</p>
	<p>
		<em>As these buildings have a direct link to the origin of the zombie outbreak, it's normal that they haven't already been stripped of resources by every passer-by. They still contain loads of valuable resources and construction blueprints.
		Unfortunately, maps of these buildings have been impossible to find, but there is no doubt that the most basic approaches will be the ones adopted to search the zone as efficiently as possible.</em>
	</p>
	
	<div class="clear"></div>
</h>

<h id="soul" title="Lost Souls" icon="item_soul_blue" sub="1" mod="SHAMAN_SOULS">
	<p>
		<strong>The souls <img src="/gfx/icons/item_soul_blue.gif" alt="" /> of your freshly departed colleagues now haunt the vast, devastated lands of the World Beyond.</strong>
		Each time a citizen does not survive the attack of the horde, their soul will appear in the desert.
		<img src="/gfx/screen/screen_ame.gif" alt="" class="art"/>
	</p>
	<p>The burden of recovering the lost souls falls on the town. If the souls are left to wander the desert, they risk becoming tortured souls! <img src="/gfx/icons/item_soul_red.gif" alt="" /> If that happens, everybody should pannick! Tortured souls attract and enrage zombies!</p>
	<p>
		<strong>Please note that it is possible for the Shaman to see souls anywhere on the map, but he connot distinguish tortured souls from lost souls</strong></p>
		
	<p>Recovering lost souls requires preparation. Any citizen can carry a lost soul, but a tortured soul requires extra protection. Their violence can be insidious...</p>
	
	<p>The shaman is impervious and can touch any soul without risk (but not without fear). A normal citizen will need the help of a shaman in order to touch a tortured soul. The shaman must prepare a potion which will allow the citizen to handle a tortured soul safely. But be careful how much trust you place in your shaman...</p>
	
	<p>Once you have brought a soul back to town you need to purify it. This requires that you have completed the correct construction site. <strong>Remember that a tortured soul is just as dangerous in town as in the desert until it has been cleansed.</strong></p>
</h>


<h id="player" title="About You">
	<p>
		Throughout the course of your life in Die2Nite, you will accumulate items found in the desert, construct buildings, contract illnesses, take drugs...
	</p>
	<p>
		<strong>You must always keep a close eye on your situation in order to make the best decisions.</strong>
	</p>

</h>

<h id="status" title="Health" icon="status_tired" sub="1">
	<img src="gfx/loc/::LANG::/status.gif" alt="" class="art"/>
	<p>
		To survive in a world like this, it is essential to <strong>keep a close watch on your health</strong>. Several health indicators can be seen at the top of the page.
	</p>
	<p>
		You will quickly get used to looking here to check if you need to drink, heal yourself, etc...
	</p>
	<div class="clear"></div>

	<dl>
		<dt>
			<img src="/gfx/icons/status_tired.gif" alt=""/> <strong>Exhaustion</strong>:
		</dt>
		<dd>
			When you run out of <img src="/gfx/loc/::LANG::/small_pa.gif" alt=""/> action points, you become exhausted and will no longer be able to move around (see <a href="/#help?id=move">Getting around</a>).
		</dd>

		<dt>
			<img src="/gfx/icons/status_thirst.gif" alt=""/> <strong>Thirst</strong>:
		</dt>
		<dd>
			You need to drink... Don't wait too long, or you risk getting
			<strong><img src="/gfx/icons/status_dehyd.gif" alt=""/> Dehydrated</strong>!
		</dd>

		<dt>
			<img src="/gfx/icons/status_hasDrunk.gif" alt=""/> or <img src="/gfx/icons/status_hasEaten.gif" alt=""/> <strong> = Satisfied</strong>:
		</dt>
		<dd>
			These states indicate that you have drank and/or eaten today. Repetition of these actions will not restore action points.
			<em>
				Example: you drank a flask of water in the morning to restore your action points and to alleviate your THIRST. If you drink again today, you can once again get rid of THIRST, but your action points will not be restored.
			</em>
		</dd>

		<dt>
			<img src="/gfx/icons/status_wound.gif" alt=""/> <strong>Wounded</strong>:
		</dt>
		<dd>
			You have been seriously wounded... Heal yourself quickly with bandages or other medication or you risk getting an <strong><img src="/gfx/icons/status_infect.gif" alt=""/> Infection</strong>, which is usually deadly.
		</dd>
		
		<dt>
			<img src="/gfx/icons/status_infect.gif" alt=""/> <strong>Infection</strong>:
		</dt>
		<dd>
			This is due to a wound, or eating something that was a little too far out of date. Heal yourself quickly, an infection comes with a 50% mortality rate, 75% in Pandemonium Cities.
		</dd>

		<dt>
			<img src="/gfx/icons/status_drugged.gif" alt=""/> <strong>Drugged</strong>:
		</dt>
		<dd>
			Drugs are powerful in Die2Nite and have many uses: relieving exhaustion, curing infections, calming nerves, rehydration... Be careful not to take too many though. The risk of becoming <strong><img src="/gfx/icons/status_addict.gif" alt=""/> Addicted</strong>. Addiction is real and extremely dangerous.
		</dd>

		<dt>
			<img src="/gfx/icons/status_terror.gif" alt=""/> <strong>Terrorised</strong>:
		</dt>
		<dd>
			23h00 (server time) has arrived. The enraged hordes are beating down on your house, but you manage to keep them at bay. Nonetheless, the memory of such a close brush with death has left you <strong>terrorised</strong>. When in the grasp of <strong>terror</strong>, your actions will be heavily limited... In any event it is out of the question to be close to zombies! If you do end up in a zone with zombies, you will be paralysed with fear... until they devour you. In the desert, you will have 0 control points, regardless of your job or what equipment you are carrying. You will not be able to do anything in any zone controlled by zombies (where the zombies have more control points than the humans).
			<p>
				There are other ways to end up terrorised, but you'll have to experience them yourself.
			</p>
		</dd>

		<dt>
			<img src="/gfx/icons/status_drunk.gif" alt=""/> <strong>Drunk</strong>:
		</dt>
		<dd>
			Alcohol lets you recover from extreme tiredness, but it is possible that you will act somewhat strangely... The following day, the effects of being <img src="/gfx/icons/status_drunk.gif" alt=""/>&nbsp;<strong>Drunk</strong> will wear off, and be replaced by a <img src="/gfx/icons/status_hung_over.gif" alt=""/>&nbsp;<strong>Hangover</strong>. You cannot drink any more alcoholic drinks when you are in either of these states.
		</dd>

		<dt>
			<img src="/gfx/icons/status_clean.gif" alt=""/> <strong>Clean</strong>:
		</dt>
		<dd>
			This status indicates you have not taken any drugs up to this point. An impressive display of restraint, when you know the kinds of marvellous hallucinations they allow you to experience...
		</dd>

		<dt>
			<img src="/gfx/icons/item_disinfect.gif" alt=""/> <strong>Innoculated</strong>:
		</dt>
		<dd>
			some medicine or something else you consumed recently has made you immune to infection!
			[mod ghouls]You will not be able to be turned into a ghoul at 23h00 (server time) either.[/mod]
			This effect will wear off just after the attack.
		</dd>

		[mod camp]
		<dt>
			<img src="/gfx/icons/small_camp.gif" alt=""/> <strong>Learned Camper</strong>:
		</dt>
		<dd>
			If you manage to survive a night camping in the World Beyond, you will be awarded 'Learned Camper' status and a searching bonus for the duration of the following day!
		</dd>
		[/mod]


		[mod ghouls]
		<dt>
			<img src="/gfx/icons/small_ghoul.gif" alt=""/> <strong>Ghoul</strong>:
		</dt>
		<dd>
			You have been possessed by an unspeakable evil which has turned you into a <a href="/#help?id=ghoul">ghoul</a>.
		</dd>
		[/mod]


	</dl>

	<h2>Drug Addiction</h2>
	<p>
		When you take too many drugs (more than one per day), you become
		<strong><img src="/gfx/icons/status_addict.gif" alt=""/>Addicted</strong>! It is <strong>impossible to kick this habit</strong>.
	</p>
	<p>
		From this point onwards, you must consume <strong>at least one drug every day before 23h00 (server time)</strong>, or you will die (foaming at the mouth and shaking uncontrolably, it's spectactularly unattractive...).
	</p>

	<h2>Types of wound</h2>
	<p>
		When you are wounded, a specific area of the body is affected!
	</p>
	<ul>
		<li>
			<strong>Head</strong>:
			your ramblings will become incoherent...
		</li>

		<li>
			<strong>Hands</strong>:
			you will no longer be able to use certain objects...
		</li>

		<li>
			<strong>Arm</strong>:
			your wound stops you from working at the town's construction sites and opening/closing the town gates...
		</li>

		<li>
			<strong>Leg</strong>:
			in the World Beyond, whenever you try to move, there is a chance your leg will give way and you'll fall. You will lose your AP but remain in the same zone!
		</li>

		<li>
			<strong>Eye</strong>:
			your chances of finding an object while searching outside the town (in the desert or in a building) are considerably reduced.
		</li>
		<li>
			<strong>Foot</strong>:
			no additional penalty.
		</li>
	</ul>
</h>

<h id="inv" title="Inventory" icon="item_bag" sub="1">
	<h2>Rucksack</h2>
	<img src="/gfx/loc/::LANG::/bag.gif" alt="" class="art"/>
	<p>
		It's thanks to your trusty rucksack that you can carry your food rations, your water or your weapons with you. It is pretty limited though, and fills up quickly... by default it has 4 storage compartments and one compartment reserved for your uniform.
	</p>
	<p>
		If you are in <strong>Hero mode</strong>, you have an additional storage compartment in your rucksack! 
		In addition, you will <strong>also</strong> have to carry your citizen's uniform and your work uniform.
	</p>

	<h2>Your House</h2>
	<img src="/gfx/screen/home.gif" alt="" class="art"/>
	<p>
		When you come back from the World Beyond, your House is where you can unpack your rucksack. It is also where you will fill it before setting off again.
	</p>

	<h2>Your personal chest</h2>
	<img src="gfx/loc/::LANG::/chest.gif" alt="" class="art"/>
	<p>
		Your personal chest can hold 4 objects by default (5 for Heroes). Certain objects and home improvements allow you to increase this limit.
	</p>
	<p>
		Certain objects, like the <strong><img src="/gfx/icons/item_carpet.gif" alt=""/>Carpet</strong> are <strong>automatically</strong> used to make <strong>improvements</strong> to your House if you place them in your chest. Improvements give various bonuses (decoration, protection against theft, defence against zombies...)
	</p>

</h>


<h id="ghost" title="Your Soul" sub="1" icon="small_ghost_blue">
	<p>
		In Die2Nite, existence is futile. Short-lived if you will. You will die often, but death is never that serious!
	</p>
	<p>
		<strong>
		Your soul tells the story of all your incarnations. The memories of all your past lives is stored here, along with your position in the Overall Rankings and Distinctions awarded. 
		</strong>
	</p>


	<h2>Distinctions</h2>
	<img src="/gfx/screen/rewards.jpg" alt="" class="art "/>
	<p>
		Every time you die, you are awarded Distinctions for many things you have done during the game: number of zombies killed, rare objects found, etc...
	</p>
	<p>
		
	Distinctions show what you have achieved during your lives and can be seen on your profile page by other players.
	</p>
	<div class="clear"></div>
	<div class="critical">
		<p>
			<strong>Warning:</strong> if you die, distinctions earned on the last day will not be awarded (a few distinctions are exceptions to this rule, for example: banishment distinctions, distinctions relating to death, etc.)
		</p>
		<p>
			In any event, starting on day::RewardsDailyRuleLimit::, this rule will not apply any more: all distinctions you earn will be awarded.
			
			In the Non-Distant Regions, <strong>as soon as you have 100 soul points</strong>, no distinction is valid before the 8th day.
		</p>
	</div>

	<h2>Titles</h2>
	<p>
		Certain distinctions unlock titles: when you earn a certain number of a given distinction, a <strong>special title</strong> will appear on your page!
	</p>
	<p>
		<em>
			Example: you will receive a "Floored zombie" distinction for each member of ther living-dead that you eliminate. After 100, the title "Mutilator" will appear on your profile! Continue to eliminate zombies and eventually a new title will appear.
		</em>
	</p>
	<p>
		If you want to display a particular title next to your name, go to <strong>Your Soul</strong> and click on the desired title.
	</p>


	<h2>Soul Points (ranking)</h2>
	<p>
		Every day you spend in a town gives you points. The first few days only give a few points, but the longer you survive, the more points you'll earn!
	</p>
	<p>
		These soul points will determine your position in the Overall Rankings.
	</p>
	<p>
		<strong>As soon as a player amasses more than 100 soul points, all future lives will begin in towns inhabited by players who also have over 100 points</strong> (allowing the best players to play together).
	</p>
</h>


<h id="death" title="Death and soul points" sub="1" icon="small_death">
	<h2>Death</h2>
	<p><strong>In Die2Nite, death is never serious.</strong></p>
	<p>It only serves to signal the end of your existence in a given town, and to mark the beginning of another existence in another town.</p>

	<h2>Gaining soul points in case of death</h2>
	<p>
		When you die, you are awarded a certain number of points depending on the <strong>number of complete days survived during your last incarnation</strong>
	</p>
	<div class="critical">
		
	A day is considered "lived in full" <strong>if you survive the night or die from consequences arising from the zombie attack at 23:00</strong>. Death of any other kind will render the day invalid.
	</div>
	<p>
		Here are the possible scenarios:
	</p>
	<ul>
		<li>
			<strong>if you die during the day (from poisoning, dehydration during an expedition, ...): </strong>the day does not count as having been "lived in full". <em>For example, if you die from Cyanide poisoning during your 5th day in town, you will only be awarded points for the 4 full days you survived.</em>
		</li>
		<li>
			<strong>if you die at 23h00 (server time), but from dehydration, an infection or any cause not linked to the zombie assault:</strong> the day is still not considered complete, because you were unable to provide for your basic needs. <em>For example, if you die from dehydration on the night following day 5, you will only be awarded points for the 4 full days you survived.</em>
		</li>
		<li>
			<strong>if you die in the desert at 23h00 (server time):</strong>
			the day does not count as having been "lived in full". (see previous example).
		</li>
		<li>
			<strong>if you die in town during the zombie attack:</strong> your day is complete! <em>For example, if you die during the zombie attack on the night following day 5, you will be awarded points for the full 5 days you survived (the 5th and final day is valid).</em>
		</li>
		[mod camp]
		<li><strong>if you die while camping and your town is not devastated:</strong> your day is <strong>NOT</strong> completed!</li>
		<li><strong>if you die while camping and your town IS devastated:</strong> the day is completed.</li>
		[/mod]
	</ul>
</h>


<h id="lastOne" title="Last Man Standing!" sub="1" icon="r_surlst">
	<p>There is a very special distinction in Die2Nite. One which only goes to the best (or most devious) citizens: <strong>Last Man Standing!</strong></p>
	<p>This offers an undeniable advantage: it transforms the average citizen into a <strong>Hero for one or more days!</strong></p>
	<p>However, to earn this distinction, three rules must be satisfied:</p>
	<ul>
		<li>The town must have survived <strong>for at least 5 complete days</strong>,</li>
		<li>The citizen must have been <strong>devoured during the Horde's attack</strong> which devastated the town,</li>
		<li>The town can not have been <a href="/#help?id=devast">devastated</a> on a previous attack (<i>a town is devastated if a night passes and there are no citizens within the town walls.</i>).</li>
	</ul>
	<p>
		<strong>a citizen who commits suicide, dies from dehydration on the last night or dies in the World Beyond, will not earn this distinction.</strong>
	</p>
	[mod camp]
	<p>
		Similarly, a citizen who is camping in the World Beyond will not be given this distinction.
	</p>
	[/mod]
	<p>
		The last survivor is chosen completely at random. <strong>The last victim will become the Last Man Standing</strong>.
	</p>
	<p>
		Finally, if the citizen selected is already a Hero, the day or days awarded will be added to the number of Hero days the citizen currently has remaining.
	</p>

	<h2>Last Man Standing awards table</h2>
	<ul>
		<li>dead during day 5 (between 0h et 23h59) or before = no award</li>
		<li>dead during the night between day 5 and 6 = 1 hero day + distinction</li>
		<li>dead during the night between day 6 and 7 = 2 hero days + distinction</li>
		<li>dead during the night between day 7 and 8 = 3 hero days + distinction</li>
		<li>dead during the night between day 8 and 9 = 4 hero days + distinction</li>
		<li>dead during the night between day 9 and 10 = 5 hero days + distinction</li>
		<li>dead during the night between day 10 and 15 = 6 hero days + distinction</li>		
		<li>dead during the night between day 15 and 20 = 7 hero days + distinction</li>
		<li>dead during the night between day 20 and 21 or thereafter = 10 hero days + distinction</li>
	</ul>
</h>

<!--
<h id="lastCamp" title="Last Man Camping!" sub="1" icon="r_surlst" mod="CAMP">
	<p>
		Cette récompense est octroyée au dernier campeur survivant d'une ville. Il faut toutefois respecter plusieurs conditions:
	</p>
	<ul>
		<li>Le citoyen doit être <strong>installé en camping dans l'Outre-Monde</strong>,</li>
		<li>Il doit mourir des suites de l'attaque (pas d'un suicide, d'une infection ou d'une déhydratation par exemple),</li>
		<li>La ville doit avoir tenu <strong>au moins 5 jours complets</strong>,</li>
		<li>
			La ville doit avoir été <a href="/#help?id=devast">dévastée</a> la veille ou avant
			(<i>une ville est dévastée si elle n'avait plus d'habitants entre ses murs au cours d'une nuit</i>),
		</li>
	</ul>
</h>-->

<!-- TODO HACK: herolock -->
<h id="hero" title="Hero mode" sub="1" icon="small_hero">
	<div class="help">
		Hero mode is <strong>the premium mode of Die2Nite</strong>.
		For all the details, please go <a href="#hero?sk=fe0ce" onclick="js.XmlHttp.get('hero?sk=fe0ce',this); return false;">HERE</a> for more information.
	</div>
	<h2>Veteran Hero advantages</h2>
	<p>
		In addition to all the advantages you have as a Hero, it is possible to unlock even more as your time served as a Hero grows. Make the most of your longevity...
	</p>
	<p>
		<strong>Each day lived as a Hero is noted in Your Soul. As soon as you have accumulated a certain number of Hero days, you automatically start to unlock awesome bonuses!</strong>
	</p>
	<p>
		The first of these bonuses is unlocked after only 7 days. The subsequent bonuses are awarded every 15 days.
	</p>
	<p>
		Please note:
	</p>
	<ul>
		<li>While you are in hero mode, bonuses will be unlocked.</li>
		<li>If you cease to be a Hero, you will no longer receive these bonuses.</li>
		<li>If you subsequently become a Hero again, you will start receiving your bonuses again and you will continue exactly where you left off (previous progress will not be lost).</li>
	</ul>
</h>

<h id="team" title="Coalitions" sub="1" icon="r_surgrp">
	<p>The <strong>Coalitions</strong> system allows for team play. It is a straightforward system which is also very powerful. It is based on the following concepts:</p>
	<ul>
		<li>1 - Allowing friends to find each other and have adventures together</li>
		<li>2 - Selecting and joining a world should be as simple as possible</li>
	</ul>
	<h2>How does it work?</h2>
	<p>A player has to create the coalition from their "Soul" page. From here, they send invitations to friends who can then accept or refuse to join the coalition.</p>
	<p>Once players have joined the coalition, they can chat amongst themselves, discuss strategies and so forth...</p>
	<p>Then it's time for adventure! <strong>The first <i>available</i> member who joins a town will be followed by the other (available) members! It's as simple as that.</strong></p>
	<p>Clearly this system demands a certain degree of coordination between the players, but private chat functions are in place to make this possible:)</p>
	<p>It is also possible to leave a coalition at any point. The creator can also dissolve the coalition.</p>
	<p><strong>Finally, it is important to know that in the event of the creator dissoving the coalition, the coalition goes straight to hell with its creator.</strong></p> 

	<h2>Special Rules</h2>
	<p>
		You are not allowed to join a coalition in which a member is detected as being another account you have set up in addition to your primary account.
	</p>
	<p>
		Furthermore, you cannot join a coalition in which 2 members (or more) have signed in from the same machine as you in the last 15 days. 
	</p>
	<p>
		If you believe this has been wrongfully detected, contact technical support: we will do the necessary. 
		WARNING: we strongly recommend you do not contact technical support if you are in the wrong, you could very well come to regret it.
	</p>

	<h2>Frequently Asked Questions</h2>
	<dl class="faq">
		<dt>When the player who started the coalition joins a town, do ALL the members join the town (even those who are not connected)?</dt>
		<dd><strong>No,</strong> only players who are not already in a town will join the new town. Being signed in at the time or not makes no diference.</dd>

		<dt>If the coalition joins a town that has more than 35 people, will the town contain more than 40 people?</dt>
		<dd><strong> No,</strong> only the first active members of the coalition will be able to join. In order to be practically certain of joining the same town at a given time, all you need do is choose a random town.</dd>

		<dt>Does a coalition only last for one life?</dt>
		<dd><strong>No,</strong> a coalition will last indefinitely as long as it has neither been dissolved by the founder, nor abandoned by all the other players.</dd>
		<dd><strong>Warning</strong>: if the creator leaves the coalition, the coalition will be dissolved automatically!</dd>

		<dt>If I am not signed in when another player from my coalition joins a town, what happens?</dt>
		<dd>If you are not already in a town, you will automatically join the town chosen by the other member. As of the next time you sign in, you will be in that town.</dd>
	</dl>
</h>

<h id="homeUpgrade" title="House and Work" sub="1" icon="r_hbuild">
	<h2>Your House</h2>
	<p>Your house is your little haven of peace and tranquility in the terrifying world of Die2Nite.</p>
	<p>It is a <strong>vital location!</strong> This is where you can:</p>
	<ul>
		<li>Carry out personal projects</li>
		<li>Store objects in your chest (4 storage compartments by default)</li>
	</ul>

	<h2>Your rucksack and your chest</h2>
	<p>Your rucksack and your chest are the places where you can store objects you have found in the World Beyond and taken from the Bank.</p>
	<p>Each of these have a finite number or storage compartments, but <strong>it is possible to increase their storage capacity</strong>.</p>
	<p>To increase storage capacity, you will need to find additional objects (rucksack and chest) or make the necessary improvements yourself (chest only).</p>

	<h2>Improve your defences</h2>
	<p>You can upgrade your house to improve its defences. <strong>Each level upgraded awards more defence points.</strong>
	Each upgrade requires resources.</p>
	<p>Upgrading your house defences has two effects:</p>
	<ul>
		<li>Preventing the zombies from devouring you at night</li>
		<li>Increasing the town's defences</li>
	</ul>

	<h2>Upgrading your house</h2>

	<p>
		Your house only needs to be built and upgraded. Die2Nite also has a system of <strong>Improvements</strong> which allow you to improve your own defences, increase your storage capacity or even become a craftsman!
	</p>
	<p>Each improvement costs <strong>APs</strong> and/or <strong>resources</strong>.</p>
	<p>There are many types of improvements to carry out: </p>
	<ul>
		<li><strong>Storage Compartments</strong>: increase your storage capacity</li>
		<li><strong>Defence</strong>: increases your ability to fight off the zombies during the nightly attack</li>
		<li><strong>Lock</strong>: allows you to prevent other citizens from "borrowing" your property</li>
		<li><strong>Alarm</strong>: informs you if other citizens have been "borrowing" your stuff </li>
		<li><strong>Curtains</strong>: allow you to hide the contents of your chest from your comrades' prying eyes...</li>
	</ul>
	<p>To carry out these improvements, you need to be a <strong>Hero</strong>.</p>
</h>


<h id="ghoul" title="Ghouls" sub="1" icon="small_ghoul" mod="GHOULS">
	<p>
		<strong>Ghouls are partially infected citizens, but who are not completely transformed into zombies</strong>
		(Sometimes Mother Nature has a really good laugh at our expense).
	</p>
	<p>
		It's really difficult to distinguish between a ghoul and a normal, healthy citizen. As such, a ghoul tends to decimate the ranks of a town if something is not done about it quickly.

	</p>
	<h2>I am a ghoul!</h2>
	<img src="/gfx/loc/fr/ghoulHunger.jpg" alt="" class="art"/>
	<p>
		In order to survive, you have to keep an eye on the <strong>Voracity</strong> meter, located at the top right, below your status.
	</p>
	<p>
		Devour a citizen or consume cold human flesh (in any form) to reduce your Voracity.
	</p>
	<div class="clear"></div>
	<table class="procons">
		<tr>
			<th>Advantages</th>
			<th>Disadvantages</th>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td>
				<ul>
					<li>eating human flesh, whether alive or dead, will restore your <img ::ignore:: src="/gfx/icons/small_ap.gif" alt=""/> and reduce your Voracity,</li>
					<li>you will gain <strong>1 day of Hero mode for each citizen devoured</strong> (awarded upon your death),</li>
					<li>you are immune to the effects of <strong>any infection</strong> and <strong>thirst</strong> ; you will not die while walking around the World Beyond or die at 23h00 (server time) as a result of an infected wound,</li>
					<li>you can, if you wish, enter or leave the town surreptitiously (ie. no record of it in the register),</li>
				</ul>
			</td>
			<td>
				<ul>
					<li>if your voracity meter <strong>crosses the red zone</strong>, you will die at 23h00 (server time) during the attack,</li>
					<li>you will be <strong>wounded</strong> if you drink water,</li>
					<li>if you decide to devour a citizen in town, your chances of being seen will be proportional to the number of citizens currently in town,</li>
					<li>your voracity increases at 23h00 (server time), after the attack: therefore, you must devour a citizen regularly to survive. Furthermore, if the town is devastated, you will feel less temptation and voracity.</li>  
					<li>if you devour a human with a particular status, it will be transferred to you at that moment: be sure to choose your victims carefully, and not give in to the temptation to snack on the first junkie that passes by!</li>
				</ul>
			</td>
		</tr>
	</table>
	
	<h2>How do I become a ghoul?</h2>
	<p>
		A citizen can become a ghoul by consuming various suspicious comestibles:
		Travellers' corpses, meaty bones, human flesh amongst other things...
		Of course the risks are minimal, but are you willing to risk mutating?
	</p>
	<!--
	<p>The frequency with which ghouls appear depends on type of town :</p>
	<ul>
		<li>in <strong>Non-distant Regions</strong>, no ghouls until around day 12,</li>
		<li>in <strong>Distant Regions</strong>, no ghouls until around day 9 or 10,</li>
		<li>in <strong>Hardcore</strong>, ghouls will appear in the first few days (if active).</li>
	</ul>
	<p>
		Several ghouls can coexist in the same town if a new ghoul appears and the previous ghoul(s) have not yet been eliminated.
	</p>
	-->
	<p>
		<strong>It is possible to use certain products to defend against becoming a ghoul, or to heal oneself once getting into that mess such as the anti-ghoul vaccine!</strong>
	</p>

	<h2>How do I kill a ghoul?</h2>
	<p>
		A ghoul isn't really a zombie and therefore is not immune to death by "natural causes" such as hanging and drug addiction. However, they are immune to thirst and infection, and therefore any related deaths.
	</p>
	<p>
		<strong>As in life, violence is the best solution, and will kill a ghoul instantly. </strong>
		Attention though: aggression costs a lot of <img ::ignore::src="/gfx/icons/small_ap.gif" alt=""/> and has an increased chance of wounding the victim. Beware of unwarranted violence.
	</p>
	<h2>How can ghouls be discovered?</h2>
	<p>
		The town register is your biggest ally. You should also keep an eye on the comings and goings of players.
	</p>
	<p>
		Don't forget that anybody can be transformed into a ghoul! Even the charismatic leader who is calling the shots and giving you good advice.
	</p>
</h>


<h id="jobs" title="Jobs">
	<img class="pip" src="/gfx/art/pip/metier.gif" alt=""/>
	<p>
		<strong>All citizens in Die2Nite start out as a simple Resident</strong>.
		Heroes choose their own job which gives them an advantage in a given domain: a Scavenger, for example, can find more objects in the desert than an average citizen.
	</p>
	<p>
		A job <strong>gives the citizen a special object or tool which only they can possess.</strong>. A camouflage suit for the Scout, a spade for the Scavenger, etc...
	</p>
</h>

<h id="job_basic" title="Resident" icon="item_basic_suit" sub="1">
	<img src="/gfx/art/pip/basic.gif" alt="" class="pip"/>
	<p>
		A Resident is effectively a normal, everyday citizen, with no remarkable abilities to speak of...
	</p>

	<label>Basic equipment: <strong><img src="/gfx/icons/item_basic_suit.gif" alt=""/> Citizen's uniform</strong></label>
	<em>
		The citizen's uniform has remained unchanged in years. This is also the uniform you will wear for the rest of your days. Nonetheless, the outfit is functional and pretty comfortable, so there's not really that much to complain about...
	</em>

	<h2>How do I play as a Resident?</h2>
	<p>
		There's no real secret to it, you can do pretty much what you like... within reason!
	</p>
</h>


<h id="job_collec" title="Scavenger" icon="item_pelle" sub="1">
	<img src="/gfx/art/pip/collec.gif" alt="" class="pip"/>
	<p>
		The Scavenger is able to find many more objects when searching in the desert.
	</p>

	<label>Basic equipment: <strong><img src="/gfx/icons/item_pelle.gif" alt=""/> Small spade</strong></label>
	<em>
		The small spade (automatically) reduces the time required for each search in the desert...  The chances of finding an object are also significantly increased.
	</em>

	<h2>How do I play as a Scavenger?</h2>
	<p>
		Your automatic searches take <strong>30 minutes less</strong> than other citizens, therefore you can carry out more searches in a day! Your chances of finding something are also much better than those of normal citizens.
	</p>
	<p>
		Furthermore, when you're in the World Beyond, your keen Scavenger's instinct lets you know in advance whether a neighbouring zone still contains objects or if it is depleted (this skill also allows you to discover buildings which contain objects)!
	</p>
	<div class="update">
		Once again, the scavenger is well versed in scavenging in cramped, labyrinthian situations. A scavenger will have <strong>50% more oxygen</strong> with which to explore the maze of corridors in abandoned buildings in more depth.
	</div>
</h>

<!--
<h id="job_soldier" title="Casque rouge" icon="item_watergun_empty" sub="1">
	<img src="/gfx/art/pip/soldier.gif" alt="" class="pip"/>
	<p>
		Le Casque Rouge est celui qu'on appelle quand il y a du zombie à décimer dans le désert. Attention
		toutefois, son arme consomme de l'eau pure et ce "gaspillage" pourrait être mal vu...
	</p>

	<label>Equipement de départ: <strong><img src="/gfx/icons/item_watergun_empty.gif" alt=""/> Pistolet à eau</strong></label>
	<em>
		Projette de l'eau pure sur 1 zombie (et le brûle instantanément). Cette arme consomme des
		<strong><img src="/gfx/icons/item_water.gif" alt=""/> Rations d'eau</strong> portées par le Casque Rouge.
	</em>

	<h2>Comment le jouer?</h2>
	<p>
		Prenez une Ration d'eau dans votre sac à dos pour l'utiliser en tant que munition. Lorsque vous arrivez
		sur une case où se trouve un Zombie, cliquez sur l'action "Utiliser: Pistoler à Eau". Votre arme a 1
		chance sur 3 de consommer totalement une Ration d'Eau pour chaque zombie que vous éliminerez.
	</p>
</h>
-->

<h id="job_eclair" title="Scout" icon="item_vest_on" sub="1">
	<img src="/gfx/art/pip/eclair.gif" alt="" class="pip"/>
	<p>
		The Scout can sneak past groups of zombies undetected, allowing them to explore the farthest reaches of the desert, in almost total safety. Warning: carrying out any actions when hiding causes you to break cover and reveal yourself!
	</p>

	<label>Basic equipment: <strong><img src="/gfx/icons/item_vest_on.gif" alt=""/> Camouflage suit</strong></label>
	<em>
		This outfit allows you to move around freely in zombie controlled zones in the desert. Always be careful though, there is always a chance of being discovered if the zone is swarming with living dead...
	</em>

	<h2>How do I play as a Scout?</h2>
	<p>
		Your role involves discovering areas of interest and being a one-man scouting party. Take advantage of your sneakiness to go beyond enemy lines.
	</p>
	<p>
		Only certain actions are allowed while you are camouflaged: drinking, eating and taking drugs for example.
	</p>
	<p>
		in the World Beyond, you will be able to estimate the number of zombies in neighbouring zones (maybe with the occasional mistake...).
	</p>
	[mod camp]
	<p>
		Finally, you will be penalised less for camping in a zone occupied by zombies. Never underestimate the sneakiness!
	</p>
	[/mod]
</h>


<h id="job_guardian" title="Guardian" icon="item_shield" sub="1">
	<img src="/gfx/art/pip/guardian.gif" alt="" class="pip"/>
	<p>
		In the World Beyond, the Guardian can keep more zombies at bay than an average citizen.	<strong>The guardian retains this advantage even when travelling as part of a group</strong>!
	</p>

	<label>Basic Equipment: <strong><img src="/gfx/icons/item_shield.gif" alt=""/>Riot Shield </strong></label>
	<em>
		In the desert, the Guardian can face 4 zombies alone instead of the usual 2 (for a normal citizen).
	</em>
	<h2>How do I play as a Guardian?</h2>
	<p>
		Normally, when in the desert, a lone citizen can face a maximum of 2 zombies. Any more than that and they will become trapped and will no longer be able to flee. <strong>As a Guardian, you can face a maximum of 4 zombies</strong> thanks to your trusty Riot Shield.
	</p>
	<p>
		Every guardian gives a defensive bonus to the town.
	</p>
	<p>
		When on watch, a guardian gives 30 additional defence points to the town, they also have a 5% greater chance of surviving if the hordes' attack is inferior to the town's defense points.
	</p>
</h>

<h id="job_hunter" title="Survivalist" icon="item_surv_book" sub="1" mod="JOB_HUNTER">
	<img src="/gfx/art/pip/hunter.gif" alt="" class="pip"/>
	<p>
		Having chosen to live in the most extreme solitude, the Survivalist is the guy nobody has talked to in years. The good thing is, that they have learned how to always get by on their own when it comes down to it. <strong>A Survivalist will always find something edible (food or water), regardless of where they are in the desert and when they want to find it</strong>.
	</p>

	<label>Basic Equipment: <strong><img src="/gfx/icons/item_surv_book.gif" alt=""/> Survival Guide</strong></label>
	<em>
		Your precious guide, entitled "Junior Woodchuck's Scouting Manual". Even though it may seem like a children's book, it contains a wealth of information on how to survive alone in the wild. It allows you to easily find something to eat or drink.
	</em>
	<h2>How do I play as a Survivalist?</h2>
	<p>
		As you no longer need to carry food, you should always have what you need on your person, no matter where you are. When other citizens risk dying of hunger the morning after some extreme camping, you will always be able to find a juicy worm or a root to nibble on.
	</p>
	<p>
		Attention, Survivalist! You can only use this ability once per day: you will only be able to find one item of food OR some water.	
	</p>
	<p>
		You also have an advantage when extreme camping: for a normal citizen, the chances of survival are capped at 90% (as for most people there is always an inherent risk of dying at 23h00 (server time)). A Survivalist is unconcerned with "most people": if they take care of business, they have a 100% chance of survival.
	</p>
	<p>
		<strong>The Survivalist, being a cantankerous neurotic with sociopathic tendancies,
		will only be able to find water or food once they are at a distance of 3km from the town.</strong>
	</p>
</h>

<h id="job_tamer" title="Tamer" icon="item_tamed_pet" sub="1" mod="JOB_TAMER">
	<img src="/gfx/art/pip/tamer.gif" alt="" class="pip"/>
	<p>
		Always accompanied by their trusty 3-legged labradoodle (a noble breed, and not even a little bit ridiculous), the Tamer is able to <strong>send some of the contents of their rucksack back to the town from anywhere in the World Beyond</strong>.
	</p>

	<label>Basic Equipment: <strong><img src="/gfx/icons/item_tamed_pet.gif" alt=""/> 3-legged Labradoodle</strong></label>
	<em>
		She follows you everywhere, smelling of wet dog, limping and drooling excessively. And she barks. A lot. You can ask her to take the contents of your rucksack back to the town once per day, from no matter where you are in the World Beyond. 
	</em>
	<h2>How do I play as a Tamer?</h2>
	<p>
		An excellent role if you like expeditions to distant zones: if you need space, give all your stuff to your dog. Your fellow travellers will be happy to make the most of it too.
	</p>
		<p>
		Your dog cannot normally carry heavy objects.
		However, you can give him some steroids to overcome this limitation... Don't make a face like that, it's probably really good for its health.
	</p>
	<p>
		The Tamer's faithful labradoodle companion will show their master the way out of the ruins, a blue arrow allows every tamer to never lose their bearings.
	</p>
</h>

<h id="job_tech" title="Technician" icon="item_keymol" sub="1" mod="JOB_TECH">
	<img src="/gfx/art/pip/tech.gif" alt="" class="pip"/>
	<p>
		Always ready to get involved with any construction project, the technician, abandoned alone on a desert island with nothing but a toothpick, could construct an enormous entirely autonomous wheel.
		So just imagine what technical marvels they could construct with a shiny new DIY kit!
	</p>

	<label>Basic Equipment: <strong><img src="/gfx/icons/item_keymol.gif" alt=""/> Handyman's Toolbelt</strong></label>
	<em>
		Unparalleled for smashing construction records, this complete tool kit includes a top-of-the-line adjustable wrench!
	</em>
	<h2>How do I play as a Technician?</h2>
	<p>
		Thanks to their highly unusual skillset, the technician will be of great help when it comes to delegating tasks at the workshop.
		Every day, they have <strong><img src="/gfx/loc/fr/small_pc.gif" alt=""/> Construction Points</strong> which allow the tech to continue building long after the average citizen is exhausted. However, the tech must always keep <strong>1<img src="/gfx/loc/fr/small_pa.gif" alt=""/> Action Point</strong> to be able to use them, otherwise the tech will lose all motivation and not be able to use any	<strong><img src="/gfx/loc/fr/small_pc.gif" alt=""/> Construction Points.</strong>
	</p>
	<p>Technicians can use their Construction Points to repair buildings and transform / refine objects in the workshop.</p>
	<p>
		The tech will also be a huge help in abandoned buildings: their talents, combined with the right tools, allows them to take impressions of locks in secured doors.
		Nonetheless, the impression has to be worked on in town in order to manufacture a temporary key, which allows the tech to open the door in question at a later date.
	</p>
</h>

<h id="jobs" title="Town Roles"  mod="SHAMAN_SOULS">
	<img class="pip" src="/gfx/art/pip/shaman.gif" alt=""/>
	<p>
		<strong>Each citizen starts as a lowly resident in the Die2Nite universe</strong>.
		However sometimes fate intervenes and drags you from your little life into grand adventures and bold actions.
	</p>
</h>

<h id="shaman" title="Shaman" icon="item_shaman" sub="1" mod="SHAMAN_SOULS">
	<img src="/gfx/art/pip/shaman.gif" alt="" class="pip"/>
	<p>
		The Shaman is an incredibly powerful voodoo sorceror who can profit from the deaths of other citizens to carry out their black magic.
		The Shaman knows how to make use of the useless and knows how to bring about a more useful reincarnation for our dearly departed.
	</p>
	<h2>How do you become the town Shaman?</h2>
	<p>
		During the first night, and each time the Shaman dies, a town meeting will take place. During this meeting a debate takes place and after much arguing, shirking of responsibilities and no doubt drinking, the most... "qualified" resident is designated as the Shaman! From that moment on the Shaman will have access to new powers and a new set of "points".
	</p>
	<h2>I'm the Shaman, what do I do?</h2>
	<p>
		Thanks to their unique world view, the Shaman can carry out unique actions, which can make them at once a healer, a psychic, or a charlatan.
		The Shaman can:
		<ul>
			<li>Heal citizens <strong>in town</strong>. Relieve terror, infections or even extract alcohol or drugs from the bodies of their comrades. Success is not guaranteed, however. Sometimes, during the healing process, the Shaman takes the illness which plagues the victim into their own body.</li>
			<li>Purify zones by making rain fall on those areas. If the rain falls on the town, the water will refill the well a little</li>
			<li>Guide citizens to the location of souls in the World Beyond.</li>
			<li>Brew up special potions that protect mere mortals against the evil of tortured souls.</li>
		</ul>
	</p>
	<p>
		The Shaman is therefore a central character in the cruel comedy that is the survival of the town. But for how long will the Shaman survive?
	</p>
</h>

<h id="guide" title="Guide to the World Beyond" icon="item_guide" sub="1">
	<p>
		The Guide to the World Beyond is a special citizen. The heavy responsibility of helping his comrades navigate the World Boyond falls on his shoulders.
		This means that this citizen can organise expiditions, be the leader (even if he's not a hero), and add a control point for each other citizen present in his zone.
	</p>
	<h2>Do how do I become this, Guide, of which you speak?</h2>
	<p>
		By being elected! 
		on the first night in town, and after the death of each successive guide (yeah it's a dangerous job) an election will be held.
		During this manifestation of democracy, a debate will take place and the vote ballot will follow. At the end the most... Qualified... citizen will be chosen to wear the tagrget, I mean hat...
		From this moment on the new Guide willhave special abilities that they will be able to exploit for the good of the town.
	</p>
	<p>
		So the Guide becomes a vital part of the survival of the town and his neighbours... But how long will this new leader last anyway???
	</p>
</h>

<h id="city" title="Welcome to the Town">
	<img src="/gfx/screen/city.gif" alt="" class="art"/>
	<p>
		The Town is the place that you leave each day and return to each night (more or less). After spending some time searching in the desert, you should return to the Town. The chances of surviving outside the town are limited... 
	</p>

	<h2>The Hub of the Community</h2>
	<p>
		The town is where you can meet all your unfortunate comrades, talk to them at the Well or at the Town Gates...
		It is in town that you will arrange expeditions, and also where you will store the items you find.
	</p>

</h>

<h id="demo" title="The Community" sub="1" icon="small_world">

	<h2>To communicate is to survive</h2>
	<p>Just as the Scout is an important job in the community because he is a vital source of information, everyone, regardless of their job title, has a role to play. Admittedly, it is possible to survive alone, but maybe this solution is best kept for when there is a shortage of people to repel the Horde...
	However, at the start of your new existence, allying with your fellow citizens is the best way to build a strong town and the best way to gather objects and resources from the World Beyond more easily.
	</p>

	<h2>The Bank</h2>
	<p>In order to construct buildings and build the town's defences, community-spirited adventurers can give the fruits of their scavenging to the town <strong>if they so desire</strong>. For example, giving pieces of sheet metal which were recovered from old aircraft cabins can be used to reinforce the armour plating on the outer walls. In the same way, wood or metal given to the town can be used in the construction of community buildings.</p>

	<p class="help"><strong>As the saying goes</strong>: Share nothing, give nothing, that's the best way to get eaten.</p>

	<h2>The Forum and message boxes</h2>
	<img src="gfx/loc/::LANG::/forum.gif" alt="" class="art"/>
	<p>The Forum and the various communication boxes around important places in town are the places of choice for meeting people, discussing strategies and having a laugh. It is also where you will find SOS calls from adventurers who are lost in the desert or who have found themselves in a bad situation...</p>

	<h2>The Chronicle</h2>
	<img src="gfx/loc/::LANG::/news.gif" alt="" class="art"/>
	<p>Every night, after the Horde have come and gone, the surviving citizens publish a newspaper which reports on the important events of the day.</p>

	<h2>Citizen's Bureau</h2>
	<img src="gfx/menu/jobs.gif" alt="" class="art"/>
	<p>It is in the Citizen's Bureau that you will find fellow citizens with whom you might travel the World Beyond.</p>

	<h2>Private Messaging</h2>
	<img src="gfx/loc/::LANG::/message.gif" alt="" class="art"/>
	<p>
		If you wish to discuss something in private with another adventurer, the messaging tool is what you need. Go to the <strong>Citizens</strong> section of the site, then click on a citizen's house. Click the button <strong>Leave a note on their door</strong>. This is how you can create group strategies or conspire against other players...
	</p>
	<p>
		<strong>Warning: You can only read your private messages when you are in the town</strong>.
	</p>

</h>


<h id="votes" title="Constructing New Buildings" sub="1" icon="small_home">
	<p>
		The town is not a static location. You need it to evolve. This is how to proceed to get new builings in the town :
	</p>
	<ol>
		<li>collect <strong>resources in the desert</strong> (wood, metal, armour...) and drop them off at the <strong>Bank</strong></li>
		<li>go to the  <strong>Construction Sites</strong> in the town</li>
		<li>find out which buildings can be constructed from resources currently available from the bank: they will have a <strong>Build</strong> button next to them</li>
		<li>click once on the <strong>Build</strong> button next to the building you wish to work on. This will use <strong>1 AP</strong> from your reserves.</li>
	</ol>

	<p>
		As soon as a building has been sufficiently worked on (sufficient APs have been invested), the building is constructed <strong>immediately</strong>!
	</p>
	<p>
		Buildings can be constructed over several days. Just come back the next day to continue working on an incomplete building! You can invest more than 1 AP on a given site, if you really want the building to get finished... <strong></strong>
	</p>

	<h2>Temporary buildings</h2>
	<p>
		"Temporary" buildings are "single use" constructions: they only last for the duration of the Horde's attack, then are destroyed. These are generally cheap, but powerful defences which need to be rebuilt each day. 
	</p>
</h>


<h id="bplans" title="Blueprints" sub="1" icon="item_bplan_u">
	<p>
		Some particularly innovative or ambitious construction projects cannot be carried out when the town is just starting out.
	</p>
	<p>
		<strong>You can unlock certain projects by getting your hands on blueprints.</strong>
	</p>
	
	<h2>How do I find blueprints?</h2>
	<ul>
		<li>it is possible to find them just by scavenging in the World Beyond, but they're reputed to be difficult to find,</li>
		<li>
			each new town starts with 3 "free" plans left in the World Beyond. These plans are diferent from those found by scavenging, because they are already uncovered, sitting on the ground. All you need to do is find them!
			<ul>
				<li>non-distant regions: 3 rare plans + 1 very rare plan</li>
				<li>distant regions: 5 rare plans + 2 very rare plans</li>
			</ul>
		</li>
		<li>
			camping: if you survive an evening camping in a building, you will automatically find a blueprint
			("uncommon" in buildings close to the town, and "rare" for faraway buildings). Note that one building can only provide <strong>one blueprint per game</strong> (there is no point in camping in the same building multiple times),
		</li>
		<li>there are other methods for discovering these plans: you just need to discover them!</li>
	</ul>
	
	<h2>How do I use them?</h2>
	<p>
		They can only be used in town: click on the plan when you're in your home to study it.
	</p>
	<p>
		The project that it unlocks will be added to the list of projects available to the town and an announcement will be made in the town register.
	</p>	
</h>


<h id="upgrades" title="Daily Upgrades" sub="1" icon="small_city_up">
	<img src="/gfx/screen/upgrades.gif" alt="" class="art"/>
	<p>
		Once they have been built, certain construction sites (like the Great Pit, for example) can be <strong>upgraded</strong>.
		Each day, the citizens can vote for <strong>one, and only one</strong> upgrade. Citizens should vote for whichever upgrade is more useful for the town.
	</p>
	<div class="clear"></div>
	<p>
		Just before the 23h00 (server time) attack, <strong>the upgrade which has received the most votes is accepted and constructed immediately.</strong>
	</p>
	<p>
		Upgrades are free: <strong> they require neither AP nor resources</strong>.
	</p>

	<p>
		Each upgrade can be improved up to <strong>5 times</strong>, each level being increasingly powerful. These upgrades can have numerous effects on a town :
	</p>
	<ul>
		<li>improved defences,</li>
		<li>increased water reserves,</li>
		<li>reduced construction costs,</li>
		<li>detection of zombies,</li>
		<li>special abilities...</li>
	</ul>

	<div class="help">
		<p>
			Warning: choosing one upgrade over another is very important! Bearing in mind that a town is limited to one upgrade
			per day, a town which lasts 10 days is only entitled to 10 upgrades, so choose wisely!
		</p>
		<p>
			Discuss it in the forum!
		</p>
	</div>


</h>

<h id="attack" title="The Attack of the Hordes" sub="1" icon="small_fight">
	<img src="/gfx/art/attack.png" alt="" class="art"/>	
	<p>
		Every night, at 23h00 (server time), the hordes of living dead attack the town. Each attack consists of a certain number of zombies.
	</p>
	<h2>Phase 1: The Return of the Living Dead</h2>
	<p>
		All the citizens who died in the town the night before and whose corpse has not been destroyed or dumped in the desert will
		rise again! As they are already within the town walls, they'll do untold damage!
	</p>
	<p>The dead who have been dumped in the desert will attack the town as one of the Horde.</p>

	<h2>Phase 2: The Town's Defences</h2>
	<p>
		For every defence point the town has amassed, one zombie will be blocked.
		<br/>Furthermore, every citizen's house will contribute half it's defensive value.
	</p>
	<p>
		<em>Eg: if the town's buildings give 5 defence points and one citizen has a house with 2 defence points, the total number of defence points will be 5 + 2/2 = 6 points. </em>
	</p>
	<p>
		<em>Eg: if the town has 7 defence points, 7 attacking zombies will be blocked every night.</em>
	</p>
	<p>Warning: <strong>If the Town Gates are open, none of the town's defences will count!</strong></p>

	<h2>Phase 3: Citizens under attack</h2>
	<p>
		Each zombie that isn't blocked will attack a citizen's house. If the citizen has less defence points than the number of zombies who are attacking him, they will be eaten alive in their home!
	</p>
	<p>
		if a citizen manages to repel the zombie attack, they will nonetheless be terrorised unless they have something to make them forget the awful event...
	</p>

	<h2>The Last Attack :</h2>
	<p>If the attack kills all the residents, one of them will be will be selected to win the <strong>Last Man Standing</strong> title! Read more on the Last Man Standing <a href="/#help?id=lastOne">here</a>.</p>
	
	[mod building_damage]
	<h2>Phase 4: Damage to construction sites (Hardcore)</h2>
	<p>
		All completed construction projects will be subjected to damage during the assault.
		<strong>the zombies which are stopped by the defences will attack the constructions instead.</strong>
	</p>
	<p>
		<strong>if any building takes too much damage, it is destroyed and must be rebuilt the next day.</strong>
	</p>
	<p>
		A partially damaged building can be repared by investing APs in the Construction Sites area. If it is an defensive object, its value will be reduced until it is repaired.
	</p>
	[/mod]
<!--
	<h2>Informations diverses</h2>
	<ul>
		<li>Si vous n'avez pas toujours pas choisi de métier avant l'attaque de la Hordes du <strong>2ème jour</strong>, vous mourrez. Sans condition.</li>
		<li><strong>Si vous êtes dehors pendant l'attaque des Hordes, vous êtes mort(e)</strong>. Sans condition.</li>
		<li>Les attaques vont en empirant, ne tardez pas à protéger la ville!</li>
	</ul>
-->
</h>

<!--
	<h2>Phase 3: les veilleurs contre attaquent</h2>
	<p>
		Chaque veilleur tue le nombre de zombie égal à la valeur d'attaque de l'arme la plus puissante contenue dans son sac à dos.
		Etant donné les risques pris, chaque veilleur à 50% de chances de subir une blessure.
	</p>-->



<h id="guard" title="The Watchmen" sub="1" icon="job_soldat" mod="GUARDIAN">
	<h2>Who are they?</h2>
	<p>
		To defend you town against the Hordes, there are several solutions.
		One of those is to join the <strong>Watchmen</strong>.
	</p>
	<p>When you decide to become a watchman:</p>
	<ul>
		<li>You have to choose your weapons and place them in your rucksack</li>
		<li>Make sure to take into account the strengths and weaknesses of your profession, and your state of health</li>
		<li>All weapons or defensive objects used on the watch will be destroyed once it is over, weapons with multiple charges will use one during the watch.</li>
	</ul>
	<h2>How does it work?</h2>
	<p>During the attack, if the zombies breach the town defences, the watchmen intevene:</p>
	<ul>
		<li>The zombies will attack watchmen at random</li>
		<li>Each watchman uses the weapons stored in their rucksack</li>
		<li>Your status affects your capacity to defend the town, along with your chances of survival. <strong>Warning! Your status will evolve before the attack, so if you are injured before you become a Watchman, when the attack comes, you will already be infected!!</strong></li>
	</ul>
	<h2>What are the risks?</h2>
	<p>A watchman has a <strong>10% chance of being wounded or terorized</strong> and a <strong>5% chance of being killed</strong> during the attack of the Hordes...</p>
	<p>Guardians have a survival bonus of <strong>5%</strong>. Therefore they can reasonably expect to return home safe from a night's watch.</p>
	<h2>What if my bottle goes?</h2>
	<p>You can abandon your post until 22h59.</p>
	<p><strong>That doesn't mean to say that your fellow townspeople will appreciate the gesture...</strong></p>
	
	<p>Warning, if the number of attacking zombies is greater than the town's defences, the watchmen's chances of surviving are drastically reduced!
	This is the moment at which you'll see the true defenders of the town.</p>
</h>

<h id="justice" title="Crimes and Punishment" sub="1" icon="small_star">
	<img src="/gfx/screen/justice.gif" alt="" class="art"/>
	<p>
		When you <strong>go to a citizen's house</strong>, in the Citizens section, you can <strong>REPORT</strong> them. 
	</p>
	<p>
		This action constitutes a complaint against the citizen. If <strong>::MinComplaints::&nbsp;complaints</strong> are registered against the citizen, they will be <strong>shunned by the community</strong>.
	</p>
	<h2>Effects of being shunned</h2>
	<p>
		All objects which are considered essential for the community <strong>are deposited in the bank</strong> (wood, metal, defensive objects, etc...).
	</p>
	<p>
		A shunned citizen is no longer able to :
		<ul>
			<li>take objects from the bank (they can still deposit objects in the bank for the community though),</li>
			<li>take additional water from the well (their daily ration is still permitted),</li>
			<li>work at construction sites,</li>
			<li>use the workshop,</li>
			<li>open and close the town gates,</li>
			<li>register complaints against citizens.</li>
		</ul>
	</p>
	<p>
		However, a shunned citizen has <a href="/#help?id=banned">new skills</a> which gives them a chance of surviving alone...
	</p>

	<h2>Rob a citizen</h2>
	<p>
		When a citizen is not in their house, i.e., in the World Beyond, you can go into their house. Once inside <strong>you can steal an object (once per day).</strong>
	</p>
	<p>
		<strong>A theft like this has a 50% chance of being discovered</strong>, in which case, all citizens will be informed (your name will appear in red in the town register)! The consequences of your actions will be decided by your fellow citizens...
	</p>

	<h2>Elimination</h2>
	<p>
		When a citizen becomes a real danger to the community, it is sometimes necessary to take things further.
	</p>
	<p>
		Citizens can construct a gallows at the construction site to definitively eliminate the wrongdoer. To hang someone, a certain number of complaints must be registered, in much the same way as for a banishment.
	</p>
	<p>
		In the case of banishment (shunning), the objects belonging to the hanged citizen will be given to the town (bank). If a citizen in possession of a rusty chain is shunned, the chain will also be returned to the town (bank).
	</p>
	<p>Note: there are other ways of getting rid of undesirable types (murder, meat locker, ...).</p>	
	[mod_fragile_hanger]
	<p>
		As a hanging is an unusually violent event, <strong>the gallows is systematically destroyed after it is used</strong>
	</p>
	[/mod]

</h>

<h id="banned" title="Shunned Citizens" icon="small_ban" sub="1">


	<h2>The Return of the Shunned</h2>
	<p>
		Every day, the pariahs (shunned citizens) of a given town can participate in an uprising. <strong>If the insurrection is successful, all free citizens will be shunned and all the pariahs will have their liberty restored.</strong>
	</p>
	<p>
		The following rules apply :
	</p>
	<ul>
		<li>each pariah can participate in the uprising once per day,</li>
		<li>each pariah must participate every day in order for the insurrection to have a chance of success,</li>
		<li>there can be a maximum of one insurrection during the town's existence.</li>
	</ul>
	<p>
		Amongst other things, the insurrection system takes into account the number of pariahs, the number of free citizens, the number of survivors and the balance of forces.
	</p>
	<p>
		<em>
			Example: if 10 citizens are shunned, they will only need a few days to stage an uprising.
			If there are only 3 shunned citizens, it will take them around 20 days!
		</em>
	</p>
	<p>
		Staging an insurrection is a long-drawn-out task: each pariah must participate every day to make it happen!
	</p>

	<h2>Strategy of the shunned</h2>
	<p>
		<strong>Once shunned, a citizen can no longer make use of the town's facilities, so to get what they need to survive, they must fend for themselves by adopting less orthodox methods.</strong>
	</p>
	<p>
		From this point forward, they will have two special actions: 
	</p>
	<ul>
		<li>
			<strong>Search the town's waste</strong>: this action is carried out at the town gates (outside) and allows you to find very poor quality bits and pieces. However, they could be useful...
		</li>
		<li>
			<strong>Hide your rucksack</strong>: this action allows the shunned to conceal the contents of their rucksack. Only the shunned can see and collect objects concealed in this way. However, normal citizens have a small chance of discovering the cache when searching. 
		</li>
	</ul>

</h>


<h id="chaos" title="Chaos" icon="small_death" sub="1">
	<img src="/gfx/screen/chaos.gif" alt="" class="art"/>
	<p>
		When a town finds itself on the brink of extinction, it falls into the grip of Chaos. It is impossible to get out of this state.
		This mode is activated if, following an attack, all the following conditions are satisfied :
	</p>
	<ul>
		<li>the town has a population of less than <strong>::ChaosLimit::&nbsp; citizens</strong> 
		[mod camp]
		(campers are not considered as being in town),
		[/mod]
		</li>
		<li>the town has already survived for<strong> more than ::BeginPeriodDays:: days</strong>.</li>
	</ul>
	<p>
		There is no law or order in a town in the grip of chaos. As such, certain rules change dramatically :
	</p>
	<div class="clear"></div>
	<ul>
		<li>banishments are lifted</li>
		<li>complaints no longer have any effect,</li>
		<li>Robbing (the dead) is <strong>no longer</strong> limited to one object per person per day,</li>
		<li>there are no longer any anti-abuse restrictions in place as regards building and upgrading houses,</li>
		<li>the coordinates of a citizen in the World Beyond are no longer visible in the Citizens tab,</li>		
		<li>twice as many objects can now be taken from the bank (before the anti-abuse feature is activated).</li>
	</ul>
</h>

<h id="catapult" title="Catapult" icon="item_courroie" sub="1">
	<p>
		<strong>The catapult is an extremely powerful tool which allows any object to be sent to any zone in the desert.</strong> Very useful for long-range refreshment / reinforcement.
	</p>
	<p>
		Please note that <i>sometimes</i> the catapult misses its target and sends the object to a neighbouring zone... Furthermore, even when due care is taken to protect the package being sent, certain <i>rare</i> objects don't travel well.
	</p>
	<p>
		Using the catapult costs <img src="/gfx/loc/::LANG::/small_pa.gif" alt=""/>. This cost could be reduced by upgrading the construction site.
	</p>
	<h2>Who controls the catapult?</h2>
	<p>A citizen will be randomly chosen from a predetermined group :</p>
	<ul>
		<li>in the first instance, a citizen will be chosen from the heroes which have been active today,</li>
		<li>if none are found, a citizen will be chosen from the heroes in town,</li>
		<li>if still none are found, a citizen will be chosen from the citizens which have been active today,</li>
		<li>finally, in a worst-case scenario, a citizen will be chosen at random.</li>
	</ul>
</h>

<h id="rne" title="Towns in Non-distant-regions" icon="small_falsecity" sub="1" mod="RNE_REWARD_RESTRICTED">
	<p>
		Towns in Non-Distant Regions are meant to provide a soft landing for new players. These towns are accessible to everyone, however they have smaller maps and are numerous other changes that are designed to make the learning curve less steep for the novice. The idea is that experienced players can still mingle with beginners and help them as they start out. So say hello and smile to the newbies, you never know they might be your new best friend.
	</p>
	<p>
		<strong>Experienced players (those with more than 100 Soul Points) will only receive rewards and distinctions if the town makes it to day 8.</strong>
	</p>
	<p>
		So if you are an experienced player and you land in a town in a Non-Distant Region make it count! Help out the beginners and go for those rewards.
	</p>
	<p>
		Don't forget <a href="/#camp">Camping</a> is not active in Non-Distant Regions.
	</p>
	<h2>Spiritual Guide:</h2>
	<p>
		<strong>One unique title is up for grabs in Non-Distant towns: Spiritual Guide!</strong>
	</p>
	<p>
		<em>If you're an experienced player and you're up for a real challenge, then why not try for the Spiritual Guide title?  All you have to do is help a town that has at least 50% of its souls with less than 100 points survive past day 8. Basically round up a bunch of noobs and help them make it past day 8. Sounds easy right... 
	The points you can earn for this title are cumulative, but you'll only get them if you make it to day 8. Every day the town survives your points stack up.
		</em>
		<em>example:</em>
		<ul>
			<li>Day 1 : 1 point</li>
			<li>Day 2 : 2+1 points</li>
			<li>Day 5 : 5+4+3+2+1 points</li>
			<li>Etc etc</li>
		</ul>
	</p>
</h>

<h id="devast" title="Devastated town" icon="item_out_def_broken" sub="1" mod="CAMP">
	<p>
		If, when the Horde attack, the town is <strong>deserted</strong> (i.e. all surviving citizens are camping outside the walls OR have been killed in town), it will be considered <strong>devastated by the zombies</strong> :
	</p>
	<ul>
		<li><strong>the gates are irreparably damaged</strong>: the town will no longer be able to serve as a refuge for the survivors,</li>
		<li>buildings under construction will have to be started again from scratch,</li>
		<li>the water reserves in the well will be affected,</li>
		<li>it is no longer possible to carry out upgrades,</li>
		<li>citizens' houses are destroyed (interior improvements and upgrades are unaffected),</li>
		<li><strong>Chaos</strong> mode is immediately in effect (even if the usual conditions are not satisfied).</li>
		[mod ghouls]
		<li>the voracity of ghouls increases more gradually at 23h00 (server time).</li>
		[/mod]
	</ul>
	<p>
		Your days are numbered... A little advice for such a situation :
		<strong>Get the hell outta here!</strong>
	</p>
</h>


<h id="hardcore" title="Hardcore Towns" icon="small_arma" sub="1" mod="HARDCORE">
	<p><strong>Hardcore is the Die2Nite Expert mode.</strong></p>
	<p>
		Hardcore is the name given to towns where survival is particularly difficult: citizens have to face additional challenges!
	</p>
	<p>
		These towns are subject to various special rules:
	</p>
	<ul>
		[mod building_damage]
		<li>23h00 (server time) assaults inflict damage on the town's buildings which will need to be repaired regularly,</li>
		<li>defensive constructions are less effective when they are damaged</li>
		[/mod]
		[mod bank_damage]<li>Defensive objects in the bank can be destroyed during the attack</li>[/mod]
		[mod camp]<li>the chances of survival while camping are reduced,</li>[/mod]
		<li>the chances of dying from an infection at 23h00 (server time) are 75%,</li>
		<li>initial water reserves are inferior to those of normal towns,</li>
		<li>the functionality of some external sites in the directory is restricted,</li>
		<li>the Last Man Standing will receive <strong>twice as many hero days</strong> as well as an additional reward!</li>
		<li>the chances of wounding someone with the <strong>assault</strong> command are high.</li>
	</ul>
</h>		
			
<h id="customMap" title="Private towns" icon="item_chair" sub="1" mod="CUSTOM_MAP">
	<p>Private towns allow you to easily play with friends, or to create *theme towns*.</p>
	
	<h2>How do they work?</h2>
	<p>
		A private town works as follows:
	</p>
	<ul>
		<li>
			go to the "play" page when you die, then click on the "private towns" tab,
		</li>
		<li>you have to have unlocked the "Mayor" Hero skill,</li>
		<li>
			when you create the town, you will need to choose a secret code which you must give to participating players
			so that they can join your game,
		</li>
		<li>
			certain features can be freely modified (water stocks, map type, ...).
		</li>
	</ul>
	
	<h2>Special Rules</h2>
	<p>The following rules apply to all private towns:</p>
	<ul>
		<li>Locked Gates: the town gates cannot be opened if less than 40 players have joined the town.</li>
		<li>
			Soul Points: dying in a private town will only earn one third of the normal number of points.
		</li>
		<li>
			Distinctions: only a third of distinctions normally given will be awarded in private towns (the rest are lost).
			Rare distinctions cannot be earned in private towns.
		</li>
		<li>Last man standing: dying in a private town never earns the LMS distinction.</li>
		<li>
			Cancellation: a private town will be cancelled if it has not been filled within 2 days. Its creator will have any Hero days invested returned and any participating players will leave the town.
		</li>
		<li>Ranking: these towns will not be counted in the official rankings.</li>
	</ul>
	
	<h2>Reserved places</h2>
	<p>
		You can enter a list of 39 players (minimum) when you create a town, so that everyone has a place reserved.
		Each nickname must be spelt correctly and separated by a comma (spaces are ignored).
		Once the town has been created, the list can no longer be modified!
	</p>
	<p>Example: <em>player01, player02, thingy_from_chicago</em></p>
	<p>
		Attention! If a player's name is not down, they're not getting in.
		If too many players decide not to participate, your town will never start and will automatically be cancelled.
	</p>
	<p>therefore, it is strongly recommended to include <strong>more than 39 names</strong> to have some players in reserve.</p>
	
</h>

<h id="rp" title="Roleplay options" icon="item_dice" sub="1">
	<p>
		On the various forums and the World Beyond discussion board, you have access to the complete range of tools governing "atmosphere" and "role-play".
	</p>
	<p>
		You can type one of the following commands :
	</p>
	<ul class="rpHelp">
		<li><strong>[card]</strong>: displays the name of a random card drawn from a deck of 52,</li>
		<li><strong>[resident]</strong>: displays the name of a random resident of your town (this will not work if you have not yet joined a town),</li>
		<li><strong>[ht]</strong>: flip a coin (heads or tails),</li>
		<li><strong>[rps]</strong>: play rock, paper, scissors,</li>
		<li><strong>[d6]</strong>: throws a 6-sided dice and displays the result (also works with d4, d6, d8, d10, d12, d20 and d100).</li>
		<li><strong>[consonant]</strong> : draw a consonant,</li>
		<li><strong>[vowel]</strong> : draw a vowel,</li>
		<li><strong>[letter]</strong> : draw a letter by chance,</li>
		</ul>
	<p>
		Don't abuse these commands! Use them to invent new games for citizens to play and to resolve situations or disputes with a game of chance, etc...
	</p>
</h>

<h id="seasons" title="Seasons and Rankings" icon="small_coin" sub="1" mod="SEASON_RANKINGS">
	<img src="/gfx/screen/rankingScreenshot.png" alt="" class="art"/>
	<p>
		The game is split up into periods of approximately 3 months, called <strong>seasons</strong>.
	</p>
	<p>
		During this time, towns are ranked according a score which reflects their capacity to survive as a group. <strong>The score is calculated by adding together the total number of days survived in the town by all the citizens.</strong>
	</p>
	<p>
	<strong>Important :</strong> Only towns in Distant Regions
	[mod hardcore]
	or Hardcore towns
	[/mod]
	are ranked. Small maps or towns created for special events will not feature in the season's rankings.
	</p>
	<h2>End of the season</h2>
	<p>
		At the end of each season, the citizens from the best town from each level of the rankings will receive various rewards. The rankings are then reset to zero  in order to start a new period with everyone at the same level.
	</p>
	<ul>
		<li><strong>messages left on the forums by champions</strong> are displayed in a very distinctive manner <sup>1</sup>,</li>
		<li>they start every game with <strong>special additional equipment</strong> <sup>1</sup>,</li>
		<li>they also receive a unique, rare <strong>distinction</strong> and a corresponding <strong>title</strong></li>
	</ul>
	<p>
		<i>1: These rewards will be lost at the end of the following season, only reigning champions will benefit from these advantages.</i>
	</p>
	<p>
		Citizens that participated in a town that made it into the rankings also receive <strong>another special distinction</strong>
		(one for <strong>each</strong> town present in the rankings).
	</p>
	<h2>Soul Rankings</h2>
	<p>
		These rankings are not reset to zero at the end of the season: accordingly, there are no bonuses awarded.
	</p>
	<p>
		Starting from season 5, a soul ranking by season will be available, this allows you to see its value over the season.
	</p>	

	<h2>Further Rules</h2>
	<ul>
		<li>
			A town in Season 1 must be destroyed in Season 1 to be counted in the rankings. If it lasts into Season 2, it will not be counted in either ranking.</li>
		<li>The rankings are updated at 23h00 (server time).</li>
		<li>Only towns which are completely destroyed (no survivors) will receive a ranking.</li>
	</ul>

</h>


<!---
<h id="story" title="L'histoire" icon="item_faerie">

	<h2>Le Monde des Die2Nite</h2>
	<p>
	On ne sait pas exactement retracer le passé du monde des Hordes. Certes, on retrouve de temps à autres des vestiges, des ruines et des objets particuliers
	qui pourraient nous donner quelques indications... Mais nous n'avons pas le temps de rechercher une vérité sur une histoire qui à l'air pour le moins sombre...
	Ce qui est certain c'est que le Monde est vaste: il compte un grand nombre de villes où se regroupent des aventuriers suicidaires.
	</p>

	<h2>Les Villes</h2>
	<p>
	Les aventuriers du Monde des Hordes se retrouvent dans de petites communautés en autarcie: ce sont les villes. Chaque cité compte une bonne centaine de
	citoyens qui se partagent des tâches, votent des décisions et agissent de concert. Ces aventuriers ont un seul et même but: survivre à l'attaque de la Horde du soir.
	</p>

	<h2>La Horde</h2>
	<p>
	Tous les jours, en fin de soirée à la même heure les villes sont attaquées par des Hordes de Zombies! Les citoyens ont donc la journée
	pour se préparer à ces assauts.
	</p>

	<h2>L'Outre-Monde</h2>
	<p>
	Pour être fin prêts, les aventuriers vont devoir sortir de la ville, dans <strong>l'Outre-Monde</strong>, pour chercher des ressources vitales à la construction de défenses et de bâtiments en ville.
	Ils vont également rechercher des objets spéciaux qui leur permettront d'integrair avec l'environnement, de décorer leurs maisons, de se détendre... et de combattre!
	</p>

	<h2>Une fin inconnue...</h2>
	Après l'attaque des Hordes, les aventuriers survivants vont continuer à se serrer les coudes. Ceux qui ont péri... Se retrouveront dans le mondes des âmes,
	prêts à repartir dans une nouvelle ville, forts de leur expérience...

</h>
-->

<!--
<h id="adv" title="Règles avancées" >
	<p>Certains modes de jeu dans Hordes ont des règles particulières. Vous trouverez dans cette section des informations utiles à leur compréhension.</p>
</h>

<h id="faraway" title="Régions Eloignées" sub="1" icon="r_explor">
	<p>Les régions avancées sont des régions partculières unqiquement accessibles aux joueur</p>
</h>
-->

<h id="mobile" title="Die2Nite on your mobile (Anthrax GPS)">
	<img src="/gfx/art/iphone.jpg" alt="" class="art"/>
	<p>
		If you have a mobile (telephone, PDA...) which is compatible with modern web sites, you can sign in to Die2Nite via :
	</p>
	<p><a href="::url::/m">::url::/m</a></p>
	<p>
		You will have access to <strong>an optimised mobile version of Die2Nite</strong> (more specifically for Iphone and Ipod touch).
	</p>
	<p>
		This mobile version is <strong>free</strong> and allows you to follow discussions in the forums, keep an eye on the bank, see what is happening in your zone if you are outside, etc...
	</p>
</h>



<h id="st" title="Support">
	<p>
		If you encounter a problem in Die2Nite, please follow the instructions in the following sections (check your browser version, clear your cache, ...).
	</p>
</h>

<!--
	<p>
		Si vous avez des questions, des problèmes ou des suggestions à faire à l'équipe de Hordes, merci
		tout d'abord de prendre le temps de lire les différentes réponses proposées ci-dessous :
	</p>
	<dl class="faq">
		<dt>Hordes est-il gratuit?</dt>
		<dd>
			Oui, Die2Nite est un site gratuit. Vous pouvez si vous le désirez devenir un
			Héros pour bénéficier d'avantages importants en jeu.
		</dd>

		<dt>J'ai un problème et je n'ai rien trouvé d'utile ici!</dt>
		<dd>
			En cas de problème ou de suggestion, consultez la section
			Support Technique de cette même aide.
		</dd>

		<dt>J'ai validé des codes et/ou ma Carte Bleue et/ou Paypal mais je n'ai pas eu mes jours héros</dt>
		<dd>Si vous pensez avoir entré assez de codes (CB ou Paypal), allez dans votre fiche, dans la section réglages.
		Un lien spécial doit être affiché pour régler ce problème.</dd>

		<dt>Les bâtiments trouvés dans le désert, disparaissent-ils en cours de partie?</dt>
		<dd>Non, les bâtiments d'une carte ne disparaissent jamais et restent toujours à la même position.</dd>

		<dt>Le Puits peut-il être à sec?</dt>
		<dd>Oui, le Puits peut se retrouver à sec. Auquel cas il faudra trouver un autre moyen pour obtenir de l'eau.</dd>

		<dt>Peut-on remplir le Puits quand il est vide?</dt>
		<dd>Oui, l'une des techniques les plus efficaces consiste à construire un Purificateur puis à ramener des Jerrycans en ville.</dd>

		<dt>Les zombies se déplacent-ils en journée dans le désert?</dt>
		<dd>Non, les zombies restent à leur place. Ce n'est qu'après l'attaque de la Horde qu'ils se déplacent.</dd>

		<dt>Le nombre de zombies augmente-t-il pendant la journée?</dt>
		<dd>
			Non, le nombre de zombies n'augmente pas pendant la journée, uniquement après l'attaque de la Horde.
		</dd>

		<dt>Si je me déplace dans une zone où la carte ne m'indique pas de zombies, peut-il quand même y en avoir?</dt>
		<dd>Oui, si la zone n'a pas été visitée auparavant par un autre citoyen.</dd>

		<dt>L'attaque de la Horde est passée et je ne vois plus de zombies sur la carte, est-ce normal?</dt>
		<dd>
			Oui, il faut re-visiter chaque zone pour afficher à nouveau les zombies qui se trouvent dessus.
			Chaque citoyen qui visite une zone permet aux autres de voir ce qu'il y a dans cette zone.
		</dd>

		<dt>L'attaque de la Horde est passée et je vois toujours les bâtiments sur la carte est-ce normal?</dt>
		<dd>Oui, une fois indiqués, les emplacements des bâtiments sont toujours visibles sur la carte.</dd>

		<dt>Quelle est la différence entre le Forum Monde et le Forum Ville?</dt>
		<dd>
			Le Forum Monde est visible pour tous, à tout moment, mais seuls les citoyens Héros peuvent y poster des messages.
			Le Forum Ville est un forum qui n'est accessible que par les joueurs de la partie en cours.
		</dd>

		<dt>Si je suis déshydraté(e) est-ce que je regagnerai mes Points d'Action en buvant?</dt>
		<dd>Non. Par contre vous ne serez plus déshydraté(e).</dd>

		<dt>Les objets que j'ai posés dans l'Outre-Monde hier disparaissent-ils?</dt>
		<dd>Non, à moins qu'un autre joueur s'en empare.</dd>

		<dt>Que deviennent les zones de l'Outre-Monde trop fouillées?</dt>
		<dd>Ces zones ne peuvent plus donner que des ressources de mauvaise qualité et en faibles quantités qui plus est...</dd>

		<dt>Que deviennent les bâtiments de l'Outre-Monde vides (explorés au maximum)?</dt>
		<dd>Depuis quelques temps, on observe des phénomènes météorologiques étranges, la nuit... Ces vents violents mettent parfois à jour de nouvelles trouvailles dans des lieux réputés épuisés.</dd>

		<dt>Pourquoi n'y-a-t-il pas d'Héroïne?</dt>
		<dd>Parce qu'il y a d'autres drogues disponibles ;) En fait, pour simplifier à l'extrême les Héros sont unisexe, Femme ou Homme.</dd>

		<dt>Tuer un zombie réduit-il l'attaque du soir?</dt>
		<dd>Non.</dd>

		<dt>Où se trouve la fonction recherche dans le Forum?</dt>
		<dd>Il n'y en a pas, seuls les propos les plus pertinents et les discussions les plus importantes ont droit de cité sur le forum. Le reste ira rejoindre les abysses...</dd>

		<dt>Nous sommes moins de ::ChaosLimit:: joueurs survivants. Pourtant le chaos n'est pas déclenché: est-ce normal?</dt>
		<dd>Si la ville n'a pas tenu au moins ::BeginPeriodDays:: jours de survie, le chaos ne peut exister.</dd>

		<dt>Je suis le dernier à mourir mais je n'ai pas gagné de jours Héros!</dt>
		<dd>C'est normal si vous n'avez pas survécu au moins 6 jours.</dd>

		<dt>Je suis mort alors que je n'ai pas encore choisi mon métier!</dt>
		<dd>A partir du deuxième jour de la partie, si vous n'avez toujours pas choisi de métier, alors vous mourrez automatiquement.
			Dans tous les cas, pensez-vous pouvoir aider votre ville sans jouer??
		</dd>

	</dl>
-->


<h id="browser" title="1- Check my browser" sub="1" ::ignore::>
	<h2>Supported browsers</h2>
	<p>The game is 100% compatible with Mozilla Firefox 2+ and Internet Explorer&nbsp;7.</p>
	<p>We do not guarantee 100% functionality on other browsers such as Safari, Opera and previous versions of Firefox and Internet Explorer.</p>

	<h2>Clearing the cache</h2>
	<p>Before trying anything else, try <strong>clearing the cache</strong> on your internet browser! This simple operation can solve many technical problems.</p>
	<p><strong>Internet Explorer 7 :</strong></p>
	<ul>
		<li>On the Internet Explorer Tools menu, click Internet Options,</li>
		<li>On the General tab, in the Browsing history section, click the Delete... button. This will bring up the Delete Browsing History Box,</li>
		<li>Select the Delete files... button to delete Temporary Internet Files,</li>
		<li>Select the Delete cookies... button to delete Cookies,</li>
		<li>Select the Delete history... button to delete your browsing history,</li>
		<li>After you select delete a box will appear asking you to confirm you would like to delete the files. Select Yes for each one.</li>
		</ul>
	<p><strong>Internet Explorer 6 or previous :</strong></p>
	<ul>
		<li>On the Internet Explorer Tools menu, click Internet Options,</li>
		<li>On the General tab, in the Temporary Internet Files section, click the Delete Files button,</li>
		<li>Click OK, close Internet Explorer et reload the site.</li>
	</ul>
	<p><strong>Firefox 3 :</strong></p>
	<ul>
		<li>Press "Control" + "Shift" + "Del",</li>
		<li>In the Clear Private Data window that appears, uncheck all checkboxes except for the Cache checkbox</li>
		<li>Click OK, then click the Refresh button.</li>
	</ul>
	<p><strong>Firefox 2 or previous :</strong></p>
	<ul>
		<li>From the Firefox menu options, choose Tools and then Clear Private Data...,</li>
		<li>In the Clear Private Data window that appears, uncheck all checkboxes except for the Cache checkbox,</li>
		<li>Click on the Clear Private Data Now button,</li>
		<li>Click OK, then click the Refresh button.</li>
	</ul>
</h>



<h id="flash" title="2- Check my Flash player" sub="1">

	<h2>How do I install Flash?</h2>
	<p>
		<strong>The game requires a recent version of Flash (version 9 or higher).</strong>
	</p>
	<p>
		Adobe Flash Player is a free program which is used to display animations and Internet games. To install Flash Player, download it in a few seconds from here :
	</p>
	<p>
		<a target="_blank" href="http://get.adobe.com/flashplayer/">Install the latest version of Flash Player</a>
	</p>
	<p>
		if problems persist, you could try uninstalling and reinstalling Flash Player. To uninstall, follow the instructions <a ::ignore:: target="_blank" href="http://www.adobe.com/fr/support/flash/ts/documents/remove_player.htm"> here</a>.
	</p>

	<h2>Additional info for Linux users</h2>
	<p>
		The addition of an avatar doesn't work properly on some versions.
		Please update your player to resolve this problem :)
	</p>
	<p>
		Using Flash Player in Firefox can cause certain in-game elements to not function correctly.
	</p>
	<p>
		However, as the game was partially developed in Linux, we are doing all we can to ensure the gaming experience is <i>as similar as possible</i> .
	</p>
</h>


<h id="parasites" title="3- Check third-party applications" sub="1">
	<p>
		If you are using one of the following applications, please deactivate it to see if this fixes the problem :
	</p>
	<ul>
		<li>anti-spyware software,</li>
		<li>a firewall,</li>
		<li>anti-virus software.</li>
	</ul>
	<p>
		If this resolves the problem, please consult the documentation for the software in question or contact their technical support department to find a long-term solution for the problem.
	</p>
	<h2>Known issues with "Norton Internet Security"</h2>
	<p>
		This software has various issues and can cause browsing problems by blocking certain links for no apparent reason.
	</p>
	<p>
		<strong>We strongly recommend temporarily deactivating Norton Internet Security while playing Die2Nite.</strong>
	</p>

</h>


<h id="contact" title="Getting help" sub="1">
	<p>
		Consult the official technical support site for Die2Nite by clicking below :
	</p>
	<ul ::ignore::>
		<li>
			<strong>FAQ</strong>: consult the <a href="/support" target="_blank">official Die2Nite technical support site</a>!
		</li>
		<li>
			<strong>DISCUSS WITH OTHER PLAYERS</strong>: you will often find the answers to your questions directly on the <a href="/#saloon">site forums</a>, which are available as long as you are signed in.
		</li>
		<li>
			<strong>REPORT BEHAVIOUR</strong>: in the case of a problem relating to another player's <strong>behaviour</strong>, please read the section entitled <a href="/#help?id=report">I'm annoyed</a> in the help section below.
		</li>
		<li>
			<strong>PAYMENT PROBLEM</strong>: if you have a problem relating to <strong>payment</strong>, please proceed by clicking here&nbsp;: <a href="/support?go=rentabiliweb">payment methods and support</a>.
		</li>
		<li>
			<strong>REPORT A BUG</strong>: to report a bug, use the following discussion area: <a href="/support?go=hordes_bug" target="_blank">bug reports</a>,
		</li>
		<li>
			finally, for all questions relating to the<strong> Die2Nite community</strong>, you can <a href="/support?go=hordes_cm" target="_blank">contact Epoq</a> (link also available at the bottom of each webpage).
		</li>
	</ul>
</h>


<h id="pass" title="Choosing a good password" sub="1">
	<p>Die2Nite stand by the following rule: <strong>a good password is the best defence against theft from your account.</strong> Here are some more pieces of good advice :
	<ul>
		<li>Choose a good password without special characters</li>
		<li>Use a combination of letters, numbers, capitals and lower case characters</li>
		<li>Your password can consist of up to <strong>32 characters</strong></li>
		<li>If you're in doubt, check your password on <a href="http://www.microsoft.com/protect/yourself/password/checker.mspx" target="_blank">Microsoft Password Tester</a></li>
	</ul></p>
</h>

<h id="quarantine" title="Quarantined towns" sub="1">
	<p>
		<strong>In the event of an error occurring during the minight attack, the town is automatically placed in quarantine.</strong>
	</p>
	<p>
		This means:
	</p>
	<ul>
		<li>that the 23h00 (server time) attack did not take place,</li>
		<li>that you have not regained your <img src="/gfx/loc/::LANG::/small_pa.gif" alt=""/> and that your state of health has not changed,</li>
		<li>that yesterday has not been completed, and therefore continues on to today,</li>
		<li>etc...</li>
	</ul>
	<div class="critical">
		<p>
			As soon as the problem has been solved and everything has returned to normal, the quarantine will be lifted.
		</p>
		<p>
			<strong>The attack which didn't occur at 23h00 (server time) will take place the following night.</strong>
		</p>
		<p>
			Note: the town gates will be closed automatically before the delayed attack.
		</p>
	</div>
</h>



<h id="report" title="I'm annoyed!" sub="1" icon="small_calim">
	<div class="help">
		<img class="art artRight" src="/gfx/loc/::LANG::/report.png" alt=""/>
		<p>
			If a player of Die2Nite is being abusive on the forums (insults, off-topic posts...), you can report the message(s) they have posted.
			<strong>Simply click on the "(Report)" link which can be found next to the date of the forum in question.</strong>
		</p>
		<p>
			<strong>The crow will look into your request, and will take any action deemed necessary against the user.</strong>
		</p>
		<div class="clear"></div>
	</div>
	<p>
		The following actions should be reported:
	</p>
	<ul>
		<li>flooding (repetition of identical messages on the forum),</li>
		<li>posting anything contrary to the spirit of public order and decency</li>
		<li>posting anything of an abusive, defamatory, racist, xenophobic, homophobic or revisionist nature, or anything which could potentially harm the reputation of, or is disrespectful to a player,</li>
		<li>posts encouraging discrimination or hatred directed at an individual or group of people based on ethnicity, origin, sexual orientation, membership or non-membership of a specific ethnic group, nationality, race or religion,</li>
		<li>threatening an individual or group of people,</li>
		<li>posts concerning anything of a zoophile or paedophile nature,</li>
		<li>posts of a urological or scatological nature, any content of a generally degrading nature or which undermines a person's character or integrity,</li>
		<li>posts inciting the commission of an offence, crime, act of terrorism, or posts justifying or praising war crimes or crimes against humanity,</li>
		<li>directly or indirectly granting third party access to pirated software, software serial numbers, software or programs facilitating acts of piracy, granting access to telecommunications systems or information systems, viruses and logic bombs, software, tools or programs of any kind which undermine the rights of the individual or constitute a security risk to people or property and generally constituting a violation of the private nature of any communications.</li>
		<li>...</li>
	</ul>
	<p>This list is not exhaustive.</p>
</h>

<h id="sitting" title="About 'account-sitting'" sub="1" icon="small_warning">
	<div class="help">
		<p>Sitting is a practice which consists of lending your account to another player so that they can carry out your daily tasks in your stead.</p>
		<p><strong>This practice is forbidden on Die2Nite</strong> (and on the majority of Motion Twin sites).</p>
	</div>
	<h2>Why is sitting forbidden?</h2>
	<ul>
		<li>More than 90% of messages received by technical support relate to cases of account theft, which results from, in the <strong>vast majority</strong> of cases (yes, indeed) of account-sitting gone bad,</li>
		<li>even your friends can delete your account: everyone doesn't appreciate how important your account is to you. This is the most common case: account lent to a "friend", deleted by said "friend", huge emotional drama directed at technical support (which we can't deal with).</li>
	</ul>

	<h2>What risk do I run by participating in sitting?</h2>
	<ul>
		<li>the closure of your account by an administrator,</li>
		<li>the theft of your account by another player,</li>
		<li>exclusion of towns from the rankings: a town in which a player has engaged in sitting is automatically excluded at the end of the season.</li>
	</ul>
	<h2>Notes concerning exclusion from the rankings</h2>
	<p>
		The Die2Nite rankings reflect the capacity of a given town to organise itself and coordinate its efforts, despite restrictions and realities relating to the human condition.
		Sitting significantly changes the impact of this factor by reducing citizens to simple <i><img src="/gfx/loc/::LANG::/small_pa.gif" alt=""/>reserves</i>
		It is therefore logical that towns found to be abusing this system are not included in the rankings.
	</p>
	<p>
		We understand the disappointment felt by players whom, in good faith, participated in towns in which players were "sitting": However, as these towns benefitted from a significant organisational advantage, they are excluded from the rankings. That is the only consequence which will be felt by those playing in good faith.
	</p>
	<p>
		A player from one of the towns which has been excluded from the rankings will still be able to see the town on their soul page.
	</p>
	<p>
		If your town is excluded from the rankings <strong>and you were amongst those participating in the sitting</strong>, your account could be blocked by an administrator.
	</p>

	<h2>How do you detect sitting?</h2>
	<p>
		For obvious reasons of security, we cannot go into details of the procedure. However:
	</p>
	<ul>
		<li><strong>couples</strong> and <strong>families</strong> have nothing to fear from this system: our filters easily dismiss normal sharing of PCs and IP addresses.</li>
		<li>never lend your account to anyone and never connect to another player's account even if they ask you nicely (that's dangerous territory).</li>
		<li><strong>if you haven't done anything, you have nothing to worry about</strong>.</li>
	</ul>
</h>


<h id="extern" title="Use of external sites in Die2Nite" icon="small_archive">
	
	<p class="help">
		Die2Nite.com offers developers extra information in the form of JSON feeds which can be used for the creation of extra applications and other novel uses based on the game.
		<br/>
		<strong>It was previously possible to create applications from an XML feed, but this will no longer be maintained and consequently any new applications must be based on the JSON feed.</strong>
	</p>
	
	<p>
		You can find more information relating to the conception and function of Twinoid applications by heading over to this address: <a href="http://twinoid.com/developers/doc">http://twinoid.com/developers/doc</a>.
		<br/>
		When you develop an application, you need to base your work on the APIs that are made available through our game.
		To find out about all of the elements we give you acces to you can visit the following addresses:
		<ul>
			<li>For Twinoid: <a href="http://twinoid.com/developers/api">http://twinoid.com/developers/api</a></li>
			<li>For Die2Nite: <a href="/tid/api">http://die2nite.com/tid/api</a></li>
		</ul>
		
		Both of these services offer access to different information. You need to work out for yourself which service you need to get the right info.
		This is rather simple in fact, as each token will allow you to access either of the APIs feely.
		<br/>
		You can find a demo application here in order to test out the system with your own requests: <a href="http://data.motion-twin.com/demoTidApi/">http://data.motion-twin.com/demoTidApi/</a>.
	</p>



	<h2>Terms of use</h2>
	<ul>
		<li>
			<strong>Under no circumstances</strong> do you have the right to ask a Die2Nite user visiting your site for 	their password,
		</li>
		<li>
			you must clearly indicate that your site is in no way officially linked to Die2Nite.com,
		</li>
		<li>
			the design of your site cannot contribute to confusion or misunderstanding by letting visitors think that your site is a subsidiary of Die2Nite.com: the designs of both pages must be completely different.
		</li>
		<li>
			if you use images or other Die2Nite content, you must indicate their source, and indicate the applicable rights of the author / artist.
		</li>
	</ul>

</h>


</help>
