
<heroUpgrades>
	<up d="3" k="falsify" icon="small_falsify" name="Manipulator">
		Twice per game, you can delete an entry in the town register (click on the icon alongside the line you wish to delete...).
	</up>
	<up d="7" k="overview1" icon="small_view" name="Clairvoyance">
		You know how active and present a player is in the game, simply by going to their house.
	</up>
	<up d="16" k="mailAll" icon="item_rp_sheets" name="Mr Writer">
		Now you can send Private Messages to all the citizens in your town at once (from the Messages section in your House).
		You can also start "RP" threads in the forums (please do not abuse this !).
	</up>
	<up d="25" k="share" icon="r_share" name="Brothers in Arms">
		Once per game, you can give 1 Hero day to a fellow citizen ! Just wait, you'll become a veritable messiah for the masses... NB: any hero days you give away will be taken from your total, simply go to another citizen's page to give them a Hero day. Warning: When you donate a Hero day, it is only valid for THAT DAY. It cannot be saved for another time.
	</up>
	<!-- 1 mois -->
	<!--<up d="35" k="job_hunter" icon="item_todo" name="Métier : Ermite">
		Vous pouvez désormais adopter le métier d'Ermite dans vos villes à venir !
	</up>-->
	<!--
	<up d="35" k="job_tamer" icon="item_todo" name="Métier : Apprivoiseur">
		Vous pouvez désormais adopter le métier d'Apprivoiseur dans vos villes à venir !
	</up>-->
	<up d="31" k="writeCityBoard" icon="small_chat" name="Dictator">
		You can change what is written on the blackboard on the town's main page.
	</up>
	<up d="45" k="chest1" icon="item_home_box" name="Large Chested">
		You have earned an additional storage space in your personal chest, in your house.
	</up>
	<!-- 2 mois -->
	<up d="61" k="drugclean" icon="status_clean" name="Healthy Body">
		As long as you stay "Clean" (i.e. you haven't taken any drugs), you have 1 additional control point when you're in the World Beyond.
	</up>
	<up d="75" k="overview2" icon="small_view" name="Omniscience">
		Omniscience works like Clairvoyance, except you will be able to see the details of EVERY citizen from the town directory. Click on the Omniscience tab when looking at the list of citizens.
	</up>
	<!-- 3 mois -->
	<up d="91" k="tool" icon="item_chest_hero" name="Resourcefulness">
		You will start out in every town with a random useful object.
	</up>
	<up d="105" k="chest2" icon="item_home_box" name="False Bottom">
		You are given an additional storage compartment in your chest.
	</up>
	<!-- 4 mois -->
	<up d="121" k="powerSuperTools" icon="item_chest_hero" name="Lucky Find">
		Your hero power "Super Seeker" allows you to find much better objects.
	</up>
	<up d="135" k="bag" icon="item_bag" name="A place for everything">
		You have an additional storage compartment in your rucksack.
	</up>
	<!-- 5 mois -->
	<up d="151" k="powerActAgain" icon="small_pa" name="Second wind">
		Now you have an extremely useful power which allows you to restore your health to 6 AP and recover from a "tired" status.
	</up>
	<up d="165" k="food" icon="item_food_bag" name="Second Breakfast">
		You will start all towns with an additional ration of food.
	</up>
	<!-- 6 mois -->
	<up d="181" k="control" icon="item_shield" name="Brick S**thouse">
		Your wealth of experience in the World Beyond has given you a permanent addition of 1 control point .
	</up>
	<up d="195" k="falsify2" icon="small_falsify" name="Treachery">
		Your "Manipulator" is upgraded : you can now use it several times per game !
	</up>
	<!-- 7 mois -->
	<up d="211" k="powerTrance" icon="small_wrestle" name="Cheat death">
		When this is activated, this new power means you will no longer be affected by Thirst, Infection or Addiction during the next attack (only lasts for one night).
	</up>
	<!-- 8 mois -->
	<up d="241" k="revenge" icon="item_april_drug" name="Sweet Revenge">
		If you are shunned on day 3 or later, you will automatically receive some poison with which to exact your revenge... Yeah, they'd better not **** with you now !
	</up>
	<!-- 10 mois -->
	<up d="301" k="camper" icon="small_camp" name="Pro Camper">
		Penalties incurred by repeated camping in the World Beyond are reduced for you : therefore you can camp more often during your time in a town.
	</up>
		<!-- 12 mois -->
	<up d="361" k="disinfect" icon="item_disinfect" name="Preventative medicine">
		You start out in every town with a sachet of paracetamol in your rucksack.
	</up>
	<!-- 18 mois -->
	<up d="541" k="customMaps" icon="item_map" name="Mayor">
		You can create private towns by simply clicking "Play", when you are dead.
	</up>
	<!-- 24 mois -->
	<up d="721" k="architect" icon="item_bplan_c" name="Architect">
		You begin every town with a construction blueprint.
	</up>
	
	<up d="1000" k="guardian" icon="r_guard" name="Pro-Watchman">
		You increase your maximum chance of survival by 5% after watches. (Therefore the first night is a 100% increase).
	</up>
</heroUpgrades>
