<texts>
	<t id="assert">ASSERT</t>
	<t id="date_fmt">%A %d %B at %H:%M</t>
	<t id="date_fmt_std_short">%Y-%m-%d</t>
	<t id="date_fmt_std_full">%Y-%m-%d %h:%m</t>
	<t id="date_fmt_full">%A %d %B %Y at %H:%M</t>
	<t id="short_date_fmt">%d %B %Y</t>
	<t id="shorth_date_fmt">%d %B %Hh%M</t>
	<t id="date_fmt_yd">%d.%m</t>
	<t id="locale1">en_US.UTF-8</t>
	<t id="locale2">EN</t>
	
	<t id="CountryRestriction"></t> <!-- exemple: FR,DE,AT,BE -->
	<t id="CountryBypass">traceface,Butch,epoqdev,mtfriends,iblis</t><!-- Liste de pseudos à autoriser à la connexion / inscription. Exemple: "kevin69,mike,zombiekiller" -->
	<t id="BankLangs">fr,be,ca,ch,lu</t>
	<t id="admins_list">warp:yota:skool:deepnight:bumdum:irvie:_hk_:mrhk:hiko:ayame:Yukit0:Epoq</t>
	<t id="OfflineHelpUrl">free_zombie_game</t>
	<t id="OfflineAboutUrl">zombie_survival_game_info</t>
	
	<!-- GENERAL -->

	<t id="err_unknown_action">Unknown Action (::act::)</t>
	<t id="err_already_logged">You are already logged in to the site</t>
	<t id="err_must_login">You must be logged in to do this</t>
	<t id="err_user_deleted">This user has been blocked by an administrator, please consult the site rules</t>
	<t id="err_upload">An error occurred during file transfer.</t>
	
	<t id="Forum_Saloon">Saloon</t>
	<t id="Forum_Discuss">Discussions</t>
	<t id="Forum_Help">Help</t>
	<t id="Forum_Hero">Heroes</t>
	
	<t id="UserWarnedBecauseInactive">You were inactive during this game, and as such penalized the other players in your town. We warn you that if you do this again, you won't be able to join another town for 4 days.</t>
	<t id="UserLockedBecauseInactive">You were inactive during this game, and as such penalized the other players in your town. You can't join another town for 4 days.</t>
	<t id="CantJoinGameUserLocked">You cannot join a game, You have been blocked for 4 days following your inactivity in your last game.</t>
	
	<!-- TWINOID -->
	
	<t id="twinoid_wall_death_short">has put an end to their miserable existence after only one day spent in *::city::* : «*::reason::*»</t>
	
	<t id="twinoid_wall_death_1">has put an end to their pitiful existence after spending only *::days::* days in *::city::* : «*::reason::*»</t>
	<t id="twinoid_wall_death_2">finally found peace after *::days::* days spent in the living hell known as *::city::* : «*::reason::*»</t>
	<t id="twinoid_wall_death_3">has left the living nightmare called *::city::* having survived there for *::days::* days amongst the zombies and all manner of treachery: «*::reason::*»</t>
	<t id="twinoid_wall_death_4">has died following attrocious suffering: «*::reason::*». That must just be the price to pay for surviving *::days::* days in *::city::*.</t>
	<t id="twinoid_wall_death_5">, a citizen of *::city::* is proud to announce that they died after *::days::* days. «*::reason::*» was much more pleasant that previously thought!</t>
	
	<t id="twinoid_wall_cadaver_msg">left the following message before they died: « ::msg:: » </t>
	

	<!-- USER/ACCOUNT -->
	<t id="err_account_pass">The password entered is invalid</t>
	<t id="err_account_email">The email address you entered is invalid</t>
	<t id="err_account_badpass">The new password is invalid. It must consist of between 4 and 12 characters.</t>
	<t id="err_account_confirm">Your request could not be confirmed.</t>
	<t id="err_account_reset_today">You can only reset your account once per day, please try again tomorrow.</t>
	<t id="account_reseted">Your account has bee reset</t>
	<t id="email_changed">Your email address has been updated</t>
	<t id="password_changed">Your password has been changed</t>
	<t id="err_user_not_found">User not found</t>
	<t id="err_cant_send_email">This user has either not provided an email address or deactivated password reminders</t>
	<t id="password_sent">Your password has been sent to the following email address: ::email::</t>
	<t id="err_pass_sent_today">Your password has already been sent today. If you haven't received it, please wait or check your "spam" folder.</t>
	<t id="subscribe_done">Registration complete! You can now log in to the site.</t>
	<t id="mail_disabled">This email address has been disabled</t>
	<t id="account_settings">You have modified your account settings.</t>
	

	<t id="RankingSeasons">0:Armageddon,1:Hang 'em High,2:Rise of the Labradoodle,3:A Chemical Necromancy,4:Going Underground,5:Shamanic Monday,6:Ghoul and the Gang,7:Along the Watchtower,8:Sleight of Hand,9:La Villa Nostra,10:Dev's Not Dead,11:Save our souls,12:Demonocracy,13:Enter the Sandman</t>
	<t id="UnknownSeason">Mysterious season</t>

	<t id="RegCrit_Crime">Thefts and Violence</t>
	<t id="RegCrit_Bank">Bank</t>
	<t id="RegCrit_Dump">Garbage Dump</t>
	<t id="RegCrit_Vote">Constructions</t>
	<t id="RegCrit_Refine">Workshop</t>
	<t id="RegCrit_Well">Well</t>
	<t id="RegCrit_Door">Gates</t>
	<t id="RegCrit_Dead">Arrivals and Deaths</t>
	<t id="RegCrit_Attack">The Attack of the Horde</t>

	<t id="unknownHelpTopic">Unknown Help Topic</t>
	<t id="H_MaxLevelReached">Maximum upgrade level of the *::n::* has been reached! </t>
	<t id="H_UpgradeDone">Evolution of the *::n::* has successfully reached *level ::l::*! </t>
	<t id="H_NotEnoughPA">This isn't possible: you *need ::pa:: AP*.</t>
	<t id="H_NotEnoughReqs">This isn't possible: you *need some more objects*.</t>
	<t id="H_UnknownUpgrade">This upgrade is not available!</t>
	<t id="HomeUpgradeLimit">You cannot upgrade your house any further without building the ::b:: in town.</t>

	<t id="TAMTAM_AFriendOf">A friend of </t>
	<t id="TAMTAM_Invitation">Invitation to Die2Nite.com</t>
	<t id="TAMTAM_InvitationSent">Your invitation has been sent!</t>

	<t id="guard_city">You have decided to put yourself in harm's way to protect the other townsfolk... highly commendable, citizen!</t>
	<t id="unguard_city">So, you've decided to abandon ship? Well, that's your call...</t>

	<!-- EVENTS -->
	<t id="EasterCross">Chocolate Cross</t>
	<!-- TEAM -->
	<t id="OneMIDPlease">Other players from your coalition are already playing from this computer. Only one player / computer / coalition is permitted.</t>
	<t id="SimilarAccount">You cannot join this coalition *because one or more accounts in the coalition have been deemed suspect in conjuction with your own*. ~This is generally down to one of the following things: <ul><li>This means that accounts involved in the coalition have been detected as potentially being *multiple accounts*,</li><li>You have been logged in to one of the other members accounts on several occasions (*sitting*)</li></ul>~</t>
	<t id="NoGameFound">There are no towns available for you at the moment. However, new towns are generally discovered *every few minutes*. ~Please try again shortly.~</t>
	<t id="GameNotAllowed">You cannot join this town. ~Either you have not acquired sufficient experience points, or the village has since reached maximum capacity.~</t>
	<t id="GameNeedXp">You have *insufficient soul points* to join this town!</t>
	<t id="GameOnlyForNoobs">Your soul score is *too high* to join this town.</t>
	<t id="GameHasTooManyVolunteers">*You cannot choose to join this town.* ~It has already reached its quote of volunteers. Only luck of the draw can land you a place there now.~</t>
	<t id="GameHasTooManyVolunteersForTeam">*You cannot choose to join this town with your coalition.* ~*Were you to join with your coalition, the quota of volunteers would be surpassed*. ~If you wish to join this town *alone*, go to your coalition page and change your status to "*unavailable*".~</t>
	<t id="NoGameAvailableForTeam">There are no towns available for you at the moment. ~All towns currently open have reached their quota of "coalition citizens".~ ~Please wait a few minutes until a new town becomes available.~</t>
	<t id="GameHasNoRoomForTeam">*This town doesn't have enough space for you and your coalition.* ~If you wish to join this town *alone*, go to your coalition page and change your status to "*unavailable*".~</t>
	<t id="GameRequiresInvit">~You cannot join this town *because your name isn't on the authorized list*.</t>
	<t id="DebtForbidden">This action is impossible *as your account is overdrawn on Hero days*.~Go to the *Buy Hero days* to remedy the situation.~</t>
	<t id="GameNeedPassword">The *password* entered for this town is *incorrect*.</t>
	<t id="GameNotOpenedYet">This town is not yet available for joining.</t>
	<t id="GameUnknown">This game does not exist. Please choose another.</t>
	<t id="BuddyJoinedGame">::u::* has just joined ::m::! *</t>
	<t id="AutoJoinOff">::u::* has not joined ::m::. They will have a think about it...* </t>
	<t id="PlaysSolo">::u::* is playing solo on ::m::.* </t>
	<t id="TeamStandardName">The Coalition of ::n::</t>
	<t id="alreadyInATeam">You have already joined the coalition of ::n::</t>
	<t id="alreadyHaveAnInvit">This citizen already has a pending invitation to join your coalition.</t>
	<t id="playerAlreadyInATeam">Sorry, ::n:: has already joined a coalition.</t>
	<t id="teamCreated">Congratulations, you have successfully created a coalition! </t>
	<t id="teamDeleted">You have just dissolved your coalition.</t>
	<t id="leaveTeamDeleted">By leaving, you have just dissolved your coalition.</t>
	<t id="notTeamOwner">Sorry, but to dissolve a coalition you must already have created or be the leader of one...</t>
	<t id="noTeam">First of all, you must create *create your own coalition* to do this.</t>
	<t id="TeamDoesNotExist">Sorry, but this coalition no longer exists.</t>
	<t id="InvitationDoesNotExist">Sorry, but this invitation has since been revoked.</t>
	<t id="TeamFull">Sorry, this team is now full</t>
	<t id="teamJoined">Congratulations, you have joined a coalition! </t>
	<t id="teamLeft">You have left the coalition.</t>
	<t id="ejectedFromteam">You have successfully ejected your former teammate! </t>
	<t id="invitationRejected">You have successfully rejected the invitation! </t>
	<t id="invitationCanceled">The invitation has been cancelled! </t>
	<t id="TeamSpeech">::name:: *:* « ::msg:: »</t>
	<t id="LeaveTeamSpeech">::name:: *has just left the coalition*</t>
	<t id="JoinTeamSpeech">::name:: *has just joined coalition! *</t>
	<t id="KickTeamSpeech">::name:: *has just been kicked out of the coalition! *</t>
	<t id="InviteTeamSpeech">::name:: has invited ::target:: to join us.</t>
	<t id="CancelInvitTeamSpeech">::name:: has *cancelled* ::target::'s invitation! </t>

	<!-- BANK -->
	<t id="bank_sync_done">Synchronisation complete</t>
	<t id="bank_ecode_error">One or more errors have been encountered during the validation process. Please check the details and try again</t>
	<t id="bank_ecode_bad_chars">The code '::code::' contains invalid characters. Please correct the details and try again</t>
	<t id="bank_eservice">The service is currently unavailable, please keep a note of your code '::code::' and try again later</t>
	<t id="bank_eprotocol">A protocol error has occurred, please keep a note of your code '::code::' and try again later</t>
	<t id="bank_credit_done">Your code has been accepted. You are now a Hero! !! </t>
	<t id="bank_etransaction">The electronic payment system is currently unavailable, please try again later</t>
	<t id="bank_cb_done">Your purchase was successful, ::money:: has been credited to your account</t>
	<t id="bank_cb_notenough">You have not entered enough codes to become a **Hero**.</t>
	<t id="ChooseAJobBeforeYouBuy">Before you continue, please *Select "Resident" as your citizen's occupation". *Once you have completed your transaction* you will become a Hero and will be able to *select an advanced profession*</t>
	<t id="MT_Terrorized">Terrorised!!</t>
	<t id="M_Terrorized">OK. We've got good news and bad news. The good news is that despite the best efforts of ::z:: zombies to devour you, you got through it! The bad news is that the experience really shook you up, so you are now terrorised by the idea of having to go through that again...</t>
	<t id="MT_TerrorDodged">A frightful night!</t>
	<t id="M_TerrorDodged">You were really sweating last night! You heard them groaning, banging around and yelling outside. Eventually your door gave way and you took refuge under your bed, clutching your remaining possessions, trying not to think about the situation. Then they left... Shaking with fear you eventually came out of your hiding place, grateful that you survived.</t>

	<t id="MT_Wounded">Wounded!!</t>
	<t id="M_Wounded">Once again, we have good and bad news for you. The good is that you managed to stop ::z:: zombies! The bad is that you got hurt...</t>
	<t id="MT_Complaint">Anonymous complaint (::n:: in total)</t>
	<t id="M_Complaint">You have received a new anonymous complaint: « ::msg:: ».</t>
	<t id="MT_ComplaintRemoved">Complaint Withdrawn (::n:: remaining)</t>
	<t id="M_ComplaintRemoved">Good news! The following complaint has been removed: « ::msg:: ».</t>
	<t id="MT_Banned">You have been shunned!</t>
	<t id="M_Banned">Too many complaints have been registered against you, so you have been shunned by the community.</t>
	<t id="M_BannedRecycle">Too many complaints have been registered against you, so you have been shunned by the community. The following objects have been taken from your inventory: ::tools::.</t>
	<t id="MT_Aggression">::u:: attacked you!</t>
	<t id="M_Aggression">While you were chilling at home, minding your own business, ::u:: came to visit you, pushed you around a bit then set about you! You defended well, young padawan, and returned the favour... Nothing broken. ~The other citizens have been informed.~</t>
	<t id="MT_AggressionWounded">You have been attacked and wounded by ::u::!!</t>
	<t id="M_AggressionWounded">While you were chilling at home, minding your own business, ::u:: came to visit you, pushed you around a bit then set about you! You defended well, but they threw you about like an empty tracksuit. *You have been injured as a result of this confrontation*! ~The other citizens have been informed.~</t>
	<t id="MT_Warning">Warning! </t>
	<t id="M_Warning">*This message has been sent to you because you have received a warning.* ~To know the reason for this warning, please go to your soul page.~ </t>
	<t id="M_WarningComportment">*This message has been sent to you because you have received a warning. * ~You are required to be polite in all exchanges with other players of Die2Nite, be they: on the forum, via private message, last words or as introduction...~ ~Any subsequent breach of these rules could result in your account being closed without warning.~</t>
	<t id="M_WarningSitting">*This message has been sent to you because you have received a warning. * ~Accounts cannot be loaned, exchanged or monitored by others. Please change your password IMMEDIATELY and do not share it with anyone.~<div class="lastWarning">Please note that this message consitutes a first and last warning: any further infringements will result in the deletion of your account.</div>~If you believe this message has been sent in error, you can contact Die2Nite technical support, and report an "account problem".~</t>
	<t id="M_WarningRetrieved">Technical support have restored your account. ~*Change your password immediately* and *add your email address* on your settings page! ~ ~Also change your *e-mail password* immediately.~ ~Please read the following page for more good advice on how to maintain your account :~ ~http://support.motion-twin.com/go/security~</t>
	<t id="M_RefererReward">Congratulations citizen! You have received a *rare distinction* thanks to one of the players you brought to the game bought Hero days for the first time! ~Go to the Sponsor area on your Soul page for more information...~</t>
	<t id="M_CreditedHero">Technical support have added one or more Hero days as compensation for *a bug found in the game*.</t>
	<t id="M_WarningSupport">Your help request is awaiting a response from the *Die2Nite technical support team*: please log in (using the link *at the bottom of the page*).</t>
	<t id="M_Multi">*This message has been sent to you because you have received a warning.* ~Multiple accounts belonging to you have been deleted. We remind you that multiple accounts are strictly forbidden on Die2Nite, in accordance with article 2 of the terms and conditions which you agreed to upon registration.~ ~Any future breaches will result in the permanent closure of your accounts, including this one.~</t>
	<t id="MT_ForumBan">Access to the forums has been suspended</t>
	<t id="M_ForumBan">Access to the Die2Nite forums through your account has been temporarily suspended! ~ ~To know more about your ban, please consult your *soul page*.~ *Repeated offences could result in more serious action being taken (permanent ban, account closure, legal action...)!*</t>
	<t id="M_BuildingsRefund">*All the buildings in your town have been refunded*. The *resources* which were used have been replaced in the bank, the *AP* which were invested have been placed in a communal reserve for all town members to use (can only be used on construction projects) and you have been given a *temporary defensive bonus*.</t>
	<t id="ThreadClosed">This discussion cannot continue. *End of discussion* You will all die tonight! Mwahahahahahah! </t>
	<t id="ThreadBugClosed">*Problem resolved! We apologise for any inconvenience caused!*</t>
	<t id="MT_Alarm">Alarm (::user::)! </t>
	<t id="M_Alarm">::user:: set off your alarm trying to break in to your house at precisely *::time::*! </t>
	<t id="MT_NewCatapMaster">You are in charge of the catapult! </t>
	<t id="M_NewCatapMaster">~You have been designated *Citizen in charge of the Town Catapult*! This nomination was down to the luck of the draw, congratulations! ~ ~Go to the Catapult area of the town.~</t>
	<t id="ThreadMoved">This thread *has been moved* to the appropriate forum! </t>

	<t id="GuardCannotLeave">You are the watchman! As such, you cannot leave the town! </t>
	<t id="HeroComplaint">::n:: (A Hero) has registered a second complaint against you.</t>
	<t id="RecyclingAlreadyDone">The recycling has already been done.</t>
	<t id="RescuedByAHero">A Hero has rescued you from the World Beyond! </t>
	<t id="UserVanished">The citizen you wanted to save has managed to get out of there, no doubt in a less than heroic fashion...</t>
	<t id="UnkownHeroItem">This object must be one of the ones that's on the "Heroes Only" list...</t>
	<t id="OutsideHeroAction">This heroic action can only be performed when you are in the *World Beyond*.</t>
	<t id="IntownHeroAction">This heroic action can only be performed when you are in town.</t>
	<t id="HeroRescueSuccess">Summoning up all your strength and will, you faced the World Beyond, saved ::s:: and returned unscathed! </t>
	<t id="HeroTeleported">Nobody knows how, but the *Hero ::name::* managed to get out of this zone and go *back to the town*... it's a miracle! </t>
	<t id="HeroUsedTownPortal">You used every ounce of energy to drag your ragged ass *back to the town* (we don't know how), and even made it back in one piece...  *It's incredible*! </t>
	<t id="TownPortalLimit">You are currently *too far from the town to use this power*! You are ::n:: km away, and the maximum distance is ::max::km.</t>
	<t id="HeroAlreadyUsedTownPortal">Ahh, going back to town is so convenient... Alas, despite your best efforts, your powers are weak. Try in another lifetime...</t>
	<t id="HeroUsedActAgain">You take a deep breath and shake your head. Come on! This is no time to give up! ~Your ::pa::AP *have been restored*.~</t>
	<t id="HeroUsedTrance">You try to pull yourself together for the evening ahead. The tension is written across your face, you are sweating, shaking...~You will not give in to the effects of thirst, infection, or addiction during tonight's attack.~</t>
	<t id="HeroLuck">Looks like *you're in luck*... You have found ::o:: in the sand! Exactly what you were looking for! </t>
	<t id="HeroLuckInTown">Looks like *you're in luck*... You have found ::o:: in a pile of rubbish near your house! Exactly what you were looking for! </t>
	<t id="HeroAlreadyUsedRescue">You have already tried to save one of your fellow citizens! You'll have to wait for your next life to be THE Hero though! </t>
	<t id="HeroAlreadyBeenLucky">You have already been lucky today. You'll have to wait for your next life to shape your destiny...</t>
	<t id="HeroAlreadyKilledAZombie">Ahh... Do you want some? You'll just have to wait for your next life to get in the ring champ...</t>
	<t id="HeroTired">You've played at being a Hero enough *for one day*! See you tomorrow for more Hero action! </t>
	<t id="BuildingUnknown">The building you voted for doesn't exist...</t>
	<t id="UnknownBuilding">The building you voted for doesn't exist...</t>
	
	<t id="RecommendedBuilding">You have recommended this building to your fellow citizens.</t>
	<t id="CantRecommendBuilding">You cannot recommend this building.</t>
	
	<t id="AlreadyDone">You have already done this once today... You must wait until tomorrow to do it again.</t>
	<t id="AlreadyDoneCounted">You have already done this today (max: *::n:: times per day*)... You must wait until tomorrow to do it again.</t>
	<t id="AlreadyDoneZone">It is not possible to carry out this action again here. Go somewhere else, or come back tomorrow.</t>
	<t id="HeroKillsZombies">Using your Heroic powers, you have exterminated *::n:: zombie(s)*! </t>
	<t id="HeroKilledZombies">Using their Heroic powers, ::u:: has exterminated* ::n:: zombie(s)* with their bare hands, screaming like a banshee! </t>
	<t id="NoZombiesToKill">There ain't no more zombies to kill round here, hoss...</t>
	<t id="NowYouWishedYouWereAHero">These amazing skills are reserved for *Heroes*... It's a shame, they'd be really useful to you right about now :)</t>
	<t id="WoundedEye">You don't see quite so good since that zombie scratched your eyeball, do you? *Blood in your eyes* is stopping you from reading your *map*...</t>
	<t id="WoundedArm">Your horrific *arm wound* is stopping you from doing that! </t>
	<t id="WoundedItemBlocked">It is impossible for you to use the ::tool:: with your *wounded hand*! You must get help or get healed...</t>
	<t id="WoundedFalls">You start to walk, but a sharp pain shoots up your leg. You fall to the ground whimpering. <strong>You lose an action point...</strong></t>
	<t id="WoundedGetsDizzy">Your head starts to spin. You fall to the ground and stay there for a few seconds, before regaining consciousness. <strong>You lose an action point......</strong></t>
	<t id="WoundedMessageTitle">Head... Huurrt... caaant... spea...</t>
	<t id="WoundedCannotSpeak">You have a head injury. Any suggestions or statements you have may not be understood by your fellow citizens...</t>
	<t id="ChaosNoBan">Your complaint has been registered but it's *not going to make much difference* given the current situation.</t>
	<t id="Chaos">the town has descended into complete and utter *chaos*... Given the feeble number of survivors, *laws are no longer respected* in town.</t>
	<t id="AlreadyDigged">You cannot explore this building again today. Wait until tomorrow.</t>
	<t id="RepairKitNeeded">You cannot carry out a repair without a repair kit.</t>
	<t id="CannotTakeThisObject">You *cannot* take this object.~You can only carry one bulky object and one container at any given time.~</t>
	<t id="NoMoreRoomInBag">You cannot take this object, as your rucksack is full.</t>
	<t id="ItemNoMoreInBank">This object has since been collected by another player.</t>
	<t id="JerrycanUsed">You have transferred the water from the ::cont:: to the town purifier. After treatment, *::n:: litres of clean water* were added to the well.</t>
	<t id="NeedJerrycan">You need a *Jerrycan*.</t>
	<t id="WaterPurifierUsed">You used the ::tool:: to purify the water in the ::target::. You obtained *::n:: litre(s) of water*...</t>
	<t id="Refined">After some DIY (thumb hammering, sweating, and colorful language), you have obtained a ::ref:: (the object has been placed in the bank).</t>
	<t id="WaterPurified">Thanks to the *Purifier*, ::n:: additional rations of water have been added to the well!</t>
	<t id="WaterPurifiedSingle">Thanks to the *Purifier*, 1 additional ration of water has been added to the well!!</t>
	<t id="NoMorePet">The butcher took great care of ::name::... You now have ::rep:: (*x::n::*). Goodbye dear friend.</t>
	<t id="And"> and </t>
	<t id="Or"> or </t>
	<t id="NeedToBeFar">You have to be more than ::n:: kilometers from the town to do that.</t>
	<t id="NeedInChest">You need to put *::n::* x ::t:: *in your chest*, to do that.</t>
	<t id="ItemNotFound">In the time it took you to make your mind up, someone else has taken the object first! </t>
	<t id="TheftChristmas">Thanks to your *costume*, you managed to steal the ::tool:: from ::name:: *without being seen*. ~Ho ho ho.~</t>
	<t id="TheftLeprechaun">Thanks to your *costume*, you managed to swipe the ::tool:: from ::name:: *and nobody saw a thing*. ~Top o' the mornin' to ye!.~</t>
	<t id="TheftUnseen">You have stolen the ::tool:: from ::name:: *without anyone noticing*. Damn! You've got skills...</t>
	<t id="TheftDetected">The robbery you've just carried *has been detected*! The citizens have been warned that you stole that ::tool:: from ::name::.</t>
	<t id="Plundered">You got the ::tool::. Nonetheless, your little visit to ::name::'s house didn't go unnoticed...</t>
	<t id="NoRoom">It is *impossible* to *take this object* (insufficient space, bulky object, etc...)</t>
	<t id="InChest">This object has been placed *in your chest*.</t>
	<t id="NoRoomCount">You need *::n:: free spaces* in your rucksack! </t>
	<t id="AlreadyStolen">Another citizen got in there and stole that object first...</t>
	<t id="SendStealProtection1">You cannot rob a citizen *if you have sent them an object today* (anti-abuse message).</t>
	<t id="SendStealProtection2">You cannot rob anyone else because *you have sent enough objects for one day*.</t>
	<t id="AlreadyStolenToday">Another citizen was quicker than you to pillage that object...</t>
	<t id="CantGiveBrokenToTown">You can't put a *broken object* in the *bank*!</t>
	<t id="BankLocked">You cannot *take an object of this type* from the bank for *::h:: hours* (resources are protected until the attack).</t>
	<t id="BigDoorLock">The Piston-Lock system has locked the gates for the night...</t>
	<t id="BasicDoorLock">*The gates are locked*, it is impossible to open them at the moment! </t>
	<t id="DoorClosed">The town gates have been *closed*.</t>
	<t id="DoorAlreadyClosed">The town gates have been closed by another consciencious citizen.</t>
	<t id="DoorLockQuarantine">It is impossible to open the town gates during a quarantine period! </t>
	<t id="DoorLockCustomMap">It is impossible to open the gates of a *private town* if there are *less than 40 citizens registered*.</t>
	
	<t id="UnlockedYourCustomMap">You have just opened your private town to everyone.</t>
	
	<t id="JobChoiceNeeded">You must choose a profession!</t>
	<t id="UnknownError">Unknown error (::t::)</t>
	<t id="Forbidden">Error: *forbidden action*.</t>
	<t id="ForbiddenToNoob">You cannot do this in rookie mode. Basically, *this action requires you to have greater experience of the game*. ~You can deactivate rookie mode by clicking the link in the info box.~</t>
	<t id="ForbiddenChaos">It is impossible to do this in times of *chaos*! </t>
	<t id="ForbiddenWhenCamping">It is impossible to do this *while you are hidden*! </t>
	<t id="ReservedToWinners">This action is reserved for *winners from the previous season*.</t>
	<t id="UploadError">An error has occurred during file transfer.</t>
	<t id="ThreadDefaultBeggining">Everyone has to start somewhere... Talk and listen up... </t>
	<t id="outside">The World Beyond</t>
	<t id="well">The Well</t>
	<t id="door">The Town Gates</t>
	<t id="anpe">Job Centre</t>
	<t id="MissingThreadTitle">Well that's no good at all! At least put a valid title (at least 6 letters, but no more than 32), ok? </t>
	<t id="UserNameNotFound">We don't know who you mean, please try again.</t>
	<t id="EmptyThread">Eh ben c'est tout ce que vous avez à dire là? Va falloir être un peu plus loquace, sinon on va pas s'en sortir! </t>
	<t id="ImpossibleAction">This action is not possible...</t>
	<t id="UnknownGameMode">This game mode is unknown, please choose another mode</t>
	<t id="OneCitizen">one citizen</t>
	<t id="Aggression">You violently attacked ::target::! </t>
	<t id="AggressionWounded">You violently attacked ::target::! The fight degenerated rapidly and resulted in you *seriously wounding the other citizen*!</t>
	<t id="CantAgressWounded">You can't seriously want to attack someone who is already injured... can you?</t>
	<t id="AggressionGhoul">Unexpectedly, ::name:: collapsed with a ungodly gurgle, their eyes rolling back in their head... *Their body is literally decomposing in places and the smell of death fills the air! * The horrible truth slaps you in the face: <strong>::name:: was a ghoul</strong>! ! </t>
	<t id="NoGhoulNoAggression">Steady on there, by all accounts there are *no ghouls in town*, so there's no need to go smacking people. Mmkay pumpkin?</t>
	<t id="CantEatGhoul">You cannot attack this citizen... They seem to smell different to the others. Just a minute... *They're a ghoul, like you!*</t>
	<t id="EventLogged">The citizens have all been told...</t>
	<t id="NapSuccess">You rest for a few minutes. *Even a short break like that made you feel much better! * ~You have regained *::n:: AP*! ~</t>
	<t id="NapFailed">You rest for a few minutes.... Unfortunately, you don't even manage to close your eyes. You think too much about tonight, about dying and about your feeble chance of survival...</t>
	<t id="NeedFood">You need *basic ingredients* in your *chest*.</t>
	<t id="Cooked">You use ::t:: and a few other bits and pieces. ~You put every effort into it. Then, after some time passes, you retrieve a ::dish:: from the "stove".~</t>
	<t id="CookedDrugSuccess">You grind the contents of ::n:: x ::t:: on the table and mix it with anything and everything that comes to hand... then let it infuse. ~It's a *roaring success*: you have obtained ::result::! ~</t>
	<t id="CookedDrugFailed">You grind the contents of ::n:: x ::t:: on the table and mix it with anything and everything that comes to hand... then let it infuse. ~The dodgy smoke pouring out of the mixture hints that *everything may not have gone exactly as planned* You have obtained a random drug: ::result::.~</t>
	<t id="UsedArmageddon">You charge, screaming, at the first zombie you see. With a solid, well-aimed shoulder charge, you leave them sprawled on the ground several metres away*... ~You could take advantage of this situation to get the hell out of there! ~</t>
	<t id="UsedContamination">You can say you've been lucky... Used to be a victom of the Total Contamination have ~saved you~ this time. *You have just avoided a terrible infection*.</t>
	<t id="UsedArmageddonFailed">You head for a zombie, but at the same time, they make a lunge for your face and only narrowly miss... You'll need to stay where you are for now...</t>
	<t id="UsedContaminationFailed">Being part of the Total Contamination victim didn't help this time... and that infection hurts...</t>
	<t id="ChoosedLevel">You have unlocked the title of "*::level::*".~It will appear near your name in all of your forum messages! ~</t>
	<t id="GotFromIphone">You manage to recover the ::tool:: from the smoking remains of the handset</t>
	<t id="UsedSmokeBomb">You throw your smoke bomb into the area, causing mass confusion!~Your *next move* will not be recorded in the register if carried out *in the next 60 seconds*.~</t>
	<t id="TooEarlyToUse">You cannot do this before *day ::n::*.</t>
	<t id="CustMapInvalidPass">The access code is invalid (between *6 and 16 characters*, consisting of *letters AND numbers*). It must also be *different from your personal password*.</t>
	<t id="CustMapCreated">You have started a private town! ~Name: *::name::*~~Access code: *::pass::*~</t>
	<t id="CustMapCancelled">Your private town has been *cancelled* because it could not be completely filled before the attack.</t>
	<t id="CustMapInvalidInvit">The username *::u::* is invalid.</t>
	<t id="CustMapInvalidInvitSelf">You cannot invite yourself.</t>
	<t id="CustMapNotEnoughInvit">Your invitation list must contain a minimum of *39 names*. It currently contains ::n::.</t>
	<t id="CustMapNeedInfo">You must enter a list of invited citizens or a valid password.</t>
	<t id="CustMapInvitMsg">You have received *an invitation* to join a private town called "*::map::*".</t>
	
	<!-- COMPTE USER -->
	<t id="UNameLength">The name you give to your soul must have between 4 and 20 characters.</t>
	<t id="UNameSChars">Only alphanumeric characters can be used in your soul's name (letters or numbers)</t>
	<t id="UNameExists">This soul name already exists. Please choose another.</t>
	<t id="UEmailFormat">This email address is invalid.</t>
	<t id="UPassLength">The password must contain between 6 and 32 characters.</t>
	<t id="UPassDiff">The secret code for confirmation is different from your passcode</t>
	<t id="UPasswordChanged">You have successfully changed your password! </t>
	<t id="UPasswordTooLong">Your password cannot consist of *more than 31 characters*.</t>
	<t id="UCommentSaved">Your comment has been saved.</t>
	<t id="UPassTooSimple">Your password is too simple! </t>
	<t id="USettingsChanged">Your settings have been saved.</t>
	<t id="UEmailChanged">You have successfully changed your email address! </t>
	<t id="UCountryRestriction">Registration is not possible in your country.</t>
	<t id="UBetaKeyInvalid">This invitation key is invalid.</t>
	<t id="MaxInvitationForN">Your sponsor has too many friends. Try to find a new sponsor.</t>
	<t id="MaxMid">You can only play Die2Nite with ::n:: different accounts per day.</t>
	<t id="MaxMidSubscribe">::mc:: accounts are already playing Die2Nite today. You can only play Die2Nite with ::n:: different accounts per day.</t>
	<t id="InvalidRefererName">*Your Sponsor's name was not recognised*, please check the spelling and try again.</t>
	<t id="BannedMid">Registration impossible.</t>
	<t id="UserDeleted">Your account has been deleted! You cannot use it to connect.</t>
	<t id="GhostTextsChanged">Your *description* has been updated.</t>
	<t id="RefererNotFound">Your sponsor could not be found! </t>
	<t id="Teasing_MaxPlayer">There are no available places remaining. Registration is only possible with invitation or with a sponsor.</t>
	<t id="Beta_MaxPlayer">There are no places available for the [BETA].</t>
	<t id="UnknownGodfather">This sponsor name is unknown! </t>

	<t id="DeathMessageSent">Your final words have been sent to the world of the living...</t>
	<t id="NeedReason">You must provide a reason for your complaint.</t>
	<t id="NeedExecutionBuilding">*This citizen is already shunned*. ~Registering another complaint will only be worthwhile *if the town constructs a "Gallows" or a "Meat Locker"*...~</t>
	<t id="SelfComplaint">Auto-denunciation... is, shall we say, a little extreme, and more importantly impossible :)</t>
	<t id="NoComplaintReason">For no apparent reason, ::name:: decided to entertain themselves by complaining about you...</t>
	<t id="SuspectIsDead">This person is already dead... You can't complain about them any more...</t>
	<t id="ComplaintRemoved">Your complaint has been withdrawn... Exercise better judgement next time...</t>
	<t id="North">the north</t>
	<t id="South">the south</t>
	<t id="West">the west</t>
	<t id="East">the east</t>
	<t id="CardClubs">Clubs</t>
	<t id="CardHearts">Hearts</t>
	<t id="CardSpades">Spades</t>
	<t id="CardDiamonds">Diamonds</t>
	<t id="CardAce">Ace</t>
	<t id="CardValet">Jack</t>
	<t id="CardQueen">Queen</t>
	<t id="CardKing">King</t>
	<t id="DrawCard">You have drawn the *::type:: of ::color::*...</t>
	<t id="DrawCardShort">::type:: of ::color::</t>
	<t id="DrawUser">::name::</t>
	<t id="NiceCard">It's a sign! It just goes to show that there is no place for morals in this world... You have won *1 AP*.</t>
	<t id="LoveCard">The queen of hearts... The symbol of love... **sigh**... You have won *1AP* as compensation for your disillusionment.</t>
	<t id="DrawRuleCard">You have drawn the... card with the *game rules* written on it. ~It makes you laugh so much that you win *1 AP*.~</t>
	<t id="DrawDoomedCard">You have drawn the... You scream as you discover your name is written on the card in blood! You don't care who is behind this evil joke...~You are now *terrorised*! ~</t>
	<t id="PFC_Rock">Rock</t>
	<t id="PFC_Paper">Paper</t>
	<t id="PFC_Scissors">Scissors</t>
	<t id="Tails">Tails</t>
	<t id="Heads">Heads</t>
	<t id="ChangedHomeMessage">You have changed your personal message. It is now visible in the *Yearbook*. </t>
	<t id="ErrorReported">A report has been created. *Please post a detailed message to Technical Support* if the problem persists. *Please do not abuse this function, or action will be taken.*</t>

	<t id="SysId_Forum_Tag">official</t>
	<t id="SysId_Bank">bank</t>
	<t id="SysId_Bank_title">The Bank</t>
	<t id="SysId_Bank_content">Use this subject for discussions involving the town Bank...</t>

	<t id="SysId_Refinery">refine</t>
	<t id="SysId_Refinery_title">The Workshop</t>
	<t id="SysId_Refinery_content">Use this subject for discussions involving the workshop and production of resources in town...</t>

	<t id="SysId_Buildings">build</t>
	<t id="SysId_Buildings_title">Construction Sites</t>
	<t id="SysId_Buildings_content">Use this subject for discussions involving buildings and construction sites...</t>

	<t id="SysId_Upgrades">cityup</t>
	<t id="SysId_Upgrades_title">Town Upgrades</t>
	<t id="SysId_Upgrades_content">Use this subject for discussions involving the town upgrades you wish to carry out...</t>

	<t id="BetaCodeNeeded">You must enter a [BETA] authorisation code to register.</t>
	<t id="BetaCodeInvalid">The [BETA] code entered is invalid</t>
	<t id="BetaCodeUsed">The [BETA] entered has already been used</t>
	<t id="NotABetaPlayer">Your account is not valid for use in [BETA] mode.</t>
	<t id="ReservedToBeta">This functionality is reserved for beta-testers</t>

	<t id="VipCodeNeeded">You must enter an VIP code to register.</t>
	<t id="VipCodeInvalid">The VIP code entered is invalid</t>
	<t id="VipCodeEmpty">No new registrations are allowed for this VIP code.</t>

	<t id="YouGotRobbed">Robbery!</t>
	<t id="GotRobbed">Apparently, one of your fellow citizens really liked the contents of your inventory... Someone has pinched your: ::tool::.</t>
	<t id="BadPass">This Passcode is invalid.</t>
	<t id="PleaseConnect">Your account has been created. You can log now log in :)</t>
	<t id="CguMustAccept">You must accept the terms and conditions of the site.</t>
	<t id="MustBeAdult">Please confirm that you are over ::age:: years old or that your parents have given you permission to join our universe.</t>
	<t id="NotEnoughMoney">You do not have enough money to do this.</t>
	<t id="UserRegistered">You have succesfully registered. That's all well and good, but will you manage to survive?</t>
	<t id="welcomeToPremium">You have just signed up for the Premium mode. But let's not be big-headed about it...</t>
	<t id="welcomeToHero">There you have it - *you are in Hero mode* ...for a while. Your happiness could be shortlived, so get that naive smile off your Chevy Chase! </t>
	<t id="UnknownJob">Somewhat remarkably, the profession you have chosen doesn't exist! It is so incredible that we invite you to contact Eternal support at the following address: support@leshordes.fr.</t>
	<t id="HeroJob">Sorry, the profession of ::job:: is only available to *Heroes*. ~Maybe it's time to realise your potential by activating Hero mode?~</t>
	<t id="HeroCantBeNoob">When you are a Hero, you cannot be a simple resident! Have some pride!</t>
	<t id="PickSameJob">You have already been a Hero in this incarnation (::j::): *you must continue where you left off not so very long ago*.</t>
	<t id="CongratulationsGotMoney">Congratulations, you just got paid! Now choose how you want to live...</t>
	<t id="MessageSent">Your message has been sent.</t>
	<t id="BlankMessage">Your message is empty! Please type another message.</t>
	<t id="AlreadyPostedAd">You have already posted an announcement. You cannot post another announcement at the same time. Delete the old announcement if it is no longer valid.</t>
	<t id="UserGotDailyWater">You have collected your daily ration: *::n::x* ::tool::</t>
	<t id="ExtraWaterLimit">You cannot take *more than ::n:: rations of water per day*.</t>
	<t id="UserAlreadyGotDailyWater">You have already received your daily allowance of water, come back tomorrow.</t>
	<t id="CanTakeMoreWater">Thanks to the building of the *Pump*, you are now allowed to take a *second ration*, if you need it.</t>
	<t id="UserGotMoreWater">You have taken *1* additional ::tool::! The other citizens have been informed. </t>
	<t id="GaveWaterToWell">You have transferred the water from the ::tool:: to the well (*+1 unit*).</t>
	<t id="NeedWaterInBag">You need *clean* water (not from a Jerrycan, for example) *in your rucksack*.</t>
	<t id="AteWell">You feel better. Your tiredness has gone. But for how long?...</t>
	<t id="MissingTool">Apparently the object you wanted to use has disappeared... Are you a magician?</t>
	<t id="StartRest">Little by little, you drift into a deep sleep...</t>
	<t id="Broken">This object is broken, so you can't use it for the time being! Perhaps a generous soul could fix it for you?</t>
	<t id="BrokenWord">broken</t>
	<t id="OuterLimited">This object can only be used in the World Beyond</t>
	<t id="TownLimited">This object can only be used in the town.</t>
	<t id="NeedBattery">You need a battery.</t>
	<t id="NeedWater">You need clean water (from a flask, for example).</t>
	<t id="NeedRawWater">You need a jerrycan of unpurified water (the nozzle will help here).</t>
	<t id="Need">You need the ::t:: for this task.</t>
	<t id="Thief">Hi, I needed something, you had one, so I took it. Hope you don't hate me too much! </t>
	<t id="NoZombie">There are no zombies here...</t>
	<t id="ZombieSingular">zombie</t>
	<t id="ZombiePlural">zombies</t>
	<t id="KilledZombies">You have eliminated ::n:: using the ::tool::. Ha! Ha! A little bit more scattered flesh... It feels good to waste a zombie now and again.</t>
	<t id="KilledAllZombies">All the zombies in the area have been wiped out using the ::tool::! You can relax for a while... Or...</t>
	<t id="ZoneTagged">Votre émetteur *répertorie cette zone en s'activant*. Tant qu'il restera allumé, l'émetteur continuera à répertorier les informations de toutes les zones que vous visiterez.</t>
	<t id="ZoneEnlightened">La Balise Radius est activée! Vous pouvez dès à présent connaître les informations des zones pérphériques.</t>
	<t id="EnlighterDepleted">*The battery is depleted*...</t>
	<t id="ZoneFlared">The flare has given us new information on zone [::x::,::y::]! </t>
	<t id="ZoneFlaredBuilding">The flare has revealed ::building:: at the following coordinates: [::x::,::y::]</t>
	<t id="ZoneBuildingRevealedByEclair">You have revealed a new building at the following co-ordinates: *[::x::,::y::]*! </t>
	<t id="NoMoreZoneBuildingToReveal">You study the horizon with your expert eye but it seems as though there are no more buildings to discover.</t>
	<t id="BatGunEmptied">The weapon has *run out of batteries*.</t>
	<t id="BatteryDestroyed">The battery seems to have been ill-suited for firing... It is now *useless*! </t>
	<t id="BatteryNotDestroyed">The battery landed a bit further away.</t>
	<t id="JerryGunEmptied">*The jerrycan is EMPTY*! </t>
	<t id="JerryGunNotEmptied">Good news, there is still water in the jerrycan...</t>
	<t id="BoxOpened">You have opened the ::box::, you have found the: ::item:: inside.</t>
	<t id="BoxOpenedWithTool">You managed to open the ::box:: with the ::opener::. You have obtained: the ::item::.</t>
	<t id="BoxDestroyed">You destroyed the ::box:: by attacking it with the ::opener::... You find the ::item:: amongst the remains on the ground.</t>
	<t id="NoOpener">You have nothing to open it with...</t>
	<t id="NoWeapon">You'll need something suitably solid to break that.</t>
	<t id="MultiBox">You unpack the ::t:: and you find the ::rep::.</t>
	<t id="MultiBoxNotEmpty">The box is not empty...</t>
	<t id="MultiBoxEmpty">::t:: is *empty*.</t>
	<t id="MultiBoxBagFull">You need *more space in your rucksack* to hold the contents of the  ::t::.</t>
	<t id="MultiBoxTrunkFull">You need *space in your chest* to hold the contents of the ::t::.</t>
	<t id="UserTired">You cannot carry out this action *when you are tired* (you have no action points remaining)... Drink, eat or drug yourself to restore points, or wait until tomorrow.</t>
	<t id="UserReallyTired">You are too tired to carry out this repair. You drop your hammer and other tools and head home to hit the hay.</t>
	<t id="NeedHeroDays">You need *::n:: day(s) of Hero mode in reserve* to do this.</t>
	<t id="NeedPA">*You need ::n:: action points to do this*. ~Drink, eat or drug yourself to restore points, or wait until *tomorrow*.~</t>
	<t id="RefundPALimit">The *town PA reserve* isn't sufficient to do this.</t>
	<t id="NeedRoom">You need at least *::n:: free space(s) in your rucksack*.</t>
	<t id="CantEvenKillOne">You hit a zombie with all your strength, several times, but your punches turned out to be more Joe Biden than Joe Calzaghe... *You couldn't get him to go down*! </t>
	<t id="CantEvenKillOneBatGun">You attack a zombie with your ::tool::, but *it hardly even flinches* and continues to advance! </t>
	<t id="JustBroken">Your weapon just broke on impact...</t>
	<t id="Useless">You don't need that right now...</t>
	<t id="UselessDrink">You have *already drank once today*: the only other use for water today will be to quench your thirst later on.</t>
	<t id="UselessDrug">You take the ::tool::, but it seems to have no notable effect... Maybe you didn't need it?</t>
	<t id="MovesDoubled">Your action points have been *multiplied by 2*! </t>
	<t id="DrunkAlcohol">Your head is spinning, you almost want to be sick, but *at least it woke you up*. Now you just need to run...</t>
	<t id="UselessAlcohol">It is impossible to drink this in your present state... *You already drank today or yesterday*.</t>
	<t id="DrunkCoffee">The sensation of well-being brought about by this small coffee puts you back on your feet instantly. Aah! </t>
	<t id="AddOnlyOneHeavyObject">You are *already carrying a heavy object*, you can only carry one at a time.</t>
	<t id="AddOnlyOneSpecial">You *already have a special object* in your bag, You can only transport one at a time.</t>
	<t id="AddOnlyOneBag">You already have one container with you (rucksac or other), you can only carry one at a time.</t>
	<t id="AddOnlyOnePocketBelt">You *are already wearing a belt like this*, you can only wear one at a time.</t>
	<t id="CantSwapBag">You cannot swap *a container* from your rucksack to your chest.</t>
	<t id="CantSwapOverflow">You cannot move objects between your rucksack and your chest *when you are overloaded* (too many objects on your person or in your chest).</t>
	<t id="NothingFound">After exhaustive searching, the only thing you have discovered is the emptiness of wasted time...</t>
	<t id="WoundedEyeHandicap">You are trying to scavenge, but your *eye injury* is really bothering you.</t>
	<t id="FoundObject">After extensive scavenging, you manage to find the ::item:: on the ground...</t>
	<t id="DriedZone">This zone is depleted, all that remains to be found here are poor-quality resources...</t>
	<t id="ExploredBuilding">Gut-wrenching fear grips you as you search the ::building::... However, it wasn't a waste of time, because you manage to find the ::item::.</t>
	<t id="SpecialFoundObject">Your scavenging instinct didn't let you down. You have unearthed the ::item::! </t>
	<t id="SpecialFoundObjectLimit">You could be fogiven for thinking there is *nothing more* to be found here... However, looking around, you find the ::item::! </t>
	<t id="SpecialNothingFound">You take a quick look around, but find nothing...</t>
	<t id="SpecialNoMoreObjectToFoundHere">You take a good look around, *but you don't find a thing*. This zone is *officially depleted*! </t>
	<t id="NoRoomDrop">You cannot carry this object for the time being, so you have left it *lying on the ground*.</t>
	<t id="NoRoomDropInChest">You cannot carry this object at the moment, so you have *left it in your chest*.</t>
	<t id="NoRoomForGather">The object you have just found cannot fit in your rucksack, so you have left it on the ground...</t>
	<t id="CannotSteal">It is impossible to steal the ::item::! This place is protected or there's somebody home...</t>
	<t id="CannotStealMine">You cannot steal ::item::! It already belongs to you! </t>
	<t id="ItemDisappeared">The object has disappeared! </t>
	<t id="PetGrenade">You send your ::pet:: over to the zombie. The wretched individual isn't the quickest of cats, but he pounces (slowly) on the animal to devour it, groaning all the time... Goodbye brave friend. On the plus side, that's one less zombie to worry about now he's distracted...</t>
	<t id="PetSurvived">Your animal *leapt at the zombie's throat*, and managed to turn itself into a zombie-cork! Well done! </t>
	<t id="NeedButcher">The town needs a *Butcher* to slaughter this animal...</t>
	<t id="NeedPurifier">You need *some kind of cleansing product* or your town needs a *Purifier* to make this water drinkable. The second option is not possible if you have been shunned.</t>
	<t id="MadeCoffee">You have made a ::name:: (by mixing ::list::)... Hmmm! Imagine how good this coffee tastes...</t>
	<t id="Repaired">You have repaired the ::tool:: with ::kit::. You have used *::cost:: action point(s)*.</t>
	<t id="CantDoWhenWounded">At the critical moment, your injury flares up, causing you to yell and drop the object. You must heal yourself before you will be able to use it.</t>
	<t id="ViolentRegen">A good dose of electricity into the spinal column, there's nothing quite like it to *wake you up*! However, you smell like burnt meat.</t>
	<t id="Rolled">You roll the dice, you get a *::a::*, a *::b::* and a *::c::*. </t>
	<t id="RolledDouble">You rolled a *double*! Check you out! .</t>
	<t id="Rolled421">You got a 421 on your first shot... not bad. ~Furthermore, this has raised your morale so much that you have gained *1 AP*.~</t>
	<t id="RolledTriple">Nicely done, you got *three of a kind*! This is a great game! ~You're enjoying it so much that you have gained *1 AP*.~</t>
	<t id="RolledSuite">You have rolled a *straight*! That always raises the spirits. ~You're enjoying it so much that you have gained *1 AP*~</t>
	<t id="CantHideNow">It is impossible to use camouflage when the zone is controlled by zombies! </t>
	<t id="LostCamo">You are *no longer camouflaged*! </t>
	<t id="CamoDetected">Although you were moving sneakily, *a zombie in the zone heard you* and turned towards you! You have been *discovered*! ~</t>
	<t id="Hidden">You are now *camouflaged*.</t>
	<t id="UsedPA">You have used *::n:: action points*.</t>
	<t id="UsedTechnicianPA">You have used *::n:: construction points*.</t>
	<t id="UsedRefundPA">You used *::n:: action point(s)* from the *town reserve*.</t>
	<t id="DidNotUsedPA">You didn't use any AP to carry out this action.</t>
	<t id="UsedPAReduced">You have used *::n:: action points* (cost reduced by ::reduc:: AP thanks to: ::reducers::).</t>
	<t id="UsedFlashTool">You set off the ::tool::... The violent flash sends a blast of photons into the zombie ranks! Blinded, they stumble around, unable to find you. ~You have *::d::* to act.~</t>
	<t id="ExploUsedFlashTool">You set off the ::tool::... The violently bright flash wreaks panic in the zombie ranks! Blinded, ::count:: zombie(s) turn back to seek shelter in a calmer place a little further from the front line. </t>
	<t id="FlashToolFailed">A dull sound and a wisp of greenish smoke escape from the ::tool::... ~*That didn't seem to work.* Disappointed...~</t>
	<t id="Slavery">The AP invested in this construction site count *double* (slavery).</t>
	<t id="Alarm">You have set off the alarm system installed at ::clint::'s house! The whole town has been alerted to your intrusion.</t>
	<t id="EmptyInvFirstToGiveBag">To give a bag to the town, first of all you must *put all other objects you are carrying in your house or in the bank*.</t>
	<t id="CantFleeWhileWounded">You cannot flee, because you are *already injured*! </t>
	<t id="NoMoveLeft">You have *run out of action points*.</t>
	<t id="FleeingIsDangerous">Whilst trying to flee, a zombie managed to cut your: ::p::! We've got to get out of this place, and quick! </t>
	<t id="ForbiddenOutside">You canot do this while you are in *the World Beyond*.</t>
	<t id="ForbiddenAtDoors">You canot do this while you are *at the town gates*.</t>
	<t id="NotWounded">You have *not been injured*.</t>
	<t id="Convalescent">You have *already been healed once today*. Sleep on it and we'll talk again tomorrow...</t>
	<t id="Healed">A snip of the scissors, spit on the wound to disinfect it... There you go, *good as new*.</t>
	<t id="CantStayInTerror">You cannot do this when you are gripped by *Terror*! ! If you are blocked in the zone *it is impossible for you to do anything*... *Are you still here? Run! RUUUUNNNN!</t>
	<t id="CantActInTerror">~If you are gripped by terror, in the desert and surrounded by zombies you can't do anything... You need to find a drug or something else to *calm your nerves* and get out of this hellhole... At least it is still possible to call for help on the forum...~</t>
	<t id="UsedFood">This has a truly bizarre taste, it's difficult to define. It does the job though: fills your stomach. On the other hand, it doesn't give you any extra energy...</t>
	<t id="HumanFood">It's not as appetising *as a nice, fresh, wriggling human*, but it does its job and makes your *voracity* subside... a little. Fortunately, the meat was quite gamey, this meal would have been dreadful otherwise.</t>
	<t id="BadHumanFood">A cold body which hasn't even started to decay yet is truly *tasteless* Your voracity has been somewhat calmed, but you really didn't get anything else from this "meal".</t>
	<t id="UsedTastyFood">Just this once does no harm, you enjoy devouring the ::food::. It makes a change from the usual disgusting slop... it perks you right up. ~You get a *bonus of 1 AP*! ~</t>
	<t id="UsedWater">You drink your water ration in one go... That's much better! </t>
	<t id="UsedWaterDehydrated">You greedily gulp down your ration of water, without tasting it in the least... Your throat still burns as much, but at least you aren't dehydrated anymore...~*Your APs have not been restored because you were dehydrated*.~</t>
	<t id="UsedWaterAgain">You drink your water ration in one go... ~However, because *you have already drank today, your action points will not be restored*.~</t>
	<t id="UsedDrug">The effects of the drug don't take long to show: nausea, trembling, cold sweats... But at least it gives you a boost. Don't abuse it! </t>
	<t id="UsedTastyDrug">It's not every day you get to hit some quality drugs. All the same, the effects are nausea, trembling, cold sweats... But it gives you more of a boost than regular drugs (AP bonus received). Don't abuse it! </t>
	<t id="UsedAprilDrug">That's strange... I'd have to say *the drug didn't have the expected effect at all*. You tell yourself that you've been *incredibly lucky*...</t>
	<t id="Intoxicated">*Bad news*, you maybe shouldn't have swallowed that... you have been *infected*! </t>
	<t id="DisgustingFood">You observe a few seconds later, that this  had a horrendous after taste...</t>
	<t id="UsedWaterDrug">You swallow the pill... A few seconds later, your thirst has disappeared. But at what price...</t>
	<t id="Addicted">Bad news! You are now *hooked*! From now on, you must take at least one drug per day... or DIE! </t>
	<t id="CalmedDown">The drug took effect rapidly... Everything suddenly seems *calmer*, more serene... Even the horrendous events of the past few days now seem unimportant... That's better! </t>
	<t id="Hugged">You hold the ::tool:: tight to your chest... Tears quickly begin to well in your eyes. The stress... You let out an audible sob when you consider the hell in which you live... ~After a few minutes you feel a bit better...~</t>
	<t id="HuggedFailed">You hold the ::tool:: tight to your chest... *Nothing happens.* You feel even sadder than before. What's the point in continuing a "life" like this?</t>
	<t id="CleanedUp">You spend a few minutes cleaning your ::tool::. You do your best to get rid of the bloodstains then you patch up the holes.</t>
	<t id="NeedZombiePart">To use this object, you need something to throw. A roundish lump of flesh could, for example, do the job...</t>
	<t id="TigerWoods">Your technique could use some work, I'm sure you'll do better next time... If you're still alive.</t>
	<t id="NoBuildingToExtract">There is no building buried in the sand here... so stop wasting your time searching for something that doesn't exist...</t>
	<t id="CheckedUnextracted">You clear a path through the debris, take a few measurements, rub the earth from your grimy hands... ~After several long minutes of investigation, you can confirm, without a shadow of a doubt, that this building is: *::bname::*!~</t>
	<t id="BuildingNotExtractedYet">You have uncovered some of the sector, but there is still a substantial amount of debris blocking the way...</t>
	<t id="BuildingAlreadyExtracted">The zone has been completely uncovered, you can now start to search for the untold treasures hidden in the :*::building::*! </t>
	<t id="BuildingExtracted">Congratulations, the zone has been completely uncovered! You can now start to search for items in the: *::building::*! </t>
	<t id="EmptyBuilding">After a sneaky scout around the building, you are sure there is nothing left to recover. Shame...</t>
	<t id="TakeFromCity">You have just taken the ::tool:: from the Bank. *Don't abuse the privilege* or other citizens might take it to heart...</t>
	<t id="RobFromCity">You have just stolen the ::tool:: from the Bank! Your name will not appear in the Register...</t>
	<t id="RobFromCityFailed">Your attampt to steal from the Bank failed! *You were caught! *</t>
	<t id="NoWaterleft">There is *no water left in  the well*! ! Go and find some jerrycans in the World Beyond! </t>
	<t id="NoMoreObjectToFoundHere">Apparently, all *resources in this zone are depleted*. There is nothing more to be found here.</t>
	<t id="AlreadyEaten">You have already eaten today.</t>
	<t id="NotHungry">You *do not need to eat* at the moment: You are not exhausted and you still have all your action points.</t>
	<t id="NotThirsty">You *do not need to eat* at the moment: You are not exhausted, you are not thirsty and you still have all your action points.</t>
	<t id="HeroTool">This object is *reserved for Heroes*. You can take it with you, but *it won't give you any bonus* and it is of no use unless you are in Hero mode...</t>
	<t id="NotAllRequired">This isn't possible, you need: ::list::.</t>
	<t id="BuildingRequired">You can't do that. You need to construct <strong>::building::</strong></t>
	<t id="CantAssemble">You cannot combine ::tool:: with this. You can do this with one of the following objects: ::list::.</t>
	<t id="Assembled">You have assembled ::name:: by combining ::list::.</t>
	<t id="AssembledWithOne">You have assembled ::name:: by combining ::first:: and ::second::.</t>
	<t id="Transformed">You have transformed the ::old:: into the ::tool::.</t>
	<t id="UsedHeroBoost">You have used your *Hero Boost*! Your *action points have been restored and you are wide awake*.</t>
	<t id="HeroOnly">This action is *reserved for Heroes*... Maybe it's time for you to become one?</t>
	<t id="TrueHeroOnly">Hero days acquired other than through subscription do not grant access to World Forums.</t>
	<t id="CantDropSoulLocked">You *cannot drop objects locked to your profession*... The good news though, is that these types of objects take up *no space* in your rucksack.</t>
	<t id="NoBuildingBuilt">None</t>
	<t id="NoCombination">You need to acquire a *second* ::tool:: to complete this.</t>
	<t id="AssembledIdenticals">You have mixed ::base:: (x2) to obtain ::tool::.</t>
	<t id="LaboIsBetter">It would be wiser to use your personal *Laboratory* for this task...</t>
	<t id="ActionCanBeForced">You are able to *force this action* by selecting it a second time.</t>
	<t id="UsedVibro">You get comfortable back home and let yourself go... Bad surprise: the toy turns out to be *incredibly painful* to use! Nonetheless, you end up getting a taste for it. After a few minutes, the effect is incredible: you are soaked in sweat, but you feel more... "zen".~The battery inside is completely spent.~</t>
	<t id="ReminderWater">Before you consider leaving the town, you should first go past the *Well* to get your *daily water ration*! </t>
	<t id="ReminderEquip">It would be a better idea to take some *provisions* with you (food and/or water) before you go... Go to the *My House* area to load up.</t>
	<t id="ReminderTutorial">Before taking your first steps in the World Beyond, we suggest you check out the guide entitled, "*Exploring the World Beyond*", located at the *top left of the site*.</t>
	<t id="NoRoomInTrunk">You cannot put this object in your chest, as it is already full! </t>
	<t id="NoRoomInTrunkWithCount">Your chest cannot accommodate *::n:: object(s)*: there are only *::max:: place(s)* remaining.</t>
	<t id="NoMoreRoomInTrunk">Your chest is already full! </t>
	<t id="EmptiedBagInChest">You put *everything you can* in your chest (there's only so much space, remember)...</t>
	<t id="FurnitureTutorial">Well done! You have added a *household object* to your house. This object will automatically be used. Click on the Improvements tab to see its value! </t>
	<t id="FurnitureTutorialBuilt">It is a *Household Object*. Once it has been placed in your chest, the object will automatically be used. Click on the Improvements tab to see its value! </t>
	<t id="NoNeedToFlee">You start to flee, but then realise that *the zone is no longer controlled by zombies*. You can breath again! </t>
	<t id="LostControl">Nightmare! Just when you were about to act, *the zombies regained control of the zone*! </t>
	<t id="CannotPickOnTown">It is not possible to scavenge in this area! </t>
	<t id="CannotDrop">You cannot drop this object here.</t>
	<t id="NoNeedToBeBrave">The danger has passed! *Humans now control the zone! *</t>
	<t id="NoYouCannotFly">As the wise man said: you cannot fly without wings...</t>
	<t id="UnknownZone">A wise man once said: it is impossible to go somewhere that doesn't exist...</t>
	<t id="CantUpgrade">If you want to upgrade your house from a *::old::* to a *::up::* (level ::lvl::), you need: ::list::.</t>
	<t id="HomeUpgraded">Congratulations! You have upgraded your house to a *::name::*. You have used: ::list:: (you have spent *::cost:: action points*).</t>
	<t id="HomeUpgradedNoRsc">Congratulations! You have upgraded your house to a *::name::*. you have spent *::cost:: action points*).</t>
	<t id="UnknownUser">Unknown citizen! </t>
	<t id="NeedJob">This citizen has not yet chosen their profession. They are taking their time weighing the pros and cons. In the mean time, they are unavailable...</t>
	<t id="CadaverGarbaged">You have dragged ::cadaver::'s corpse out of town. A good job well done! </t>
	<t id="CadaverCooked">You have brought ::cadaver::'s corpse to the cremato-cue. You manage to get *::n:: rations* out of it... but at what price?</t>
	<t id="AlreadyGarbaged">This corpse has already been taken outside the town! </t>
	<t id="CadaverWatered">The body liquified into a sickeningly vile puddle. Your shoes got the worst of it, that's for sure...</t>
	<t id="AlreadyWatered">This corpse has already been watered, did you not see the puddle at your feet?!!</t>
	<t id="TheCrow">The Crow</t>
	<t id="SantaClaus"><strong><img src="/gfx/icons/item_christmas_suit_full.gif" alt=""/> Father Christmas</strong></t>
	<t id="Leprechaun"><strong><img src="/gfx/icons/item_leprechaun_suit.gif" alt=""/> Leprechaun</strong></t>
	<t id="ResetUniverse">The universe has perished. Nothingness and vacuity dominate the landscape.</t>
	<t id="Complained">You have registered a complaint against ::suspect::. If sufficient complaints are received, *::suspect:: will be shunned by the community*, or hanged if there is a gallows.</t>
	<t id="AlreadyComplained">You have already registered a complaint against ::suspect::.</t>
	<t id="ComplaintHanged">Your complaint was the final straw... A large number of citizens have voted against ::suspect::! ~The pariah was *hanged*, drawn and quartered. *The gallows was destroyed during this violent operation...~</t>
	<t id="ComplaintCrucified">Your complaint was the final straw... A large number of citizens have voted against ::suspect::! ~The pariah was *crucified* on your chocolate cross as an example to others.~</t>
	<t id="ComplaintMeatCage">Your complaint was the final straw... A large number of citizens have voted against ::suspect::! ~The pariah was dragged to the *Meat Locker* then stoned in front of a cheering crowd. What an atmosphere!~</t>
	<t id="ComplaintBanned">Your complaint was the final straw... A large number of citizens have voted against ::suspect::!  ~The citizen is now shunned by the community: they will no longer have access to the town's resources, with the exception of the well (still limited to one ration per day, no additional rations).~</t>
	<t id="HangerDestroyed">*The gallows have been destroyed* during that particularly gruesome event...</t>
	<t id="EasterCrossDestroyed">*The chocolate cross was erm... tasted* during the last bout of extreme violence...</t>
	<t id="RandDrugTerror">You swallow the ::tool::... Just a few seconds later, you panic... Cold sweats, paranoia... You curl up in a ball, out of breath, waiting for the feelings to subside... but it doesn't happen. ~You become *Terrorised*.~</t>
	<t id="RandDrugPowerful">You immediately regret swallowing the ::tool::... The product turns out to be a powerful steroid for animals (the kind usually given to horses as it happens). Your APs have been restored, but you instantly become *dependant on drugs*! </t>
	<t id="RandDrugNothing">You gulp down the ::tool::. After several minutes, your head starts to throb and your nose starts bleeding. The pain is not unbearable, but it's pretty far from pleasant...</t>
	<t id="Disinfected">The ::tool:: rapidly takes effect. *The fever subsides*, your heart starts beating at a a semi-normal rate again... You weren't far away from a horrible death.</t>
	<t id="UsedDigger">You have partially cleared the zone using your ::tool:: (*1 point* cleared)...</t>
	<t id="UndiggedBuilding">Buried building</t>
	<t id="UsedDiggerMany">You have partially cleared the zone using your ::tool:: (*::n:: points* cleared)...</t>
	<t id="ParticipatedBuilding">You have participated in the construction of the "::building::".</t>
	<t id="RepairedBuilding">You have repaired *::repair:: point(s) worth of damage* on the site of the *::building::*.</t>
	<t id="RscMissing">It's too late, it seems there is a *shortage of raw materials* for this building! </t>
	<t id="DoneBuilding">Hurrah! Construction of the ::building:: is complete!</t>
	<t id="TooManyPA">You don't need to invest *as many APs* on this task (*maximum ::max:: APs*)! </t>
	<t id="TooManyItemsForDump">*You can't destroy as many objects at the dump* (insufficient PA or insufficient stocks in the bank.</t>
	<t id="UsedInDump">You have destroyed ::n:: x ::tool:: at the public dump. ~The town has gained *::def:: defence point(s)*.~</t>
	
	<t id="PurifiedSoul">You have purified a lost soul. It evaporates leaving you with an aftertaste of peace and serenity...</t>
	
	<t id="YouAreShaman">~*Congratulations!*~! You've been elected as the Shaman of your town by your comrades! Don't forget to go and <a href="/#help/chaman">read the guide</a> to learn about the role you're now playing.  ~*<a href="/#help/chaman">Read the Help</a>*~</t>
	<t id="CantBuildNow">It is not possible for the construction of the ::building:: to progress, additional resources must be placed in the *Bank*! ~These resources only need be present in the bank during the construction. They will not be "used* (and therefore taken from the bank) until the construction is complete*.~</t>
	<t id="BuildingAlreadyBuilt">It would appear that another citizen *completed the site* before you arrived :) That's good news, no?</t>
	<t id="RecyclingDone">You have finished dismantling ::c::'s house! All the objects that were in his chest are now in the Bank.~The town has also recovered the following resources: ::rsc::.~</t>
	<t id="RecycledNothing">You have finished dismantling ::c::'s house! All the objects that were in his chest are now in the Bank.~The town didn't recover anything useful from their house, there was really *nothing of interest to take*...~</t>
	<t id="Recycling">You use *1 AP* to dismantle ::c::'s house. There is still more work to be done...</t>
	<t id="CooledDownActionLocked">This action is blocked for *approximately ::n:: minutes* (anti-abuse system). ~*Warning: if you try to repeat this action before this time, the duration of the restriction will be extended.!*~</t>
	<t id="CooledDownActionPenalty">*Repeated attempt*: waiting time has been increased by *::n:: minutes*.</t>
	<t id="BigCooledDownAction">This action blocks access to the bank for *::n:: minutes* (anti-abuse system).</t>
	<t id="UnlockedBook">You examine the ::tool:: closely... You find a text, seemingly entitled " ::title:: ". You read it intently...</t>
	<t id="UnlockedBookNew"><strong>A new text has been added to your documents! </strong></t>
	<t id="AlreadyHaveBook">You have already found this book, so it *doesn't earn you any additional distinctions*</t>
	<t id="FoundBookInBox">You open and shake the ::from::. You find ::book:: inside! </t>
	<t id="WrestledAndKilled">During an frightful encounter, you finally managed to *throw a zombie* against a rock... Its head literally *exploded* and the contents splattered onto your shoes!  Breathless, you stagger backwards: that's one more down...one...less...</t>
	<t id="WrestledFailed">You grab one of the wretched automatons with both hands, touching the *sticky, putrefied flesh*... it's unbearable... You wrestle with it, trying to force it back, but it's not happening... *It tries unsuccessfully to bite you several times! * You retreat, out of breath and demoralised...</t>
	<t id="NoNeedToWrestle">Screaming like a madman, you launch yourself at a zombie... ready to do anything to get past, but you then realise that *the zone is no longer controlled by zombies*. You can breathe again! </t>
	<t id="AdminPowa">You prepare to do the unthinkable, but in the end you tell yourself... no... they're an *admin*... :)</t>
	<t id="BanForbidden">It is impossible to do this when you have been *shunned by the community*! </t>
	<t id="AnyBanForbidden">It is impossible to do this when you have been *shunned* by the community and banned from the forums! </t>
	<t id="NotInDemo">This action is not available in the trial version of Die2Nite :) ~Don't panic though, you can do all these things on the online version! ~</t>
	<t id="ChestUpgraded">You set up the ::t:: in your house. It's not very aesthetically pleasing, but really... who cares? ~This object allows you to permanently add *::n:: storage compartments* to your chest.~</t>
	<t id="DefUpgraded">You install the ::t:: in your house. There's no way that thing is going anywhere, but that's kinda the point... ~This object permanently adds *::n:: defence points* to your house.~</t>
	<t id="CleanedUpHome">You pick up the rubbish that's lying around, tidy up your few remaining possessions and generally try to make the place you call home a little less squalid...</t>
	<t id="CatapultNewMaster">A new catapult operator has been nominated: ::u::.</t>
	<t id="CatapultUseless">There is no need to use the catapult at the moment! </t>
	<t id="CatapultInvalidZone">These coordinates are invalid! You cannot catapult objects into the town or outwith the confines of the map.</t>
	<t id="CatapultInvalidItem">The object you have chosen is invalid.</t>
	<t id="CatapultLaunch">You carefully wrap, pack and place the ::t:: in the catapult. The object has been fired to <strong>[::x::,::y::]</strong>! </t>
	<t id="TowerInspection">From the top of the tower, you study the surrounding desert and try to count the zombies to predict their movements... ~After a few minutes of intense consideration, you register your observations in the *Watchtower register*.~ ~Using this information and that of other citizens, it should be possible to make a reasonable estimation of the attack....~</t>
	<t id="Conspiracy">You begin you hatch a dastardly scheme to *revolt* and turn the tables on the citizens who shunned you. It's a long term project... other shunned citizens must join the cause! </t>
	<t id="Revolted">*The shunned citizens are revolting* :)! !</t>
	<t id="AlreadyRevolted">There has already been an insurrection of the shunned in this town... *It is no longer possible to reverse the situation*.</t>
	<t id="SmokedCig">You light a cigarette. The smoke makes you cough violently, no doubt because you're not used to it... After a few minutes, *you manage to calm down*. This brief moment of respite allows you to clear your mind a little and take stock of the situation. ~You crush the stub on the ground ready to fight for survival once more! ~</t>
	<t id="LastCig">You notice that *the packet is empty*! </t>
	<t id="LastMatch">That was your *last match*... It's going to be tricky to light another cigarette now.</t>
	<t id="CantTeleportDoorClosed">*The town gates are closed*, it is impossible to be teleported to the town! </t>
	<t id="MadePoison">Warning! You have poisoned the ::tool::! It is now *almost impossible to distinguish from a safe one*, so be careful... It's up to you to do with it what you feel is "fair".</t>
	
	<t id="LastChance">Building the ::name:: has brought *+::n:: temporary defence points* to your town, but *everything in the bank was destroyed*. Here's hoping that it's enough...</t>
	<t id="Baloon">Constructing the ::name:: has allowed you to reveal *the entire map*!</t>
	<t id="RocketKill">Using the ::name:: pulverised a good number of zombies in the World Beyond!</t>

	<t id="PutDefense">You install the ::tool:: then place some rubbish and dried branches over it for camouflage. There you go, that should hopefully improve your chances of making it through the night.</t>
	<t id="PutDefenseForbidden">You cannot use this object at the town gates! </t>
	<t id="CanOnlyUseOnBuilding">This object can only be used *on a ruin in the World Beyond* (which must not have been ravaged by the zombie hordes).</t>
	<t id="DrunkPenalty">Your *sobriety*, or lack thereof, is quite inconvenient. Things become pretty tricky pretty quickly when you're completely wasted...</t>
	<t id="ChristmasCandy">You smile as you swallow the ::tool:: ... but you rapidly become disillusioned. The candy contained a powerful *psychotropic poison*! </t>
	<t id="ChristmasCandy_Terrorized">You are now *terrorised*! </t>
	<t id="ChristmasCandy_Infected">You are now *infected*! </t>
	<t id="ChristmasCandy_Addicted">You are now *dependant* on drugs! </t>
	<t id="NothingToFill">You have *no water-based weaponry to fill* either in your rucksack OR in your chest.</t>
	<t id="FilledWaterWeapons">You have refilled ::list:: for free, thanks to the plumbing improvements in town! </t>
	<t id="CantFindSafeCode">You waste precious time looking for the combination to the chest. ~You have used *1 action point*.~</t>
	<t id="FoundSafeCode">Nice one! *You have found the secret combination for the chest! * The code was ::code::... You find the ::tool:: inside.</t>
	<t id="CantFalsify">It is *impossible* to tamper with this kind of entry in the register.</t>
	<t id="Falsified">You have discretely *tampered with an entry in the register*... ~You can do this ::n:: more times.~</t>
	<t id="GameActionLimit">You can only carry out this action *::n:: times per game*.</t>
	<t id="GainedPA">You have gained *::n:: AP*! </t>
	<t id="Minutes">::n:: minute(s)</t>
	<t id="Seconds">::n:: second(s)</t>
	<t id="GarbageFoundObject">Scavengin in the rubbish lying around near the town, you manage to find ::item::.</t>
	<t id="GarbageNothingFound">You spend some time rummaging in the garbage trying to find something useful, *but you find nothing*...</t>
	<t id="HasHiddenTools">You spend a while *hiding all the obects on your person*... Ha Ha...</t>
	<t id="HideToolsDetected">One or more regular citizens in the zone *saw you hiding your stash*! </t>
	<t id="DiscoveredHiddenTools">You started to search, when you noticed some kind of... *cache* containing: ::list::! ~Hmmm... This was probably hidden by a *shunned citizen*...~</t>
	<t id="BannedNote">This scrawled note used to belong to a *shunned citizen*... The only thing you can read is "*::x::,::y::*"... Strange. ~You destroy the page just to be sure that nobody else reads the message...! ~</t>
	<t id="BannedNoteEmpty">Unlucky, the contents of this manuscript are *completely illegible*.</t>
	<t id="NoUse">You have absolutely *no use whatsoever* for this object...</t>
	<t id="RscBurnt">You have completely burnt the ::tool::... Hahaha...</t>
	<t id="Depleted">::tool:: is of no more use to you for the moment...</t>
	<t id="ObjectiveComplete">Well done... *You have successfully completed your objective*. Good work, but I'd bet my last dime that the others won't be as happy about it...</t>
	<t id="ObjectiveNotComplete">It would appear that you still have not done what was required of you...</t>
	<t id="ObjectiveTooLate">Maybe you succeeded... or maybe not. Whatever the case, *it's too late now: the deadline has passed! *</t>
	<t id="GotNewObjective">You read the piece of paper attentively... Interesting... Very interesting indeed... ~You have the presence of mind to rip up the sheet so that nobody else reads it.~ ~You have been issued a new *secret objective*: go to your house to read the message and discover what it is...~ </t>
	<t id="Infected">This really has a *funny taste*... A few seconds after swallowing the ::tool::, you feel incredibly sick, and have a thundering headache... A fever quickly overcomes you. Your hands start to shake...~You have been *infected*! ~</t>
	<t id="GaveTool">You have given the ::tool:: to ::target::...</t>
	<t id="CantGiveThat">You cannot give *this object* to a citizen.</t>
	<t id="Detected">Your were spotted! *The citizens have been warned! *</t>
	<t id="Terrorized">You are now *terrorised*! </t>
	<t id="TerrorizedCantMove">While taking a look around, *you are gripped by a sudden and unremitting panic)! You can't go one step further... Your planned movements have been disrupted and you have lost *1 AP*.~</t>
	<t id="InvalidActionReported">The action you have attempted is invalid. It has been noted, and could lead to sanctions if this turns out to be related to abuse or manipulation of the game.</t>
	<t id="RobinetIsBetter">It is better to use the *Fill* option below to do this...</t>
	<t id="CantShareNotEnoughDays">It is impossible to do this, *you do not have sufficient Hero days remaining*! </t>
	<t id="CantShareHeroWithHero">ou cannot give an additional hero day to another Hero.</t>
	<t id="CantShareHeroWithGhost">You cannot give Hero days to players that are dead or who have left the game in progress.</t>
	<t id="SharedHeroMsg">::name:: has given you a free day to play as in Hero mode!</t>
	<t id="SharedHeroCancelMsg">::name:: was unable to use the Hero day you sent them! This Hero day has been returned to you.</t>

	<t id="XPGivenHeroMsg">*The Crow* congratulates you and in honour of your accession to the realms of experienced souls, you have been awarded ::count:: Hero days!</t>
	
	<t id="SharedHero">You have given a free Hero day to ::name::! </t>
	
	<t id="HunterBookFailed">So much for the survival book. Hardly surprising that this book didn't go beyond the elementary stages... No wonder Junior Woodchuck only wrote one book - he probably starved to death in a desert somewhere. You have found absolutely nothing, but you probably knew that already.</t>
	
	<t id="HuntedFood">You go in search of food in the surrounding area...~After many minutes of searching, you get your hands on a *twisting fistful of fat, sticky worms*. Your manual is very clear on the subject: they are edible! *You swallow the lot before they have a chance to escape*.~ ~*All of your APs have been restored! *~</t>
	<t id="HuntedWater">Examining your surroundings, you come across a puddle of stagnant water. As you really don't have a choice, you force yourself to drink the lot (as well as whatever was floating in it)...~*All of your APs have been restored! *~</t>
	<t id="HunterRegen">*All your action points have been restored*</t>
	<t id="HunterRegenDehydrated">Your AP have not been restored because you were *dehydrated*.</t>
	<t id="TamedPetToChest">You send ::pet:: in the direction of the town with the contents of your rucksack. ~As you asked, *everything was left at your house*.~ ~Brave animal! ~</t>
	<t id="TamedPetToBank">You send ::pet:: in the direction of the town with the contents of your rucksack.~*Your neighbours will be really happy when they see all that in the bank.*~</t>
	<t id="TamedPetCantPickUpHeavy">::pet:: cannot return the contents of your rucksack: you are carrying a *heavy object* which is just too much for your pet to take! </t>
	<t id="TamedPetNothing">::pet:: has nothing to take back to town, *your rucksack is empty*.</t>
	<t id="TamedPetDoorClosed">::pet:: starts to whine and look at you  strangely. Unless your trusty pet's intuition is having an off day, this almost certainly means that *the town gates are closed*... ~It would be fair to say that you're all out of luck.~</t>
	<t id="TamedPetDrug">You give some ::drug:: to ::pet:: which got wolfed down in one gulp.~It only took a few minutes for the drugs to kick in: your labradoodle now has bright eyes, a glossy coat and a wagging tail.~</t>
	<t id="GhoulAttack">Without a moment's hesitation you throw yourself at ::name::, teeth bared! Leaving them no time to react, your barrage of blows quickly cause them to lose consciousness. ~When you are finally sure that your victim isn't getting up, *you finish the job by eating them*.~ ~There you have it, *it's done*.~</t>
	<t id="GhoulStatusInherited">You have inherited certain *health traits* from your victim! </t>
	<t id="NoGhoulAttackOnDoors">You cannot devour a citizen *at the town gates*.</t>
	<t id="GhoulWaterWound">You swallow your water ration in one gulp: the result was certainly not as you has imagined... Without any warning, your throat starts to burn horribly, and gives way to a frightful and painful cough! You fall, breathless, to your knees. As a *ghoul*, you cannot drink water an more: you are now *wounded*.</t>
	<t id="UsePlanInTown">To study the plans, head back to the *relative calm* of the town.</t>
	<t id="UnlockedBuilding">After examining the plan, you realise that it shows precisely how to build the ::b::! ~You record this new information in the construction site section.~ ~This project requires the ::deps:: to be build first.~</t>
	<t id="BuildingAlreadyUnlocked">After axamining the plan, you realise that it shows precisely how to build the ::b::, a site which your town has *already unlocked*. ~Dammit! ~</t>
	<t id="NoBuildingLeft">*Your town has already unlocked all construction projects in this category!* ~This object is therefore useless, so you decide to throw it away.~</t>
	<t id="Muted">You cannot write here: *your comment-writing privileges have been revoked*. This right affects (among other things) the ability to write comments during games and leaving post-mortem messages.</t>
	<t id="Immune">The medicine has given you strength: you are now immune to infections, and cannot be transformed into a Ghoul. *This effect will wear off following the attack*.</t>
	<t id="Anonymous">Unknown Author</t>
	<t id="Someone">an unknown citizen</t>
	<t id="GotPlan">lost in the middle of a ludicrous quantity of pointless documents, you have discovered ::t::!</t>
	<t id="UsedWatchmen">You take a walk round the town to check for weaknesses and kick some dodgy-looking repairs to test their worth. ~The town has earned *+::n:: temporary defence points*.~</t>
	
	<t id="CantHideWithEscort">It is not possible to use the *Camouflage* with ::n:: people following you...</t>
	<t id="OnlyHeroesCanEscort">Only *Heroes* have the skills needed to guide other citizens in the World Beyond...</t>
	<t id="SquadLimit">You cannot be followed by more than *::n::&nbsp;citizens*.</t>
	<t id="SquadCantMove">*One or more of the citizens in your group cannot follow you*. You will need to check out the situation... or leave the weak behind.</t>
	<t id="PetHasNoFood">You tell the citizen to *eat something* before continuing, but they tell you they have *nothing to eat*...</t>
	<t id="PetHasNoWater">You tell the citizen to *drink something* before continuing, but they tell you they have *nothing to drink*...</t>
	<t id="PetEaten">You tell the citizen to *eat something* before continuing. They agree and whip out their ::tool::... After a brief lunch stop...~::user:: has regained all their APs! ~</t>
	<t id="PetDropped">::user:: is no longer following you.</t>
	<t id="PetPickedUp">::user:: has agreed to follow you.</t>
	<t id="CantPickUpPet">This citizen has *refused* to follow you! ~Perhaps they are already following someone else?~</t>
	<t id="PetNothingFound">After some thorough searching, this citizen has *found nothing*...</t>
	<t id="PetWoundedEyeHandicap">Their *wounded eye* is significantly affecting their ability to scavenge.</t>
	<t id="PetDrunkPenalty">Their drunken state doesn't enhance their scavenging skills whatsoever...</t>
	<t id="PetFoundObject">After searching for some time, this citizen managed to find the ::item:: on the ground...</t>
	<t id="PetNoRoomDrop">They cannot carry this object for the moment so they have left it *on the ground*.</t>
	<t id="PetWantToGoHome">::user:: refuses to go in this direction! *This citizen wants you to take him back to the town*...</t>
	<t id="ForbiddenInEscort">You cannot do this *while you are following another citizen*.</t>
	<t id="PetArrivedAtHome">::user:: thanks you wholeheartedly for taking them back to the town! </t>
	<t id="PetUselessDrink">This citizen has *already drank once today*: the only use they will have for water later will be to quench their thirst later on.</t>
	<t id="PetNotThirsty">This citizen *does not need to drink* at the moment: they are not tired or thirsty and they still have all their APs.</t>
	<t id="PetUsedWater">The citizen gulps down your water ration... that's much better! </t>
	<t id="PetUsedWaterDehydrated">the citizen greedily gulps down their ration of water, without tasting it in the least... Their throat still burns as much, but at least they aren't dehydrated anymore...~*Their APs have not been restored because they were dehydrated*.~</t>
	<t id="PetUsedWaterAgain">The citizen swallowed their water ration in one go... ~However, *as they had already drank today, their action points have not been restored*.~</t>
	<t id="PetDiscoveredHiddenTools">As ::name:: starts to search, they notice some kind of... *cache* containing: ::list::! ~Hmmm... This was probably hidden by a *shunned citizen*...~</t>
	<t id="PetCantActInTerror">This citizen is *terrorised*, therefore it is impossible for them to act in the desert when surrounded by zombies...</t>
	<t id="PetWantToKeepThat">The citizen has refused to drop the ::tool::! </t>
	
	<t id="Cinema">Yes, ok... you've watched it and re-watched it a thousand times, the subject doesn't exactly help with escapism from your daily life, but in any case there's nothing as entertaining as a good zombie film.</t>
	<t id="CinemaCancelTerror">Strangely distant cries of terror have helped you to put your life into perspective: *you are no longer terrified*.</t>

	<t id="OutTitle_Sunset">An ominous twilight</t>
	<t id="OutTitle_Night">A bitterly cold night</t>
	<t id="OutTitle_Sunrise">A new day is dawning</t>
	<t id="OutTitle_Morning">A fresh morning</t>
	<t id="OutTitle_Normal">The World Beyond</t>
	<t id="OutTitle_Alone">... alone</t>
	<t id="OutTitle_Duo"> beside ::name::</t>
	<t id="OutTitle_Group"> on a group expedition</t>
	<t id="OutTitle_Building"> just outside a disturbing ruin towards the ::dir::...</t>
	<t id="OutTitle_Ruin"> in the middle of an inescapable forest of debris...</t>
	<t id="OutTitle_Feist">, trapped and waiting for death...</t>
	<t id="OutTitle_Calm">, somewhere to ::dir:: of the town...</t>

	<t id="UnnamedExpedition">Unnamed Expedition</t>
	<t id="ExpeditionDeleted">Your expedition has been cancelled.</t>
	<t id="InvalidPath">The coordinates supplied are *invalid*! ~The finishing point of the expedition must be the town.~</t>
	<t id="AlreadyHaveExpedition">You have *already created an expedition*... You need to delete it before you can create another.</t>
	<t id="ExpeditionNameMissing">Please choose a name for this expedition! </t>
	<t id="TooManyExpeditions">You *cannot create any more expeditions*, there are already too many (max: *::n::*). Ask the other citizens to delete any expeditions which are not required.</t>

	<t id="Today">today</t>
	<t id="Yesterday">yesterday</t>
	<t id="DaysAgo">::n:: days ago</t>
	<t id="OnDate">on the ::date::</t>
	<t id="AtSector0">in the north east</t>
	<t id="AtSector1">in the north</t>
	<t id="AtSector2">in the north west</t>
	<t id="AtSector3">in the west</t>
	<t id="AtSector4">in the south west</t>
	<t id="AtSector5">in the south</t>
	<t id="AtSector6">in the south east</t>
	<t id="AtSector7">in the east</t>

	<t id="ToSector0">the north east</t>
	<t id="ToSector1">the north</t>
	<t id="ToSector2">the north west</t>
	<t id="ToSector3">the west</t>
	<t id="ToSector4">the south west</t>
	<t id="ToSector5">the south</t>
	<t id="ToSector6">the south east</t>
	<t id="ToSector7">the east</t>

	<t id="Regen0">Sandstorms were recorded in *::to::*.</t>
	<t id="Regen1">Our sources indicate meteorological anomalies in *::to::*.</t>
	<t id="Regen2">Meteorological anomalies were observed *::at::*.</t>
	<t id="Regen3">Widespread sandstorms raged *::at::*.</t>
	<t id="Regen4">Isolated phenomena were detected *::at::*.</t>
	<t id="Regen5">Last night, *::to::* as a whole was a theatre for several meteorological anomalies.</t>
	<t id="Regen6">During the night, *::to::* was hit by gale-force winds.</t>
	<t id="Regen7">Extreme winds swept the desert in *::to::*.</t>
	<t id="Regen8">A violent storm erupted *::at::* last night.</t>
	<t id="Regen9">Strong gusts of wind shook *::to::* during the night.</t>
	<t id="Regen10">Various sources confirm extreme weather conditions occurred *::at::* last night.</t>
	
	<!-- ELECTIONS -->
	
	<t id="shaman_role">*Shaman*</t>
	<t id="mayor_role">*Mayor*</t>
	<t id="guide_role">*Guide to the World Beyond*</t>
	<t id="electionVoteConfirmed">You vote for *::user::* as *::role::* has been lost, I mean counted! It's been counted!</t>
	<t id="electionVoteUnique">You've already voted in the election for *::role::*.  No you can't change you're vote! You'll just have to wait... Untill they die.</t>
	
	<!-- MESSAGES -->

	<t id="msg_err_user_doesnt_play_with_me">This citizen is not from my town...</t>
	<t id="msg_all_archived">All messages have been *archived*.</t>
	<t id="msg_all_readed">All messages have been marked as *read*.</t>
	<t id="msg_err_invalid_user">Please select a *valid recipient*...</t>
	<t id="msg_sent">Your message has been *sent*! </t>
	<t id="msg_osent">Your message has been *sent along with the objects* you chose.</t>
	<t id="msg_drunk_mistake">Unfortunately, given your state of health, it seems you have made a slight *recipient-based error*... *oops*.</t>
	<t id="DrunkExplanation">~[ \Judging by the writing on the back of this paper, the message below was intended for ::to::! By some mysterious turn of events, it has landed in your mailbox...\ ] ~</t>
	<t id="msg_archived">The message has been *archived*</t>
	<t id="msg_err_empty">You cannot send an *empty message* or a message with *no subject*...</t>
	<t id="msg_contact_added">This player has been *added to your contacts*.</t>
	<t id="msg_contact_isbanned">This player has been shunned, so they will not be able to receive messages from you.</t>
	<t id="msg_contact_bannedLimit">Shunned players can only receive objects from other shunned players. This also holds true for regular citizens.</t>
	<t id="msg_contact_banned">This player has already been *added to your Blacklist*.</t>
	<t id="msg_contact_removed">This player has been *removed from your contacts*.</t>
	<t id="msg_you_are_banned">This player has added you to their *Blacklist*. You will no longer be able to send them messages! </t>
	<t id="msg_is_spam">Your message *could not be sent*. Sending multiple *similar messages* in a short period of time is *not permitted*.</t>
	<t id="msg_item_limit_in_chaos">In chaos mode, *you can only send ::n:: messages containing objects per day*! </t>
	<t id="msg_recipient_not_outside_in_chaos">In chaos mode, you cannot send an object to a citizen who is outside the town.</t>
	<t id="msg_no_subject">Reply to a message...</t>
	<t id="msg_replying">~\In response to :\~</t>
	<t id="msg_no_room">The recipient appears to have *no space remaining in their chest*! Therefore they cannot receive the attached object(s). Try sending less objects at the same time, or ask them to free up some space. ~Your message has not been sent*.~</t>
	<t id="ReceivedToolInMsg">The following object has been placed in your chest: ::list::.</t>
	<t id="ReceivedToolsInMsg">The following objects have been placed in your chest: ::list::.</t>
	<t id="CantMsgSelf">No, *you cannot send yourself messages*... Do you need some friends?</t>
	<t id="CantSendThisItem">You cannot send the ::tool:: in a message.</t>
	<t id="NoGlobalMailWhenAlone">You are alone. Nobody is going to answer you, give it up. Anyways, what does it matter? You are almost certainly going to die tonight...</t>
	<t id="CantSendToAllWhenBanned">You cannot send a global message when you have been *shunned*.</t>
	<t id="MsgBanned">You have been *banned* from sending private messages.</t>
	<t id="FindHighlightOne">*One reply* has been found on *page ::p::*.</t>
	<t id="FindHighlightMany">A reply has been found on *page ::p::* (other replies have been found on pages ::list::).</t>
	<t id="HelperAdded">You have been promoted to ORACLE. ~This role gives you an additional responsibility on the World Forums! You can find more information at :~ ~http://www.die2nite.com/support~</t>
	<t id="HelperRemoved">Your ORACLE status has been revoked. This decision is irreversible.</t>
	<t id="CampUpgraded">You spent considerable time upgrading your hiding place with everything that came to hand...</t>
	<t id="CampMaxed">You don't think this zone can be upgraded any further. You have done your best...</t>
	<t id="BallNoTarget">You have *no target* available for your chosen projectile (there is either nobody there, or you've already hit everyone in the last ::n:: minutes)...</t>
	<t id="UsedSandBall">You have thrown ::t:: at ::target::! </t>
	<t id="SandBallWound">In the FACE! Your victim has been *injured*.</t>
	<t id="SandBallDelay">You were hit by a sand ball *in the last ::n:: minutes*! You cannot throw any for the time being.</t>
	<t id="DrankUselessThing">You have swallowed the suspicious looking vial...</t>

	<t id="NoInfirmaryBuilt">You haven't built an Infirmery... You little rascal</t>
	<t id="NotInfected">You weren't infected, this action has no effect.</t>
	<t id="InfectionCanceled">Your wretched infection has been cured!</t>
	<t id="WoundedCanceled">Your wound has been healed, at least superficially...</t>
	<t id="TookShower">You jump under the homemade shower without giving it a second thought. The frozen water shocks you but you stay under the weak stream of water for a few moments. In the absence of soap, you rub yourself with a smooth stone, trying to shift the mud and bloodstains. ~You try to persuade yourself that it feels good.~</t>
	
	<t id="XMasDecorationDone">You've just nailed up your Christmas Crow decoration thing. Here's hoping it brings a little Christmas cheer and raises spirits around town... Lord knows you need it.</t>
	<t id="CL_SpecialXMasGift">Thanks to ::user::, who just hung a  crow garland, the Christmas Crow has delivered a hero day to all the remaining survivors!</t>
	
	<t id="CL_Attack_Quarantine">Following a partial horde attack, the town has been placed under quarantine awaiting external intervention.</t>
	<t id="CL_Attack_OutsideZombieAttack">Tracking the villagers' scent, ::n:: zombies attacked!</t>
	<t id="CL_Attack_Devastation">Due to the lack of living citizens in town, it has been completely devastated by the zombie assault...</t>
	<t id="CL_Attack_Camp">There's been no news from certain citizens who chose to stay in the World beyond last night... But one thing is certain: they're not dead...</t>
	<t id="CL_Attack_ZombiesCount">The now visibly agitated citizens watched a horde of ::z:: zombies heading for the town!</t>
	<t id="CL_Attack_PlayerZombiesMeanwhile">Meanwhile, the corpses of former citizens remaining in town woke up...</t>
	<t id="CL_Attack_Start">All of a sudden, the source of our nightmares began to gather in front of the town gates...</t>
	<t id="CL_Attack_NoDoor">...which were LEFT OPEN! ! The zombie horde swept mercilessly over the citizens. The town's defences were completely useless!</t>
	<t id="CL_Attack_Door">...which, fortunately, were closed...</t>
	<t id="CL_Attack_NoCityDef">...but the town, being void of defences, allowed the zombies to enter without the slightest resistance!</t>
	<t id="CL_Attack_CityDef">::r:: zombies made it into the town! </t>
	<t id="CL_Attack_CityDefOne">Only 1 zombie made it into the town! </t>
	<t id="CL_Attack_LastPlayerGuardDefense">If only the others had been there to see you! You are, without doubt, an excellent watchperson!</t>
	<t id="CL_Attack_LastPlayerDefense">In a valiant last-ditch attempt you managed to overcome the zombies! Bravo!</t>
	<t id="CL_Attack_LastPlayerCityDefense">Fortunately for you, the zombies were stopped in their tracks by the town's defences!</t>
	<t id="CL_Attack_PlayerZombiesKilledAll">Alas, the last remaining citizen died before the zombies attacked... Their tongue is now hanging between their former friend's teeth...</t>
	<t id="CL_Attack_PlayerZombiesDefeated">Stopped by the town's defences, your ex-cohabitants left empty-handed and gnawing on each other's putrified carcasses.</t>
	<t id="CL_Attack_PlayerDefense">The citizen's defences, combined with those of the town reduced the damage sustained!</t>
	<t id="CL_Attack_PlayerZombieDefeated">Stopped in their tracks by the town's defences, ::z:: was sent packing to join their new living-dead friends...</t>
	<t id="CL_Attack_PlayerZombieAttack">::z::, a young zombie, opened up ::d:: with a hefty bite!</t>
	<t id="CL_Attack_PlayerZombie_WaterLoss">::name:: was seen foaming at the mouth, screaming and brandishing a large stone. Upon arriving at the well, they threw it in, causing the loss of ::n:: rations of water! Disaster!</t>
	<t id="CL_Attack_PlayerZombie_KilledCitizen">::name:: dragged their huger-driven corpse to ::p::'s house, smashed their door in rage, grabbed their head and smashed it against the wall in a bloody display of cerebral fireworks. Never forget to recycle dead citizens. Never!!</t>
	<t id="CL_Attack_PlayerZombie_DestroyedBuilding">::name::, kept attacking the ::b:: with teeth, claws and old, pointy bones, taking out ::n:: APs of hard work!!</t>
	<t id="CL_Attack_PlayerZombie_RemovedBankItem">::name:: went into the bank and pilfered the first item they could get their german bands on... We have lost the ::n::!</t>
	<t id="CL_Attack_PlayerZombieOutside">In this Horde, we managed to pick out ::z::! Dead in the World Beyond, this new zombie made new friends pretty damn quickly...</t>
	<t id="CL_Attack_PlayerZombiesOutside">In last night's horde, ::z:: former residents who died in the World Beyond came back, gnashing their teeth and looking famished...</t>
	<t id="CL_Attack_PlayerZombieGarbaged">We recognised ::z::, whose corpse we dragged outside yesterday! Isn't friendship swell?</t>
	<t id="CL_Attack_PlayerZombiesGarbaged">::z:: former citizens, whose bodies were thrown out of the town yesterday reappeared looking pretty rough... grotesque actually!</t>
	<t id="CL_Attack_CityDefAll">no zombies managed to make it into town!</t>
	<t id="CL_Attack_NoDeath">No citizens were eaten... it's a miracle! it would be fair to say that our home security was thoroughly tested...</t>
	<t id="CL_Attack_NoDeathDevastated">In any case, even the rats abandoned this ship days ago... The town is merely a shadow of it's former self.</t>
	<t id="CL_Attack_Death">::name:: was devoured by ::zombies:: zombie(s)!</t>
	<t id="CL_Attack_Death_Fail">::name:: tragically fell off the top of the wall.</t>
	<t id="CL_Attack_SingleDeath">Only one citizen was killed, a stroke of luck say some citizens...</t>
	<t id="CL_Attack_Deaths">::n:: citizens died during the attack!</t>
	<t id="CL_Attack_ZombiesAdded">::z:: zombies have been added to the existing Horde. </t>
	<t id="CL_Attack_IAmLegend">You stood alone against the world and made it through the night: Congratulations! You are legend... wait for it...</t>
	<t id="CL_Attack_BuildingDestroyed">During the battle, the ::name:: was reduced to dust.</t>
	<t id="CL_Attack_ZombiesDiscarded">*::n:: zombies* were seen in town, *but they didn't attack anyone*: Result!</t>

	<t id="CL_Attack_NoGuardians">There were no watchman present to defend the town.</t>
	<t id="CL_Attack_HasGuardiansSingle">Only one watchman is posted at the limit of the town to stop the zombie attack! </t>
	<t id="CL_Attack_GuardiansListSingle">Only one suicidal maniac is watching the gates tonight! Wish ::guardianName:: a quick death.</t>
	
	<t id="CL_Attack_HasGuardians">::n:: watchmen were posted to the furthest corners of the town to contain the Horde's attack!</t>
	<t id="CL_Attack_GuardiansList">Last night, these watchmen showed incredible courage: ::guardiansName::</t>
	<t id="CL_Attack_GuardianDefAll">No zombies got through. The watchmen courageously defended the town!</t>
	<t id="CL_Attack_GuardianLazy">Last night's watchmen showed incredible courage, it's just a shame the zombies were clearly busy doing something else!</t>
	
	<t id="CL_Attack_GuardiansKillZombies">::z:: zombies were pulverized thanks to our courageous Watchmen!</t>
	
	<t id="CL_Attack_ZombiesRemainAfterGuardian">... however, ::z:: zombies made it through our defenses and pounced on the citizens!</t>
	
	<t id="CL_Attack_WoundedGuardian">No!!! Watchman ::name:: has been wounded, the Horde got one over on him...</t>
	<t id="CL_Attack_TerrorizedGuardian">Watchman ::name:: resisted all they could, but this zombie onslaught etched a look of total terror on their face!</t>
	
	
	<t id="CL_Attack_SomeDeadGuardians">Some were killed in their struggle against the Horde! Peace be upon them.</t>
	<t id="CL_Attack_SomeWoundedGuardians">Some citizens were injured during their attempt to resist the Horde's onslaught!</t>
	<t id="CL_Attack_SomeTerrorizedGuardians">Some citizens were terrorized during their attempt to resist the attack of the Horde!</t>
	
	<t id="CL_Attack_FalseGuardian">Watchman ::z:: had no weapons??!! Was this simply a mistake...</t>
	<t id="CL_Attack_OverPopulation">The *overpopulation* of the town caused the death of ::n:: citizen(s)... And yes, the lack of space at midnight is unforgivable.</t>
	<t id="CL_Attack_SurplusUser">::name:: didn't manage to find shelter during the assault: there was no space in town!</t>

	<t id="CL_Attack_NotEnoughPlayers">There are insufficient citizens in town, the attack and restoration of APs have been postponed until tomorrow night.</t>
	<t id="CL_BuildingDestroyed">The *::name::* has taken *::n::* points worth of damage and has been completely devastated by the zombies!</t>
	<t id="CL_BuildingDamaged">The *::name::* has taken *::n::* point(s) worth of damage.</t>
	<t id="CL_BankDamaged">The assault also affected our *defensive objects*! We lost ::n:: in total: ::list::.</t>
	<t id="CL_ReactorDamaged">Our ::b:: has taken ::d:: points of structural damage tonight: this has to be repaired or we all risk dying tonight!</t>
	<t id="CL_ReactorDestroyed">The whole region has been irradiated by the *destruction of the ::b::*! </t>
	<t id="CL_FireworksDestroyed">The whole area felt the effect of the *destruction of ::b::*! I'd bet that there's going to be some fallout from this...</t>

	<t id="CL_BuildingsSuppliedWater">The construction of the *::building::* has added *+::n:: rations of water* to the well!</t>
	<t id="CL_GiveInventory">::name:: has given ::item:: to the town.</t>
	<t id="CL_GiveInventoryTamedPet">::pet::, ::name::'s foul-smelling dog has brought their owner's ::item:: to the town!</t>
	<t id="CL_TakeInventory">::name:: has taken the ::item:: from the bank!</t>
	<t id="CL_TakeInventoryByNight">Someone has taken the ::item:: from the bank but they could not be identified.</t>
	<t id="CL_BankRobFailed">::name:: tried to *steal* the ::item:: from the bank, but was *completely incapable of doing so secretly*!!</t>
	<t id="CL_Thief">::name:: was seen stealing the ::item:: from ::victim::!</t>
	<t id="CL_Plunder">::name:: aquired the ::tool:: during the pillaging of ::victim::'s house!</t>
	<t id="CL_OpenDoor">::name:: *opened* the town gates!</t>
	<t id="CL_CloseDoor">::name:: *closed* the gates...</t>
	<t id="CL_EnterCity">::name:: has returned to the town.</t>
	<t id="CL_LeaveCity">::name:: has left the town...</t>
	<t id="CL_BigDoorLock">::user:: wants you to know that the town gates will be closed automatically.</t>
	<t id="CL_Well">::name:: has taken a ration of water.</t>
	<t id="CL_WellExtra">::name:: has decided it was ok for them to take more water from the well than had previously been anticipated...</t>
	<t id="CL_GiveWater">::name:: added *::n:: rations of water* to the well.</t>
	<t id="CL_GiveWaterSingle">::name:: added *1 ration of water* to the well.</t>
	<t id="CL_NewBuildingFailed">The citizens did not have sufficient resources to build the ::name:: (::votes:: votes)...</t>
	<t id="CL_NewBuilding">A new building has been constructed: ::name::.~This construction used: ::list::.~</t>
	<t id="CL_NewBuildingNotEnoughVotes">The construction of the: ::name:: has been cancelled because it was missing ::missing:: votes. It needed at least ::needed::.</t>
	<t id="CL_NewUser">A new citizen has arrived: ::name:: (::j::).</t>
	<t id="CL_HomeUpgraded">::name:: decided to upgrade their house to a *::up::* (level ::lvl::)...</t>
	<t id="CL_HangDown">The citizens decided to *hang ::name::*! ! The gallows were destroyed during this particularly violent event!</t>
	<t id="CL_Crucified">The citizens have decided to *crucify ::name::*!! The chocolate cross was eaten by the citizens immediately following this tragic event!</t>
	<t id="CL_MeatCage">The citizens have dragged ::name:: to the *Meat Locker*, then stone them for the craic... The town has gained *+::def:: temporary defence points*!</t>
	<t id="CL_Ban">The citizens decided to *banish ::name::* from the community! </t>
	<t id="CL_RetrievedItems">The town has recovered the following items: ::list:: (following the banishment of ::clint::).</t>
	<t id="CL_BuildingUsedRsc">The construction of the ::building:: used the following items: ::list::</t>
	<t id="CL_Refined">::name:: has produced one ::tool:: at the workshop (from the ::from::).</t>
	<t id="CL_Aggression">::name:: has violently attacked ::target::!</t>
	<t id="CL_AggressionWound">::name:: has violently attacked and *wounded* ::target::!</t>
	<t id="CL_Upgrade">::name:: has built something in their house...</t>
	<t id="CL_Alarm">::thief:: has sneaked into ::clint::'s house and set off their alarm!!</t>
	<t id="CL_CatapultPut">::u:: has *loaded* ::t:: into the catapult.</t>
	<t id="CL_CatapultGet">::u:: has disarmed the catapult...</t>
	<t id="CL_CatapultSetDir">::u:: has turned the catapult towards *::dir::*.</t>
	<t id="CL_CatapultLaunch">::u:: has *catapulted* ::t:: into the following sector: <strong>[::x::,::y::]</strong>!</t>
	<t id="CL_WorkedOnBuilding">::name:: worked on constructing the *::building::*.</t>
	<t id="CL_WorkedOnBuildingSlavery">::name:: worked on the construction of *::building::* (slavery: +50% of AP).</t>
	<t id="CL_RepairedBuilding">::name:: repaired *::repair:: points worth of damage* on the *::building::*.</t>
	<t id="CL_Falsified">This entry has been *falsified*: it is now completely illegible! What could they be trying to hide...</t>
	<t id="CL_GaveTool">::name:: tried to discretely leave the ::tool:: in ::target::'s house... Unfortunately for this citizen, they were spotted! One question remains though: what could they have been plotting?</t>
	<t id="CL_DumpedItem">::name:: has destroyed *::n::* x ::t:: at the dump (*+::def:: def*).</t>

	<t id="CL_Garden">Several vegetables have sprouted in the vegetable plot: ::n::x ::veg:: and ::nt::x ::vegt::.</t>
	<t id="CL_Architectoire">"*::name::*" has been discovered thanks to the *::building::*. It has been deposited in *the bank*.</t>
	<t id="CL_BuildingToInventory">*::building::* has produced "*::n::* *::name::*s". They have been deposited *in the bank*.</t>

	<t id="CL_Death">*::name::* has been taken from us: *::reason::*</t>
	<t id="CL_Heal">*::name::* has been healed! </t>
	<t id="CL_CadaverRemoved">That's one body less! ::cadaver:: has been thrown out by ::name::!</t>
	<t id="CL_CadaverWatered">::name:: has used water to burn ::cadaver::'s corpse.</t>
	<t id="CL_CadaverCooked">::name:: decided to take ::cadaver:: to the cremato-cue. They have been turned into *::n:: rations* for the town...</t>

	<t id="CL_HeroRescued">Nobody knows how such a miracle is possible, but ::hero:: has returned with ::target:: (who was at *[::x::,::y::]*) on their shoulders! Long live our Heroes!</t>
	<t id="CL_RecyclingDone">The citizens have finished dismantling ::c::'s house! All objects found in their house have been deposited in the bank. The town also recovered the following resources: ::rsc::.</t>
	<t id="CL_RecycledNothing">The citizens have finished dismantling ::c::'s house! All the objects present in their chest have been placed in the bank. The town did not recover anything from the house itself per se, as there was really nothing to take...</t>
	<t id="CL_PetBackToHome">The courageous ::name:: escorted and brought ::pet:: back to the town!</t>
	<t id="CL_GhoulAttack">Nightmare! ::victim:: has been found *devoured in their home*! From the evidence, it appears to be the work of a *ghoul*...</t>
	<t id="CL_GhoulAttackNamed">An abominable crime has been committed: ::name:: was seen *devouring ::victim:: in their house*!</t>
	<t id="CL_UnlockedBuilding">::user:: has discovered the blueprints for the ::b::! This required the construction of the ::deps::.</t>
	<t id="CL_BuildingAlreadyUnlocked">No luck, ::user:: has (re)discovered the blueprints for the ::b::. It's of no use to us at all now...</t>
	
	<t id="CL_UseBlueSoul">::user:: has just used the ::t:: which has earned ::pts:: points for the town!</t>

	<t id="CL_Shaman_Heal">::user:: has just healed ::clint:: thanks to their shamanic powers!</t>
	<t id="CL_Shaman_HealFail">::user:: tried to heal ::clint:: with their shamanic powers, but they failed!</t>
	<t id="CL_Shaman_RainCity">::user:: made it rain baby! Thanks to them the well has gained ::count:: rations of clean water!</t>
	<t id="OutsidePurifyZoneFail">::user:: tried to purify the zone, but had no success.</t>
	<t id="OutsideSpeech">::name:: *:* « ::msg:: »</t>
	<t id="OutsideMoved">::name:: has set out towards *::to::*...</t>
	<t id="OutsideArrived">::name:: has arrived from *::from::*.</t>
	<t id="OutsideDeath">::name:: died here (*::reason::*).</t>
	<t id="OutsideNothingFound">::name:: found nothing during their last search...</t>
	<t id="OutsideDropped">::name:: has dropped the ::tool::.</t>
	<t id="OutsideTaken">::name:: has picked up the ::tool:: which was lying around...</t>
	<t id="OutsideTakenHidden">::name:: seems to have picked up the ::tool::, but where was it... Could there be a *cache* around here?</t>
	<t id="OutsideKilledZ">::name:: has annihilated ::n:: zombie(s) with their ::tool::!</t>
	<t id="OutsideLostControl">*Zombies have taken control of the zone!!*</t>
	<t id="OutsideGainedControl">*The zone is now under control *.</t>
	<t id="OutsideKeepControl">*::n::* has left. *The zone is still under control*.</t>
	<t id="OutsideFeistTime">*::n::* has left, *the zone will be controlled by the zombies in a matter of minutes if nothing is done to stop it*.</t>
	<t id="OutsideFled">*::n::* managed to flee from the zone, although they were *seriously injured* in the process!</t>
	<t id="OutsideTimeToFeist">*Time has run out: let the festivities commence!*.</t>
	<t id="OutsideEndGather">*Control has been lost :* ::n::'s searches have been interrupted!</t>
	<t id="OutsideDigged">::name:: has cleared part of the zone...</t>
	<t id="OutsideDiggedWithTool">::name:: cleared *::n:: parts* of the zone with their ::t::.</t>
	<t id="OutsideDiggedDone">The zone has been completely cleared, revealing a: *::building::*.</t>
	<t id="OutsideWrestledAndKilled">*::u:: went toe to toe with a zombie and managed to finish him! *</t>
	<t id="OutsideWrestledFailed">::u:: managed to get punched square in the crotch by attacking a zombie with their bare hands... that'll learn them</t>
	<t id="OutsideFlash">::name:: has distracted the zombies for *::d::* minutes using the ::tool::!</t>
	<t id="OutsideArmageddon">::name:: used a *special skill* to kill ::z:: zombie(s) and regain control of the zone for *::d:: minutes*!</t>
	<t id="OutsideDebug">::info::</t>
	<t id="OutsideCitizenTeleported">::name:: has been *returned* to the town!</t>
	<t id="OutsidePutDefense">::name:: has upgraded their hiding place using their ::tool::.</t>
	<t id="OutsideUpgradeDefense">::name:: spent some time *upgrading their hiding place* with anything and everything that they could get their hands on.</t>
	<t id="OutsideCamp">::name:: decided to find a place to hide in tonight. Wish them good luck!</t>
	<t id="OutsideCampLeft">::name:: has left their hiding place...</t>
	<t id="OutsideWoundedFalls">After only a few metres, ::name:: fell to the ground with a yell! Their *wounded leg* is stopping them from leaving the sector!</t>
	<t id="OutsidePetPickedUp">::master:: has convinced ::pet:: to follow them.</t>
	<t id="OutsidePetDropped">Finally, ::master:: decided to leave ::pet:: there...</t>
	<t id="OutsidePetWaitLeader">::name:: has decided to wait for an *escort*...</t>
	<t id="OutsidePetCancelEscort">::name:: has finally decided to take back their independance.</t>
	<t id="OutsideToolsHidden">Showing a monumental lack of discretion, everyone saw ::name:: trying to hide their ::list:: in the sector...</t>
	<t id="OutsideAggression">::name:: violently attacked ::target::!</t>
	<t id="OutsideAggressionWounded">::name:: violently attacked ::target::! The fight degenerated rapidly and ::name:: ended up *seriously injuring* ::target::*!</t>
	<t id="OutsideDiscoveredHiddenTools">::name:: has discovered a *cache of objects* (probably hidden by a shunned citizen)! It contained: ::list::.</t>
	<t id="OutsideTerrorizedCantMove">*::name:: seems to hat been seized by a sudden and uncontrolable panic*! It's impossible for them to take one more step... *Their journey has been interrupted*.</t>
	<t id="OutsideNewHero">::name:: has revealed their unknown potential and has become a *Hero*! They have become a ::job::.</t>
	<t id="OutsideHunt">Contrary to all expectations, ::name:: seems to have been able to find something in the zone to survive on...</t>
	<t id="OutsidePetToCity">::name:: has sent their animal companion back to town with *::n:: object(s)* on its back...</t>
	<t id="OutsideGhoulAttack">There are splashes of blood covering several metres here: it seems that someone has literally been dismembered here by a... something or other. Or someone. A ghoul maybe?!</t>
	<t id="OutsideGhoulAttackTemp">::name:: leapt at ::victim::'s throat and *devoured* them!!</t>
	<t id="OutsideCatapultLand">The town's catapult has fired the ::t:: into this sector!</t>
	<t id="OutsideSmokeBomb">A smoke grenade has been used!</t>
	<t id="OutsideSmoked">[ I love the smell of fir trees in the morning... ]</t>
	<t id="OutsideSandBall">::from:: has thrown a sand ball right into ::target::'s face!</t>
	<t id="OutsideSandBallWound">::from:: has *wounded* ::target:: with his nasty sand ball. Ouch, that hurt...!</t>

	<t id="OutsideRain">::user:: made it rain and destroyed ::count:: zombies!</t>
	<t id="OutsideShamanCantMakeRain">You cannot carry out the incantation, you do not have all the necessary equipment.</t>
	
	<t id="OutsideT1">*We now control the area that was previously condemned!*</t>
	<t id="OutsideT2">*No need to wait! From now on we control the zone!*</t>
	<t id="OutsideT3">*::n:: said: I'm the last to leave!*</t>

	<t id="cronErrorEmail">cron Error (::args::): ::error::</t>

	<!-- Newspaper articles -->
	<t id="A_NoDeath">One swallow does not a summer make. The community dealt well with last night's attack. *No deaths*. We should maybe thank ::name:: who had the presence of mind to close the town gates...</t>
	<t id="A_SadQuote">Wouldn't it be nice if all nights were like that...</t>

	<!-- Saloon -->
	<t id="saloon_incity">in town or at the gates</t>
	<t id="saloon_outside">outside</t>
	
	
	<t id="saloon_well">The Well</t>
	<t id="saloon_agora">Chests</t>
	<t id="saloon_co">Office</t>
	<t id="saloon_door">The Main Door</t>

	<t id="forum_help_tag">Help</t>
	<t id="forum_rp_tag">Roleplay</t>
	<t id="browser_first">first</t>
	<t id="browser_last">last</t>
	<t id="browser_next">next.</t>
	<t id="browser_previous">prev.</t>
	<t id="browser_page">page</t>

	<t id="marked_as_readed">All forum messages have been marked as read.</t>
	<t id="err_forum_title_empty">The title field cannot be empty</t>
	<t id="err_content_too_short">Your message is too short! </t>
	<t id="err_thread_locked">This thread has been locked! </t>
	<t id="forum_move_confirm">The thread has been moved.</t>
	<t id="err_forum_flood">Your message appears to be part of a flood and therefore has not been sent. Please use fewer icons and read the Forum rules.</t>
	<t id="err_forum_ban">You have been banned from the forum by a moderator, please consult the Forum rules and regulations.</t>
	<t id="err_world_ban">You have been given a *lifetime ban* from the WOrld Forums.</t>

	<t id="WhyDoYouSayThat">Why do you say that?</t>
	<t id="YouDontKnow">You don't know anything, you suck! </t>
	<t id="LittleLittle">Awww... aren't you just cute as a button, but don't believe for a second that we won't eat you...</t>

	<t id="W_Arm">Arm</t>
	<t id="W_Hand">Hand</t>
	<t id="W_Foot">Foot</t>
	<t id="W_Leg">Leg</t>
	<t id="W_Eye">Eye</t>
	<t id="W_Head">Head</t>
	<t id="W_Unknown">Unknown</t>

	<t id="DT_Infected">Generalised infection</t>
	<t id="DT_Dehydrated">Terminal dehydration</t>
	<t id="DT_Abandon">Suicide by strangulation</t>
	<t id="DT_Cyanure">Suicide by ingestion of Cyanide</t>
	<t id="DT_Unknown">Unknown reason</t>
	<t id="DT_Drugged">Withdrawal</t>
	<t id="DT_HangedDown">Mob justice (death by hanging)! </t>
	<t id="DT_KilledOutside">Disappeared in the World Beyond during the night! </t>
	<t id="DT_Eaten">Lacerated... Devoured...  during the night's attack! </t>
	<t id="DT_Banned">Shot in the head! </t>
	<t id="DT_Deleted">Unknown reason</t>
	<t id="DT_Poison">Injected with a poison! (Dead)</t>
	<t id="DT_GhoulAttack">Devoured by a ghoul! </t>
	<t id="DT_GhoulWounded">Your ghoulishness was killed during a fight! </t>
	<t id="DT_GhoulHungry">Famished Ghoul</t>
	<t id="DT_MeatCage">Meat Locker</t>
	<t id="DT_Exploded">Seriously smashed up!</t>
	<t id="DT_Haunted">Possesed by a tortured soul.</t>
	<!--<t id="DT_Taken">Enlevé par des Extra-terrestres</t>-->
	
	<t id="DTS_Infected">Infection</t>
	<t id="DTS_Dehydrated">Dehydration</t>
	<t id="DTS_Abandon">Strangulation</t>
	<t id="DTS_Cyanure">Cyanide</t>
	<t id="DTS_Unknown">Unknown reason</t>
	<t id="DTS_Drugged">Withdrawal</t>
	<t id="DTS_HangedDown">Hanged</t>
	<t id="DTS_KilledOutside">Killed in the World Beyond</t>
	<t id="DTS_Eaten">Eaten in town</t>
	<t id="DTS_Banned">Bullet in the head</t>
	<t id="DTS_Deleted">Unknown reason</t>
	<t id="DTS_Poison">Murder (poison)! </t>
	<t id="DTS_GhoulAttack">Murder (Ghoul)</t>
	<t id="DTS_GhoulWounded">Fight (Ghoul)</t>
	<t id="DTS_GhoulHungry">Famished ghoul</t>
	<t id="DTS_MeatCage">Meat Locker</t>
	<t id="DTS_Exploded">Explosion</t>
	<t id="DTS_Haunted">Possesed</t>
	<!--<t id="DTS_Taken">Expérimentation</t>-->

	<t id="DT_Unknown_Desc">Nobody knows what happened to you... You were found dead in the early hours, without the slightest sign of injury. In any case, the mysteries of the world are many-fold. It's just that nobody has any time to solve them...</t>
	<t id="DT_Dehydrated_Desc">Lack of water is something really rough. During your last hours, your skin began to dry out and crack, and your tongue was massively swollen. You tried to find anything at all to drink, to no avail. Some said they saw you shovelling sand into your mouth with both hands before you collapsed, stone dead.</t>
	<t id="DT_Abandon_Desc">The privilege of being an admin is that you can die when you choose. There's no need to wait for zombies to start noshing on your intestines.</t>
	<t id="DT_HangedDown_Desc">You weren't the most popular cat in town... Several citizen, your neighbours and friends even, dragged you to a construction site and put a rope around your neck. Two of them tugged violently on it, lifting you a metre off the ground. After that was done... they applauded, then they went back about their business without even hanging around to watch you die.</t>
	<t id="DT_Cyanure_Desc">Rather than continue living with this band of losers, you decided to simplify your existence... by shortening it somewhat. In short, by a day or so...</t>
	<t id="DT_Infected_Desc">Little by little, the illness spreads inside you... Quickly, the signs of the infection start to show on your body: wounds, bruising, decomposing flesh... Up until the final agony, which lasts several hours. Death is now almost a relief.</t>
	<t id="DT_KilledOutside_Desc">A little after midnight, a deathly silence fell all around you, as if all life had suddenly come to a halt. The night was icy cold... Then you saw them, dozens of them... hundreds even, meandering towards you... Their hands grasp you, grab you, pull and claw at you... Then they drag you with them throughout the night, to be devoured in the small hours.</t>
	<t id="DT_Eaten_Desc">Barricaded in your house, you had hoped they would pass by... You heard them groaning, sniffing at your door... then, nothing. A nearby window shattered. Badly boarded up no doubt...You screamed as they pinned you against your bed and devoured you slowly. Nobody came to help you. Nobody.</t>
	<t id="DT_Drugged_Desc">Drugs are fine when you've got some. When your stash runs out, it's a whole other ball game... You start shaking, then your body empties its contents every ten minutes. When your dependance gets worse, you end up losing your mind. That's when you see people swallowing pebbles, thinking they've found pills.</t>
	<t id="DT_Banned_Desc">Died in most mysterious circumstances...</t>
	<t id="DT_Deleted_Desc">Died in most mysterious circumstances...</t>
	<t id="DT_Poison_Desc">You swallow the product without a second thought... It only took a few seconds for the poison contained within to hit your bloodstream, causing your blood vessels to dilate almost instantly. First, you collapse, then your whole body begins to spasm. Then your heart stops. You have been murdered! !</t>
	<t id="DT_GhoulAttack_Desc">Argh! It would appear that a ghoul moves among us! With no time to react, someone, or something jumped on you, and rained blows on you before devouring you whilst you were still semi-conscious. Before slipping into the darkness, one question plagues you: what do I taste like?</t>
	<t id="DT_GhoulWounded_Desc">You have been fatally wounded... Your constitution isn't what it used to be, and being a ghoul makes you extremely vulnerable. It's a shame, you could have gone far with this power (or curse)...</t>
	<t id="DT_GhoulHungry_Desc">You've been dying of hunger all day, wandering the land, looking for a suitable victim to get your teeth into... But the hours have passed without a single opportunity presenting itself. In the end, you start to lose your strengh. Very gradually. It reaches the point where even breathing causes you intense pain... Then, suddenly, you let out a terrifying, inhuman cry of despair.</t>
	<t id="DT_MeatCage_Desc">Let's not beat about the bush. There are some people in town who don't like you... Several in fact, your neighbours, and even some of your friends helped drag you to the town gates... To the "meat locker". Without trial, they locked you inside, then someone suggested throwing stones at you for entertainment purposes. What a result for you! You were barely conscious when the zombie horde arrived...</t>
	<t id="DT_Haunted_Desc">While you heard the Shaman's words, you never thought he was serious. Nothing is 100% in this desert and the potion he gave you... Well it didn't work. The tortured soul you tried to help latched onto you and easily overcame your unprotected soul. It's violence and rage left nothing of you but an empty shell, doomed to be devoured by the horde.</t>
	<!--<t id="DTS_Taken_Desc">Certains citoyens ont cru voir des lueurs dans le ciel, après un flash blanc, vous aviez disparu de la surface de l'Outre-monde, quelles horribles expérimitations allez vous devoir subir avant de mourir atrocement déchiqueté...</t>-->

	<t id="IT_Nothing">[ nothing ]</t>
	<t id="IT_Help">Call for help</t>
	<t id="IT_Rsc">Resource(s) (wood, metal...)</t>
	<t id="IT_Item">Item(s)</t>
	<t id="IT_GoodItem">Important object(s)!</t>
	<t id="IT_Empty">Depleted zone</t>
	<t id="IT_Secured">Temporarily secured zone</t>
	<t id="IT_Dig">Uncleared Zone</t>
	<t id="IT_Zombie5">Between 5 and 8 zombies</t>
	<t id="IT_Zombie9">9 zombies or more!</t>
	<t id="IT_Camp">Likely campsite</t>
	<t id="IT_Explo">A ruin to explore</t>
	<t id="IT_Soul">Lost soul</t>

	<t id="Handler_Reserved_HASJOB">NOTE: This action is only possible for players with a profession.</t>
	<t id="Handler_Reserved_HERO">NOTE: This action is only possible for Heroes.</t>
	<t id="Handler_Reserved_ALIVE">NOTE: This action is only possible for players that are still alive.</t>
	<t id="Handler_Reserved_DEAD">NOTE: This action is only possible once you are dead.</t>
	<t id="Handler_Reserved_ISOUTSIDE">NOTE: This action is only possible when you are in the World Beyond.</t>
	<t id="Handler_Reserved_INTOWN">NOTE: This action is only possible when you are in town.</t>
	<t id="Handler_Reserved_ISPLAYING">NOTE: This action is only possible when you are in a game.</t>
	<t id="Handler_Reserved_LOGGED">NOTE: This action is only possible for players that are connected</t>
	<t id="Handler_Reserved_MODERATOR">NOTE: This action is only possible for moderators</t>
	<t id="Handler_Reserved_ANONYMOUS">NOTE: This action is reserved for anonymous users.</t>
	<t id="Handler_Reserved_GHOST">NOTE: This action is reserved strictly for the souls of players who have died and have not yet chosen their next incarnation.</t>
	<t id="Handler_Reserved_BARDO">NOTE: This action is reserved strictly for the souls of players who have accepted their death.</t>

	<t id="Saloon_Forbidden">NOTE: This action is not possible</t>
	<t id="Saloon_TopicMoved">Your thread *::thread::* has been moved to the *::theme::* forum.</t>

	<t id="ComplaintReason_1">Theft of multiple objects</t>
	<t id="ComplaintReason_2">Excessive water consumption</t>
	<t id="ComplaintReason_3">Insults or behaviour</t>
	<t id="ComplaintReason_4">Blockage of construction sites</t>
	<t id="ComplaintReason_5">Sabotage of expeditions</t>
	<t id="ComplaintReason_6">Never goes outside</t>
	<t id="ComplaintReason_7">Selfish play</t>
	<t id="ComplaintReason_8">Community Extremist</t>
	<t id="ComplaintReason_9">Minimal participation</t>
	<t id="ComplaintReason_10">Aggressive citizen! </t>
	<t id="ComplaintReason_11">Keeps too many items for themselves</t>

	<t id="Login_UnknownUser">Invalid Username</t>
	<t id="Login_WrongPass">Incorrect Password</t>
	<t id="Login_Deleted">This account has been deleted</t>
	<t id="Login_NoName">Please enter a Username</t>
	<t id="Login_VIPDenied">Please enter a Username</t>

	<t id="ForgetPass_NoMail">Error: This account has no known e-mail address</t>
	<t id="ForgetPass_Sent">Error: Your password has already been sent today.</t>
	<t id="NotOpenedYet">Registration is not open yet... have a little patience :)</t>

	<t id="KCreditUserCash">Gift of ::n:: Hero days</t>
	<t id="KWarn">Warning</t>

	<t id="Reported">This abusive message has been reported. ~*Caution :* any unjustified reports could result in action being taken against you! ~</t>
	<t id="Censored">Message edited by the Crow.</t>
	<t id="CensoredShort">(Edited by the Crow)</t>
	<t id="CantReport">It is impossible to report this message as abusive.</t>
	<t id="CantModerate">This subject cannot be moderated in this way.</t>

	<t id="SiteStatsNotAvailable">Stats are not available for this site.</t>

	<t id="BankCat_None">Miscellaneous</t>
	<t id="BankCat_Weapon">Armoury</t>
	<t id="BankCat_Box">Containers and boxes</t>
	<t id="BankCat_Drug">Pharmacy</t>
	<t id="BankCat_Armor">Defences</t>
	<t id="BankCat_Rsc">Resources</t>
	<t id="BankCat_Food">Food</t>
	<t id="BankCat_Furniture">Furniture</t>

	<t id="Objective_killc">Kill a citizen</t>
	<t id="Objective_ban">Banish a citizen</t>
	<t id="Objective_delrsc">Destroy resources</t>
	<t id="Objective_drugad">Get a citizen hooked on drugs</t>
	<t id="Objective_infect">Infect a citizen</t>

	<t id="crow_reply_1">Keep this Die2Nite relaaaAAAAAAted. :!!:</t>
	<t id="crow_reply_2">Welcome to the World Forums! Please take a look at the sticky threads and familiarise yourself with the forum rules - unless you want your heart ripped apaaaaAAAAAArt, that is. </t>
	<t id="crow_reply_3">This thread has gone on for long enough. Time to rip into some rotten flesh! CrroooOOAAAAWW!</t>
	<t id="crow_reply_4">Bugs should be reported to technicaaAal support! Use the link at the bottom of the page: "Bug Reports". CrooaAAa! </t>
	<t id="crow_reply_5">There is already a topic for this. Please use it!</t>
	<t id="crow_reply_6">If you have a problem with an external site, please contact that site's webmaster directly!</t>
	<t id="crow_reply_7">Stay on topic or I'll have your liver on a platter.</t>
	<t id="crow_reply_8">Public denunciations are not permitted on the World Forum. Messages should be reported.</t>
	<t id="crow_reply_9">You will all die tonight. End of discussion, CccrrroooOOAAAW!!</t>
	<t id="crow_reply_10">The appropriate people have been made aware of your problem! Croaa.</t>
	<t id="crow_reply_11">This is your laaaAAAAst warning. :|</t>
	<t id="crow_reply_12">Do not open another thread in order to repeat yourself or you will suffer the consequences! Croââ!</t>
	<t id="crow_reply_13">The spoiler taaaaAAAAAAAG is for game spoilers only :grr:</t>
	<t id="crow_reply_14">Please use the SPOIL marker when revealing advanced information on the game!</t>
	<t id="crow_reply_15">I remind you that multiple accounts, lending and sale of accounts are forbidden. Re-read the site rules for more information. Crooâââ!</t>

	<t id="MobileActionFailed">You were unable to carry out this action (required object missing, AP shortage, etc...).</t>

	<!-- DATES -->
	<t id="FullDate">::date::, at ::time::</t>

	<t id="RD_Past_Yesterday">yesterday, at ::time::</t>
	<t id="RD_Past_Date">on ::fullDate::</t>

	<t id="RD_Past_Close">a moment ago</t>
	<t id="RD_Past_Minutes">::elapsedMin:: minute(s) ago</t>
	<t id="RD_Past_Hours">::elapsedHours:: hour(s) ago</t>
	<t id="RD_Past_Morning">at ::time:: this morning</t>
	<t id="RD_Past_Evening">at ::time:: this evening</t>
	<t id="RD_Past_Afternoon">at ::time:: this afternoon</t>

	<t id="RD_Future_Tomorrow">at ::time:: tomorrow</t>
	<t id="RD_Future_FewDays">at ::time:: in ::dayOffset:: days</t>
	<t id="RD_Future_Date">on the ::fullDate::</t>

	<t id="RD_Future_Close">imminently! </t>
	<t id="RD_Future_Minutes30">in under 30 minutes</t>
	<t id="RD_Future_Morning">at ::time:: in the morning</t>
	<t id="RD_Future_Evening">at ::time:: in the evening</t>
	<t id="RD_Future_Afternoon">at ::time:: in the afternoon</t>

	<!-- MESSAGE SCRAMBLE -->
	<t id="RandomPain">
		...ggh..
		cough...
		...argh..
		..nng..
		... I...
		.n...
		groan...
		..Gr..
		..raah..
		....
		 RAAH! ..
		..the...

		bu.. no...
	</t>
	<t id="RandomCraziness">
		.. AH AH AH! ...
		..why i oughtta...
		..the.. voices...
		.gghhh...
		NOOOoo! ...
		mumble...
		..hehe...
		GO AWAY! ..
		the spiders...
		..they are everywhere...
		..Leave me! ..
		.. Ah... Ah ah..
		.. who's there?..
		..rrRRR... RAAAAaah!
		.redrum...
		...laugh..
		...
		..my giddy aunt.. Noo.. NOOOO!!...
		 and then, and then, and then ...
		..as the bishop said to the nun, what?
		..is underestimating the sneakiness..
		..ouch! pointy...
		.. What the ...
		 no?.. Yes?
		. that's what she said..
		.. No touchy!
		..Hehehehehe! ...
		groan...
		... My sainted trousers! ....
		.. oooh! look! shiny!!! ...
		... but seriously, onions? wheeeee! ...
		.. Meuuuhh.. What?..
		 alright stop, collaborate and listen...
		 so much more room for activities!
		 By the beard of Zeus! ! Ah! ...
	</t>
	<t id="RandomDrunkenness">
		... yep...
		and euuh..
		 ...2 Scotsmen, 2 Englishmen and a Canadian walk into a bar
		 .. and I...will always love yooooouuuuuu...
		 no...
		... mind..
		.. no, wait..
		 and erm... yeah
		.. dammit...
		 no?.. yeah?
		..Hehehe! ...
		... I believe the plural is peniii...
		.gghhh...
		..well well...
		..Heehee...
		..have you met Epoq?
		..now then...
		.. What the...
		 nah?.. huh?
		... or what...
		.. in the end.. you see...
		.. yeah dude...
		 there it is... what?
		.. and eh... what was I saying...
		... so you see...
		...I didn't fall, there's just more gravity over here...
		 like...
		 y'know...
		 then...beep, cleep, chimney...
		 but... erm...
		HIC...
		... what already...
		 arf.
		... thingy..
		 you and me. outside...
		...
		... and that's why it won't fit...
		...
		...best actor in Hollywood? Easy. Steven Seagal.
		..
		... but don't you remember I said I was allergic to rabbits ...
	</t>
	<t id="RandomWord">
		zombie
		cadaver
		suffering
		atrocity
		decay
		infection
		putrid
		phantom
		horrible
		filthy
		monster
		tomato
		poisonous monkeys
		banana
		berk
		exploding trousers
		fear
		plane
		pip, tiddly bang bang
		funny
		flower
		ultra-banana
		table
		fingledom
		yingiebert
		dandleban
		duck
		fistlebars
		teepee
		potato
		gourd
		giant carrot
		tree
		Father Christmas
		shovel
		how rude
		smurf
		crazy
		bzzz, bzzzz, listen
		jabberwocky
		tra-la-lah
		munch
		smugly
		Ernie
		Zinglebert Wangledack
	</t>
	<t id="RandomWordDrunk">
		... the...
		an' emmm..
		 .. so I...
		.. no...
		... well..
		.. no wait..
		 and eh... there were Jagerbombs...
		.. meh...
		... i believe...
		.t..T..Thing is...
		... the...
		..huh?..
		..you see, he was standing ON the giraffe...
		..or ...
		.. a ahh...
		.. no?.. eh?
		... or not...
		.. finally.. do you see...
		.. thingummy...
		.. you have pretty eyes...
		.. erm yeah... so yeah...
		... now lookee heere...
		 beer o'clock...
		 siesta!!! ...
		.. disgusting...
		.. but... euh..
		HIC...
		... but seriously...
		 arf.
		... doofer..
		... banjo..
		.. that thing there...
		... whatsitsname..
		.. whatsherface...
		.. burp...
		.. dump..
		eh...
		huh...
		..stranger and strangerer...
		... b'cause y'know..
		...that's numberwang!...
	</t>
	<t id="RandomMidnightAction">
		Hold the door
		Scream
		Hide under the bed
		Clench your cheeks
		Wait under the sheets
		Call for help
		Hug a broken guitar
		Pray for your life
		Sing at the top of your voice, alone
		Yell "help"
		Curl up in the foetal position
		Hug your rucksack
		Grind your teeth
		Scream and panic
		Hide behind the wreckage
		Hide in a box
		Wait calmly...
		Cry nervously
		Wail like a banshee
	</t>
	<t id="RefererStupidReward">
		your scalp will become healthier and better nourished.
		your hair will become softer and more silky.
		you will feel more at ease than an average citizen destined to die horribly.
		your nose hair will grow so long you can stand on it and strum it like a harp.
		you will become the cake.
		you will feel all squishy inside.
		you will become an influential and respected leader.
		you will have bright eyes and a shiny coat.
		when people see you in the street, they will be captivated by your presence.
	</t>
	
	<!-- Exploration -->
	<t id="ForbiddenInExplo">You cannot do this *while you are exploring*.</t>
	<t id="ExploTitle_Bunker">Euh.... is somebody there?</t>
	<t id="ExploTitle_Hospital">What's up doc?</t>
	<t id="ExploTitle_Hotel">An Unnerving Twilight</t>
	
	<t id="ExploCantEnter">You cannot enter this building ...</t>
	<t id="ExploCantEnterTerrorized">you are terrified already!!</t>
	<t id="ExploCantEnterWounded">your wounds are getting infected!!</t>
	<t id="ExploCantEnterCamping">you are currently camping!!</t>
	<t id="ExploCantEnterInGroup">there isn't enough oxygen for more than one person!</t>
	<t id="ExploCantEnterInEscort">you're being escorted, or waiting to be escorted, you cannot enter!!</t>
	<t id="ExploNothing">There is nothing to explore here... excpet the depths of your despair.</t>
	<t id="ExploCurrentlyVisited">There is already someone inside.</t>
	<t id="ExploAlreadyVisited">You cannot go back in there today... Your body wouldn't be able to take it.</t>
	<t id="ExploCantDoAction">You cannot do this.</t>
	<t id="ExploCantDoBlankKeyTwice">You cannot take another imprint of this lock.</t>
	<t id="ExploNotTechnician">this action is reserved for technicians.</t>
	<t id="ExploOutOfOxygen">The air is becoming unbreathable... you can't go on. You don't know how but you made it to the exit. There is a chance that you were wounded during your escape.</t>
	<t id="ExploCantMoveZombie">You can't do that! You are somewhat surrounded by an unspecified number of zombies....</t>
	<t id="ExploNeedToolUnlockDoor">To open this door, you'll need something that looks a bit like <img src="/img/icons/item_::icon::.gif" alt=""/> ::key::.</t>
	<t id="ExploUnlockDoor">You have managed to unlock the door, however, the <img src="/img/icons/item_::icon::.gif" alt=""/> ::key::, looks busted...</t>
	<t id="ExploCantGatherTooMuch">You have already searched this room today</t>
	<t id="ExploFindToolInRoom">You have found the ::name:: whilst searching the dingy corners of this wretched place</t>
	<t id="ExploNotInRoom">You have to be in a room to be able to do this.</t>
	<t id="ExploNoRoom">Stop running into walls, there is no room here!</t>
	<t id="ExploAlreadyInRoom">You are already in a room!</t>
	<t id="ExploDoorLocked">This door is locked.</t>
	<t id="ExploCantUSeObject">::name:: cannot be used during explorations</t>
	<!-- Ghoule Vaccine -->
	<t id="CantVaccineNoGhoul">You cannot use this vaccine on yourself, why not try to befriend a ghoul...</t>
	<t id="GetVaccinatedFromGhoul">You're going to make it! Little by little, the hunger that raged violently within you disappeared. Is it really possible that you're human again?</t>
	<!-- Shaman curative actions -->
	<t id="ShamanHealTerror">There's nothing better than fear to vanquish terror. You remove your Shaman mask and gently blow a home-made hallucinogenic powder onto their face, to induce a sleep-walking state. Your tete-a-tete quickly provokes "pavor nocturnus". When they reawaken ::clint:: seems to have been relieved from their terrorized state.</t>
	<t id="ShamanHealTerrorInjured">However, simply seeing this citizen in such a state of utter terror has terrorized you.</t>
	
	<t id="ShamanHealDrug">You unsheath your sacred knife and begin to «prepare» following a well-practised sequence of ritualistic movements. The energy flow guides you and without hesitation you make an incision just beside the right lung. Try as you may to resist the forces guiding you, you cannot stop your blade from plunging deep into ::clint::, causing a clear liquid to leak from their freshly mutilated body.</t>
	<t id="ShamanHealDrugInjured">Your fatigued spirit doesn't know how to fight your demons, and it permits you to try to suck up the liquid, which could be deadly, and you know it.</t>
	
	<t id="ShamanHealAlcohol">You unsheath your sacred knife and begin to «prepare» following a well-practised sequence of ritualistic movements. The energy flow guides you and without hesitation you make an incision just beside the liver. As a clear liquid leaks from their freshly mutilated body, ::clint:: is freed from the clutches of alcohol.</t>
	<t id="ShamanHealAlcoholInjured">These alcoholic vapours captivate you and entice you into tasting this freshly liberated liquor with relish.</t>
	
	<t id="ShamanHealInfection">You unsheath your sacred knife and begin to «prepare» following a well-practised sequence of ritualistic movements. The energy flow guides you and without hesitation you make an incision at the base of the infected limb. The decontamination process is underway, albeit slowly.</t>
	<t id="ShamanHealInfectionInjured">Suddenly an infected blister bursts. Your already scorched skin quickly breaks out in open sores and infectious germs decide to make them their home.</t>
	
	<t id="ShamanHealFailed">That's impossible... you don't feel anything, no energy, no flow to guide you. The risk of killing ::clint:: is too great.</t>
	
	<t id="ShamanNoMoreActions">You can't do that, you don't have any shamanic points left.</t>
	<t id="ShamanNeedWaterToMakePotion">You need to have a water potion in order to make this potion.</t>
	<t id="ShamanMadePotion">It worked! A perfect shamanic potion. Now it's up to you to share it with the town and prove you mystic powers.</t>
	<t id="ShamanCantHeal">You cannot carry out that action in your current state.</t>
	<t id="ShamanCantHealUser">You cannot heal this citizen. Their status either cannot be healed, or someone has already tried to heal them today.</t>
	<t id="ShamanHealRestricted">You cannot heal anybody else today. Your aura is exhausted.</t>
	
	<t id="ShamanRainDance">You perform a shamanic dance and plead to the sky to bring rain to cleanse this zone of evil spirits,</t>
	<t id="ShamanRainDanceOutsideSuccess">and the energy invested in this dance finally pays off, the first drops of rain fall on the zombies and their flesh melts like snow in the sunshine and you watch and wait until their bodies are completely liquefied.</t>
	<t id="ShamanRainDanceCitySuccess">and be it mastery of the spirit world or blind meteorological fortune, drops of rain fall on the town, adding fresh drinking water to the well.</t>
	<t id="ShamanRainDanceFail">but nothing happens. Admittedly, for anyone watching, you looked like the worst kind of amateur. To add insult to injury, you've given yourself blisters on your feet...</t>
	<t id="ShamanRainDanceZoneLimited">It would be pointless to attempt to carry out this action, as someone has already tried to purify this zone today.</t>
	
	<t id="ShamanMagicPotionDrink">You just drank a shamanic potion. Now there's nothing for it, but to cross your fingers and hope this witch doctor isn't just some crazy drunk who doesn't like to wash...</t>
	<t id="ShamanMagicPotionAlreadyProtected">The townsfolk can smell the confidence on you... As you were in fact, already protected.</t>
	
	
	<t id="GrabSoulAndSurvive">You hold your breath and scoop up the lost soul! .....  It'a miracle! You're still alive! Someone must be watching over you, because you wouldn't have bet a cent on that Shaman and his potion.</t>

	<!-- MAJ septembre 2013 -->
	<t id="YouDiedBadThief">Well there you go, that's what happens when you mess with a paranoid explosives fan. You're now splattered across the four walls of their house. It's not all fun and games though, they're going to have to clean you up.</t>
	<t id="YouWoundedBadThief">Oops! Looks like one of your fellow citizens didn't wan't you going through their stuff. Some kind of IED just exploded under your feet and launched you against the wall. You're hurt!</t>
	<t id="GuitarGaveCitizenEnergy">A little live music can seduce the ladies and restores the spirit... but you'll have to be content with the 2nd effect. Your playing has generated ::pa:: action points which will be shared amongst the townsfolk.</t>
	<t id="GuitarAlreadyUsed">Warning, overplaying is as bad as not playing at all, and one of the townspeople has already played it today. Your ears wouldn't be able to handle it!</t>

	
	<t id="LittleCatCleanedArea">This kitten is incredible, no fear whatsoever, not even of the unworldly stench of Zombies. Stronger than the Duracell Bunny and the Killer Rabbit of Caerbannog combined, it has completely cleared the zone.</t>
	<t id="LittleCatWound">This kitten is incredible, no fear whatsoever, not even of you! It jumps at your throat and delicately buries its claws deep in your flesh.</t>

</texts>

