<news>

	<!-- ATTACK DESCRIPTION -->

	<n id="AttackIntro">
		<t>Furthermore, </t>
		<t>Otherwise, </t>
		<t>Apart from that, </t>
		<t>Please note : </t>
		<t>It should be noted that </t>
		<t>NB : </t>
	</n>

	<n id="petNames" ::ignore::>
		<t>K'mere</t>
		<t>Squeak</t>
		<t>Frank</t>
		<t>Toast</t>
		<t>Sheba</t>
		<t>Click</t>
		<t>Trousers</t>
		<t>Carwash</t>
		<t>Gigantor</t>
		<t>Christian</t>
		<t>Vartan</t>
		<t>Murphy</t>
		<t>Bernard</t>
		<t>Ernie</t>
		<t>Chas</t>
		<t>Luath</t>
	</n>

	<n id="petTypes" ::ignore::>
		<t>terrapin</t>
		<t>kitten</t>
		<t>meerkat</t>
		<t>abnormally large rat</t>
		<t>capybara</t>
		<t>alaskan malamute</t>
		<t>fat hamster</t>
		<t>toyger</t>
		<t>labradoodle</t>
		<t>pot-bellied pig</t>
	</n>

	<n id="directions">
		<t>near the northern quarter</t>
		<t>near the western quarter</t>
		<t>not far from the great southern wall</t>
		<t>at the town gates</t>
		<t>near the great wall</t>
		<t>at the western wall</t>
		<t>at the eastern wall</t>
		<t>at the northern wall</t>
		<t>near the western wall</t>
	</n>

	<n id="objects">
		<t>a pile of wood</t>
		<t>a mound of rubbish</t>
		<t>a scrapheap</t>
		<t>a dead tree trunk</t>
		<t>a misplaced ladder</t>
		<t>a stack of crates</t>
		<t>a pile of rocks</t>
		<t>a load of garbage</t>
		<t>a pile of rubbish</t>
		<t>some scaffolding</t>
	</n>


	<n id="poisons">
		<t>curare</t>
		<t>botulinum toxin</t>
		<t>cyanide</t>
		<t>anthrax</t>
		<t>arsenic</t>
		<t>ricin</t>
		<t>chlorotwin</t>
		<t>sarin</t>
		<t>tetradoxin</t>
		<t>mercury</t>
		<t>strychnine</t>
		<t>compound 1080</t>
	</n>

	<n id="DayOne">
			<t>Now, I should really wish you good luck in your survival attempt. However, in this hell-hole, luck has nothing to do with whether or not you lose an arm (or worse) in tonight's attack. Just try to minimise the damage. That is, and will always be, the best tactic...</t>
		<t>Old Jack didn't come back last night. I'm sure you know what that means. *The Hordes are at the gates* ! We thought we could fly under the radar in our lousy shanty town... but no. We're going to have to haul ass if we don't want to die on the first night.</t>
		<t>Early this morning, a group of citizens made us aware of the presence of *Zombie Hordes* near ::city::. We thought we'd escaped, but they found us again. It's time to It's time to get our game faces on and organise ourselves. It's either that or we all die.</t>
		<t>Some time ago, we celebrated the arrival of the period of greatest vacuity in the history of our town. Nothing going on. Nada. SFA. Seriously, to say we were bored s***less would be like saying that Iceland gets "a bit cold"... That's all about to change though, with the *Hordes of living dead* wailing at the city gates since this morning...</t>
		<t>The groaning we all hear at the gates last night left us in no doubt. *The Hordes have found our town*. If we don't react quickly and decisively, ::city:: will be missing some citizens tomorrow.</t>
		<t>The sheer number of *animal corpses* that are seen rotting outside the town gives us an insight into that horror that awaits us... The Hordes have been groaning outside the gates. Tonight, they'll be there again...</t>
		<t>Our days of relaxation are officially over. *Over fifty zombies were seen* surrounding ::city:: ! It wouldn't be a bad idea to get our asses in gear and prepare for their *imminent assault*...</t>
	</n>

	<n id="NoDeath" ::ignore::>
		<t>*No deaths* to report from last night. It could even be said that the community has (finally) worked out how to organise itself to avoid extinction.</t>
		<t>Some citizens were sweating last night. A wave of around ::z:: monsters tried to *destroy* our town, albeit unsuccessfully.</t>
		<t>Good, *nobody died* last night. A horde of nearly ::z:: zombies wailed outside all night, but around none managed to breach our defences.</t>
		<t>Our defences ::dir:: withstood the Hordes' terrifying attack last night.  Around ::z:: zombies ! No loss of life during the attack.</t>
		<t>It looks like we got it right, since no zombies breached the walls last night.</t>
		<t>Our defences ::dir:: seem satisfactory. The terrifying creatures from the horde were kept at bay... this time ! </t>
		<t>The zombies came at us *hard* for some time, but none got through... However, don't doubt for a second that they'll be back tonight, even hungrier and certainly greater in number...</t>
		<t>Our defences made it through the night. I doubt they'll be sufficient for  tonight, the zombies are going to be starving...</t>
		<t>You heard them last night... the cries, the groans. Around ::z:: zombies. We managed to prevail this time, but tomorrow... tomorrow will be even worse... </t>
		<t>We had what we needed ::dir:: to keep the ::z:: shuffling stiffs from getting through last night, that much is sure. Zero losses - save a few houses they hit.</t>
		<t>No deaths tonight. All is well. However, I *guarantee* you the zombies will be  *starving* tonight: I don't fancy our chances...</t>
		<t>A peaceful night in town. The ::z:: that came last night hit some parts of town pretty hard, but there's nothing remarkable to report.</t>
		<t>Horde food shortage : ::z:: zombies, and not one of them got anything to eat last night, our defences held up well.</t>
		<t>We all remember the fun we had the day ::rcitizen:: christened the ::ranimal:: who lived in the town, ::rpet:: ... I'm sorry to report that *::rpet::* was found sprawled out on a construction site this morning. I'm sure ::rcitizen:: would appreciate a short message of support.</t>
		<t>A great night for some well-earned celebrations. No deaths in town resulting from the attack ! A sizeable horde attacked ::dir::.</t>
		<t>With Around ::z:: zombies at the gates last night, we could have feared the worst, but not a single one got in : good times ! Don't break your arm patting yourself on the back just yet !</t>
		<t>The ::z:: zombies from last night had nothing but our scraps to get their teeth into, and some animal carcasses... Our defences held up well.  </t>
		<t>We bid a fond farewell to ::rpet::, the old dog that lived in the village... ::rpet::'s incessant barking which annoyed everyone in the neighbourhood stopped for good as of last night's attack. Poor thing... The good news is that there was no loss of human life in the town to speak of.</t>
		<t>The ::ranimal:: which was christened ::rpet:: by someone or other was found cut in half this morning. One half was found in the well, which explains the strange-tasting rations today...</t>
		<t>There is a great sadness in town this morning following the disappearance of our mascot ::rpet::. We suspect there is a traitor in our midst (some are talking about ::rcitizen::) but it's difficult to know more at this stage.</t>
		<t>::rcitizen:: spent the whole night howling in their house, to the point that everyone thought that the zombies were making citizen steaks out of him. It turns out that they were just having a *massive breakdown*. No deaths in town last night.</t>
		<t>This morning, ::rcitizen:: celebrated last night's thwarting of the zombie hordes by *running buck naked* through the streets. "I wanted to celebrate the dawning of this new day in an appropriate fashion", the citizen explained.</t>
		<t>No losses in the ranks to report following the attack (none in town at least). "Yeah, I guess, but we're all going to die tomorrow night!" according to ::rcitizen::, a sceptical citizen.</t>
		<t>::rcitizen:: was saved in the nick of time when getting ready to hang themselves in their home last night. They explained, "I thought they were going to eat me alive, and I didn't want to live to see that". In hindsight, it was a poor decision, as *no zombies* made it into town last night.</t>
		<t>One of the ::z:: attacking zombies from last night was found *in the well* I'd strongly advise you to skip your water ration today, as it'd be a great way to get an infection...</t>
	</n>

	<n id="SingleDeath">
		<t>Poor ::name::, the only victim of last night's attack... the ever-sympathetic ::rcitizen:: mumbled, "Good! ...prick anyway... still owed me a tenner".</t>
		<t>::name::, sole victim of last night's attack. Enjoy hell... it can't be much worse than here...</t>
		<t>Everyone heard ::name:: screaming when they were being torn apart by the zombies. Evidently nobody tried to help. Survival instinct. Will you be able to sleep at night now?</t>
		<t>Everyone clearly chose to hide in their homes rather than help ::name::, who was the only person to die in last night's attack. Community spirit - that's what  we like to see...</t>
		<t>::name:: ran out of luck last night. That aside, it was a tranquil night in town...</t>
		<t>No investigation necessary : the blood in the street is ::name::. It looks like that was who the zombies were really after...</t>
		<t>Some citizens witnessed a strange event... It could be said that the zombies came exclusively for ::name:: last night. They carried the body all the way to the construction site before the dismembering began !</t>
		<t>Some say that the death of ::name:: was not down to luck... the *only* victim last night... Could someone among us have *provoked* their death?</t>
		<t>Everybody seems to be silently *rejoicing* following the death of ::name:: last night... However, nobody has explained why. ::rcitizen:: commented: "their mother was  hamster, and their father smelt of elderberries".</t>
		<t>::name:: was found stone dead in their house this morning. Only problem is... it *wasn't* a zombie that was responsible... So,*who* could have done this?</t>
		<t>The zombies didn't bother with the niceties last night... all that remains of ::name:: is a jawbone and some crushed organs which were found ::dir::. Come on, smile! They were the only victim, it could have been ::rcitizen:: !</t>
		<t>Nobody knows the reason for it, but it seems like ::name:: lost the plot last night. Several citizens report having seen them running around naked outside during the attack! One thing explains the other...</t>
	</n>
	
	<n id="ShamanDied">
		<t>By the way, your seer and resident mystic, the shaman died last night. His soul will reincarnate in one of the survivors.</t>
		<t>Spare a thought for our lost Shaman. Adieu useless charlatan!</t>
	</n>
	
	<n id="GuideDied">
		<t>Our wonderful guide went and get himself lost... There will be an election tonight to decide who'll be the next victim.. I mean, guide.</t>
	</n>

	<n id="FewDeaths" ::ignore::>
		<t>A night just like any other in hell. Our defences repelled some of the attckers, but some others made it through ::dir::. *::n:: dead*.</t>
		<t>No really bad news from last night, losses were limited to ::n:: citizens. Nobody who will be missed (according to ::rcitizen::)...</t>
		<t>Our defences were tested last night ! Some zombies used *::obj::* to get into the town ::dir::. Result : *::n:: citizens dead*.</t>
		<t>A handful of zombies broke through our defences ::dir::, we have no idea how... According to ::rcitizen::, there was a crack in the wall near their house. As "luck" would have it, ::n:: citizens are dead, but they survived. It would appear that after the attack, the citizen carefully and conscientiously repared the crack... Does that sound a little suspect to you ?</t>
		<t>We didn't see it coming, but some zombies took advantage of *works* underway ::dir:: to get into the town and chow down on ::n:: people... We should really try not to leave construction sites *unsecured*...again.</t>
		<t>Forgetting how for a moment, a small band of zombies got past our defences last night. *::n:: citizens* paid for this *mistake* with their lives.</t>
		<t>Some of the walking-dead breached our defences ::dir:: by using ::obj:: which had been left there. ::rcitizen::, who lives close by, said he had "nothing to say on the matter".</t>
		<t>No earth shattering news to report following last night's attack. Only *::n:: citizens* were killed. ::rcitizen::, who survived, offered his support and condolences to those close to the victims. Altruism ? Irony ?</t>
		<t>Last night, ::n:: citizens didn't make it back home in time. Caught by the zombies during the attck, they would have had *no chance*. Some parts of them were found ::dir::. Eye-witnesses report seeing ::rcitizen:: shouting "Run, Forrest, RUN !" before bursting out laughing and running into their house.</t>
		<t>Our defences were borderline last night : a small group of zombies managed to get in to the town *::dir::*, killing *::n:: citizens*.</t>
	</n>

	<n id="ManyDeaths" ::ignore::>
		<t>Last night's bloodbath was brought to you by the number of dead citizens, *::n::*, and by the letters *F*, *M* and *L*.</t>
		<t>The zombies found a weakness in our defences last night ::dir::... Some houses withstood the attack. Others didn't... *::n:: dead*. End of story.</t>
		<t>There were insufficient defences in lpace last night. ::n:: citizens paid for your lack of organisation with their lives. not bad...</t>
		<t>A tidal wave of *::z:: zombies* crashed against our town last night! *::n:: citizens* were devoured in their own homes or dragged into the desert... Another night like that, and we won't be here to talk about it.</t>
		<t>A dreadful night for the town. The living dead massacred ::n:: of our community during the attack. You might like to take another look at our defences before tonight...</t>
		<t>There was blood in the streets this morning belonging to last night's victims. The horde got past our walls.</t>
		<t>We need to get a move on; our inability to build satisfactiory defences cost the lives of ::n:: citizens last night. For your information, there were around ::z::  zombies attacking the town last night.</t>
		<t>The organs and remains of the ::n:: citizens that were massacred last night (spread all over town) should serve as a clear message: improve the town's defences or *die*.</t>
		<t>The horrifying assault last night cost the lives of ::n:: people. Around *::z:: zombies* ! The violence witnessed during this most recent attack leaves us expecting the worst...</t>
		<t>There were roughly ::z:: zombies surrounding the town last night ! Some managed to breach the walls, an influx which cost us ::n:: good people.</t>
		<t>A good night for our friends the hordes who *devoured ::n:: citizens* of our community. ::rcitizen:: was heard saying : "That'll be the end of that then"...</t>
		<t>::rcitizen:: broke down in tears in front of everyone this morning (stress, no doubt), so happy not to be one of the *::n:: victims* of the last attack.</t>
		<t>What a giant cock-up : *::n:: died* in town last night! A massacre to which must be added ::rpet::, ::rcitizen::'s ::ranimal::  whose crushed head was found wedged in the gates.</t>
	</n>

	<n id="DoorCriminalFewDeaths">
		<t>Let's all thank ::name:: who *opened the gates* just before the attack! With a massive stroke of luck, the consequences weren't too serious. Here's an idea, let's try it again next time for a laugh.</t>
		<t>The *gates were left open* last night. According to the register, it was down to ::name::. Bravo! In the end up it could have been worse... despite this minor balls-up there weren't that many victims.</t>
		<t>It looks like ::name:: forgot to close the gates last night. That could have been an expensive mistake, but fortunately the result wasn't too bad. It's a nice day for a hanging...</t>
		<t>What is the point of building defences if citizens like ::name:: open the gates and don't think to close them before midnight? Fortunately there was only limited damage... *BAN! BAN! BAN!* </t>
		<t>::name:: tried to *kill us all* last night. Fortunately the plan failed and our losses were minimal. I vote that we *get rid of him*.</t>
		<t>I'm sure it's not just me who thinks we have a score to settle with ::name:: who "forgot" to close the gates after having opened them. It's ultimately down to you guys though...</t>
	</n>

	<n id="DoorCriminalManyDeaths">
		<t>Last night, some citizens report having seen ::name:: opening the gates just before the attack. There are also some who say that it wasn't entirely accidental... Result: *::n:: deaths*.</t>
		<t>Red card for ::name:: who forgot to close the gates last night! ::n:: citizens died ! The question now is: *did they really forget?*</t>
		<t>What is the point in building the town's defences if you're going to leave the bloody gates open? We can thank ::name:: who caused the deaths of ::n:: citizens through their "forgetfulness".</t>
		<t>Evil at our gates... which were left open last night. Clear-cut result: *::n:: deaths*. Accordin to the register, ::name:: would be to blame as they left the gates open a short while before the attack. Some say that it was not an act of negligence...</t>
		<t>Looks like it was open-doors day in the town yesterday: *::n:: deaths* ! A big thanks to ::name:: who opened the gates, then *forgot to close them*! What are you waiting for them to do before you ban them?!</t>
		<t>Haven't you people ever heard of closing the god damn door ? Thanks go to ::name:: who is responsible for the deaths of ::n:: citizens by rendering our defences completely useless.</t>
		<t>Where is the lynch mob?! ::name:: opened the gates last night with impunity, causing carnage in town and ::n:: victims, *no defences* used !</t>
	</n>

	<n id="DoorFewDeaths">
		<t>It was really kind of ::name:: to be generous enought o open the gates around ::h::h, but if nobody thinks to close them later... Fortunately, our losses were minimal.</t>
		<t>::name:: took the initiative and opened the gates yesterday at ::h::h, but nobody had the presence of mind to close them again. Good job everyone...</t>
		<t>The gates were opened, and remained that way all night... You were lucky this time, we didn't suffer massive losses. Well, nobody important anyway.</t>
		<t>We should really look into electing a "gatekeeper" to take care of closing the gates. Yesterday wasn't too bad, minimal losses... But tonight... I'd rather not think about it. Why not elect ::name:: (who opened them yesterday) ?</t>
		<t>Well then. Let me explain *the basics* to you. After 23h30 we *close the gates*. It's hardly rocket science! Fortunately enough there were minimal losses yesterday...</t>
	</n>

	<n id="DoorManyDeaths" ::ignore::>
		<t>What happend to *the gates* ? Nobody closed them ? Do you really want us *all* to die?!</t>
		<t>The ::n:: deaths in town last night could have been avoided if only someone had hit upon the bright idea to close the gates to the town before the attack. Good job. No, really...</t>
		<t>The town is starting to be shaped by its impressive organisational skills. Take the gates for example. Opened at ::h::h by ::name:: and then nobody closes them. ::n:: dead. Continue like this...</t>
		<t>The epitome of uselessness ! The gates were opened at ::h::h, but weren't closed afterwards. Its something of a shame for the ::n:: citizens who got chomped last night.</t>
		<t>Gates open, but here's the thing... they *close* too... unless you want to cause the deaths of ::n:: citizens every evening ?</t>
		<t>The cold breeze last night was coming from the gates... which *nobody* thought to close. The smell of rotting flesh this morning, that's coming from the ::n:: citizens  who paid *the ultimate price* for your lack of organisation...</t>
		<t>It should be noted that the ::n:: pointless deaths last night could have been avoided if someone had closed the gates! Will someone take this responsilbility ? ::rcitizen:: ?</t>
		<t>Well last night was an unmitigated cock-up ! Nobody thought to close the door before the attack? Really? This is basic stuff people, it's not complicated! Seriously...</t>
		<t>::rpet::,  ::rcitizen::'s ::ranimal:: took advantage of the gates being left open to escape. Oh yeah, and we also lost some citizens. Close the door... does that mean anything to you?</t>
	</n>

	<n id="quote_optimist" ::ignore::>
		<t>Come on! Have a little faith!</t>
		<t>Can we keep going like this ?</t>
		<t>Erm.</t>
		<t>Uhh... yeah.</t>
		<t>So-so.</t>
		<t>Cool.</t>
		<t>Nice one...</t>
	</n>
	<n id="quote_pessimist" ::ignore::>
		<t>Well it looks like the next few days will be lots of fun.</t>
		<t>We don't have long left, that I promise you.</t>
		<t>Thats all I have to say...</t>
		<t>I'm saying nothing...</t>
		<t>What organisation...</t>
		<t>Awesome.</t>
		<t>Pfff...</t>
		<t>Whatever...</t>
		<t>Great.</t>
	</n>



	<!-- GOSSIPS -->

	<n id="GossipIntro">
		<t>Listen to this, </t>
		<t>That reminds me, </t>
		<t>Other than that, </t>
		<t>One more thing, </t>
		<t>Story for you, </t>
		<t>Another thing, </t>
		<t>Funny story, </t>
		<t>FYI, </t>
		<t>I meant to tell you, </t>
		<t>Oh, before you go, </t>
	</n>

	<n id="Suicide">
		<t>There is a great sadness in town. No less than *::n:: people* decided to *call it a day* in various ways. Oh the joy.</t>
		<t>I counted *::n:: suicides* yesterday. In the end, it seems tht maybe the danger isn't outside the gates... What have you done to them ?</t>
		<t>*::n:: people committed suicide* yesterday. We're living the good life here, aren't we?</t>
		<t>It is only fitting that we salute the bravery of the *::n:: citizens* who chose to commit suicide yesterday rather than face the attack last night.</t>
		<t>Suicide was very à la mode yesterday, ::n:: attempts, all successful. At least they managed to do *that* properly...</t>
	</n>
	
	<n id="SuicideSingle" ::ignore::>
		<t>nobody seemed to notice ::name::'s depression, which got too much for him and he chose to *end it all* rather than continue living with *you*.</t>
		<t>yesterday, some noticed that ::name:: was really under the weather yesterday. So much so, in fact, that he opted to commit *suicide*.</t>
		<t>good news! We can all say goodbye to ::name:: who decided to top himself yesterday.</t>
		<t>we'll never hear from ::name:: again, as he decided to escape the zombie hordes by *committing suicide*.</t>
		<t>we never thought we'd see the day : ::name:: killed themselves yesterday. They had ben banging their head off walls and eating sand for days rather than drinking their ration of water... Shame.</t>
		<t>::name:: finally made a good decision yesterday : committing suicide. "Better late than never", remarked ::rcitizen::...</t>
		<t>yesterday, ::name:: did something properly for the first time. and the last... They ended their life in a... pretty violent fashion.</t>
		<t>::rcitizen:: found ::name::'s body lying in a construction site this morning. According to them, it was suicide... Although, ::rcitizen:: couldn't explain the knife planted in the corpse's back...</t>
	</n>

	<n id="Infected">
		<t>we must try to care for our sick and wounded. *::n:: citizens* died from various *infections* yesterday. In a pinch, you could always hang the infected, that leaves fewer to treat.</t>
		<t>The town smells like death. *Deadly infections* have stricken several citizens as of last night... Do we have anything in the bank to stop it?</t>
		<t>It didn't take long for *the sickness* to take down several citizens (::n::, I think) during the night. Just *two days of incubation* and that's the end of them.</t>
		<t>Their skin started to crack and peel, but that wasn't the worst of their worries... ::n:: people died of infections last night.</t>
		<t>We don't need to worry about the ::n:: infected citizens in town any more. They all died (more or less) last night. Champagne anyone ?</t>
		<t>Our *::n:: infected citizens* finally kicked the bucket during the night. "Not before time", according to ::rcitizen::.</t>
	</n>
	
	<n id="InfectedSingle" ::ignore::>
		<t>I hope nobody has gotten too close to ::name:: lately. They died during the night from a *generalised infection*. We all heard his *screams of agony*, let's be honest...</t>
		<t>::name:: was in agony for several hours before literally *decomposing* on the ground. An infection *never* shows mercy...</t>
		<t>the smell in the town this morning is due to ::name:: who died from a *generalised infection*. Could someone please get rid of the body ?</t>
		<t>Everyone will be happy to hear that ::name:: died from their infection.</t>
		<t>The bloated thing at ::name::'s house is ::name::, whose infection was particularly invasive.</t>
		<t>If you're wondering what the dangers are if you become *infected*, you should take a look at ::name::'s body. They died in their bed last night.</t>
	</n>

	<n id="Water" ::ignore::>
		<t>*dehydration* took the lives of *::n:: citizens* yesterday. An extended period of agony culminating in an excruciating death. Is there a shortage of water or something ? Mwahahahaha...</t>
		<t>*::n:: citizens* forgot that without water, they wouldn't survive for long. More deaths by dehydration tomorrow ?</t>
		<t>::n:: citizens departed during the night. *Terminal dehydration*. The groans of agony? Yes. That was them...</t>
		<t>water shortages are expensive, ::n:: citizens dried out properly in town yesterday. Or did they just "forget" to collect their ration? Better go and check.</t>
		<t>a *dry spell* in town (if you know what I mean). ::n:: citizens died from dehydration during the night... </t>
	</n>
	
	<n id="WaterSingle">
		<t>as of yesterday, ::name:: is nothing more than a dried out corpse in a bed.  That's what happens when there's a water shortage. For some reason there seem to still be some people who think they can take it or leave it...</t>
		<t>a sterling effort from ::name:: who made a bet with me that they could survive *without water*. I won though !</t>
		<t>yesterday, ::name:: finally understood that water has its uses. A fine example of *death by dehydration*.</t>
		<t>::name::'s death from dehydration is a worrying sign. The more you think about it, the more thirsty you become, don't you find?</t>
	</n>

	<n id="Hanged">
		<t>there were some fine *hangings* yesterday, it could be said that you're being a bit harsh, but there's no point in messing around, is there ?</t>
		<t>yesterday was crackdown day in town, with the *arrest* and *hanging* of ::n:: citizens. Due process? What process ? There was no time.</t>
		<t>::n:: citizens have gone too far. Or not far enough. Whatever the case, the community decided to *make them vanish* yesterday.</t>
		<t>in our town, we try to make the most of everything we have. So yesterday, we decided to really get our money's worth from the gallows. To this end, ::n:: citizens were condemned and hanged yesterday.</t>
		<t>::rcitizen:: was with the angels this morning following the execution of ::n:: "Community Traitors". A "shining example of our beautifully decisive democracy in action" a clearly impressed citizen commented.</t>
	</n>
		
	<n id="HangedSingle">
		<t>justice has been served, yesterday you voted to hang ::name::. Well we need some kind of entertainment now there's no X-Factor...</t>
		<t>big part in town last night after the *hanging of*::name::. That's the first social event we've had in ages.</t>
		<t>::name:: won't annoy anyone anymore, especially when he's currently dangling from the end of a rope... We don't mess around here !</t>
		<t>::name:: didn't last long in town. *Hanged in the town square* and *stoned to death*. No half-measures here! Isn't civilisation grand?</t>
		<t>the community wanted to spare ::name:: from the horror of last night's attack, so they *hanged* him during the day.</t>
		<t>the town decided to hang ::name:: yesterday. It took three attempts, as they had a particularly strong neck.</t>
		<t>yesterday, instead of leaving it to the zombies, the citizens decided to eliminate ::name:: in advance. "I laughed so hard a little bit of wee came out!", commented ::rcitizen::...</t>
		<t>grand melodrama yesterday during the hanging of ::name::. The grief-stricken ::rcitizen:: tried to spoil the festivities, and eventually attempted to achieve this goal through violence and other anti-social behaviour. Onlookers suggested hanging the wretched party-pooper...</t>
	</n>

	<n id="Crucified">
		<t>a little bit of excitement in town yesterday with the *arrest* and *crucifiction* of ::n:: citizens on the magnificent chocolate cross. A trial? What trial? No, there wasn't time.</t>
	</n>
	<n id="CrucifiedSingle">
		<t>big party in town yesterday, with the *crucifiction of *::name::. For once, something happens that shows that a chocolate cross can be delicious AND useful at the same time.</t>
	</n>

	<n id="Outside" ::ignore::>
		<t>::n:: citizens missed roll-call this morning... They went out last night... not one of them came back... *Not ONE*.</t>
		<t>Nobody lifted a finger to help the ::n:: citizens that were blocked outside last night. I hope you can sleep at night with their deaths on your conscience.</t>
		<t>Some of our nearest and, dare I say, dearest were trapped outside last night in the cold and lonely wastelands. There has been no sign of them since the attack... there's little or no chance of seeing them again...</t>
		<t>::n:: of your fellow citizens likely got turned into zombie chow last night. We haven't anything from them in several hours...</t>
		<t>Some citizens are missing. They've been in the desert since yesterday, but there has been *no sign of them* since the attack. I hope there is nobody you care about out there...</t>
		<t>No news from our ::n:: courageous citizens who ventured into the World Beyond yesterday. If in doubt, pillage their house...</t>
		<t>We'll just forget about the citizens who ventured into the World Beyond yesterday, shall we? According to the latest news, there were ::n:: of them.</t>
		<t>The ::n:: citizens who went into the World Beyond yesterday still have not returned. I guess we can pretty much write them off as dead by now.</t>
		<t>According to ::rcitizen:: who was interviewed at the great wall this morning, the ::n:: citizens who went into the World Beyond yesterday still have not returned.</t>
		<t>"They're never coming back and we'll just have to deal with it", proposed ::rcitizen:: this morning, talking about the ::n:: citizens that have been missing in the World Beyond for several hours...</t>
		<t>Still no news from the ::n:: citizens who went into the desert yesterday. "Good news!" added ::rcitizen::, ironically.</t>
		<t>"You shouldn't go out", ::rcitizen:: warned yesterday. He was correct, at least as far as the ::n:: citizens who we heard screaming in the desert all night were concerned...</t>
		<t>The community starts to downsize slightly following the disappearance of ::n:: citizens in the desert last night.</t>
		<t>the ever-vigilant ::rcitizen:: informed us of the disapearance of ::n:: citizens who were outside overnight. "They tried to hide, but it was a foregone conclusion. I saw it all through my binoculars. It's not a great loss". </t>
		<t>forgetting *how* for a moment, but one of the ::n:: citizens missing outside last night found his way back to the town. They were *seen ::dir::* ! That said, they were missing both legs and they were dead in the minutes that followed. Grim.</t>
		<t>Abandonned in the desert, the ::n:: citizens who went outside yesterday will surely never return.</t>
	</n>

	<n id="OutsideSingle" ::ignore::>
		<t>::name:: wanted to play at being a Hero, wandering around outside *without an escort*. We haven't seen or heard from him in several hours.</t>
		<t>We add ::name:: to the list of those missing. They have been in the World Beyond since yesterday. It's unlikely they'll be coming back.</t>
		<t>Still no news from ::name::, who apparently thought it was a good idea to pitch their tent outside last night. Time will tell if that was  good idea.</t>
		<t>A  little clarification on the mysterious message left by ::name:: : "Don't expect me for dinner tonight". They clearly decided to spend the night outside... </t>
		<t>::name:: hasn't returned to the town since they went outside yesterday...</t>
		<t>No news from ::name:: in the several hours prior to my writing this.</t>
		<t>No sign of ::name:: in town this morning. Some citizens report having seen them heading out yesterday during the day. No news since then...</t>
		<t>The danger continues to grow in the desert, as ::name:: found out to their cost. Don't go out alone any more !</t>
		<t>::name:: has been added to the list of *Victims of the Horde*, who has been missing in the World Beyond since yesterday.</t>
		<t>The citizens clearly decided to leave ::name:: to their own devices in the World Beyond, but we haven't heard from them in some time. You guys are all heart...</t>
	</n>

	<n id="GaveMany" ::ignore::>
		<t>If you take a look at the register, you'll see that ::name:: has spent a considerable amount of time *at the bank*... Yeah - I said it!...</t>
		<t>I don't know what you think, but it looks to me like ::name:: filled the bank with useless crap yesterday.</t>
		<t>The *bank* is looking quite healthy, mostly thanks to ::name:: who brought back a decent selection of trinkets for the troops yesterday...</t>
		<t>Some were asking what ::name:: was doing *at the bank* all day yesterday... There were some *very* suspicious comings-and-goings...</t>
		<t>It seems ::name:: decided to dump all their random findings in our bank. It's quality we need here, not *quantity*, ::name::...</t>
		<t>::rcitizen:: provided some news which is maybe to be taken with a pinch of salt. Basically, according to them, ::name:: was seen sneaking around near the bank all day yesterday... What were they doing ? Mysterious...</t>
		<t>::name:: spent several hours rummaging through the bits and bobs  in the bank yesterday... skulduggery or greater good?</t>
		<t>A quick thank you should go to ::name:: who brought a decent amount of useful kit to the bank yesterday. Or not.</t>
	</n>
		
	<n id="Ban">
		<t>The community has decided to banish ::name::. Nobody backed them up... Good riddance some say.</t>
		<t>::name:: was finally shunned by the community by a small group of determined citizens. ::rcitizen:: remarked, "I know everything's going to be a little bit better now".</t>
		<t>::name:: won't annoy us any more. Not because they are dead (not yet  anyway...), but they have been banned *for life* from this community. Good luck, ::name:: !</t>
		<t>::name:: wanted didn't want to play with the others... so the community naturally decided to help - by banning them from the group for life.</t>
		<t>A group of angry citizens decided to ban ::name:: yesterday. Some community members were in favour of stoning them to death.</t>
	</n>

	<n id="Refiner" ::ignore::>
		<t>There was some great work done by ::name:: in the *workshop* yesterday. A good job by all accounts...</t>
		<t>::name:: spent most of their free time yesterday building and dismantling things in the workshop. That's worth a mention...</t>
		<t>If you didn't manage to grab a siesta yesterday, it's probably down to ::name::. They spent many hours banging away in the *workshop*...</t>
		<t>::name:: was seen all day running between the *workshop* and *::dir::*. "I've got no time, the damn thing won't build itself !", they shouted as they ran past.</t>
		<t>::name:: was certainly making the most of the *workshop* yesterday.</t>
		<t>I don't know what scheme ::name:: was hatching yesterday, but with everything they made at the *workshop*, we have the right to ask the question!</t>
		<t>A little DIY session for ::name:: and several others in the *workshop* yesterday. Is some sort of project underway ?</t>
	</n>

	<n id="TookMany" ::ignore::>
		<t>It looks like some items in the bank caught ::name::'s eye yesterday . It didn't pass by unnoticed though, did it ?</t>
		<t>A fair amount of skulduggery by ::name::, who was rummaging around in the bank yesterday... Take a look at the register...</t>
		<t>Check out how many times ::name:: was seen helping themselves from the bank like it was a free buffet. *::n:: times* yesterday alone.</t>
		<t>On the register, look how many times ::name:: has been meddling with the stocks in the bank. Did someone say *suspicious* ?</t>
		<t>Some are quite happy to sponge off the workers in town, I assure you. For example, ::name:: who on ::n::  occasions was seen taking bits and pieces from the bank... and we just let it happen..</t>
		<t>Having perused the register, I feel obliged to inform you that ::name::   is having fun with our *hard-earned resources*...</t>
		<t>All day long, the citizens were able to keep an eye on all the suspicious deposits and withdrawals ::name:: made at the bank. Judge for yourselves.</t>
		<t>::name:: calmly helped themselves to whatever they wanted in the bank without being disturbed by anyone. Except perhaps ::rcitizen:: who said: "I can fix this, I'll go to work on the Holmes here with a pair of pliers and a blowtorch...".</t>
		<t>Several objects suspiciously went "missing" from the bank yesterday. Witnesses report that it was down to ::name::, but others are talking about ::rcitizen::.</t>
	</n>


	<n id="Thief" ::ignore::>
		<t>I saw ::name:: in the passageway, trying their best to hide, but they've been caught with their hand in another citizen's cookie jar...again! That makes ::n:: times, ::name:: !</t>
		<t>take a look at the register. ::name:: has been seen pilfering other people's stuff ::n:: times. I can only make you aware, it's up to you to act on it...</t>
		<t>the most disgusting vermin lurk around this town... ::name::, for example, who regularly steals from his neighbours.</t>
		<t>rather than risk setting foot outside, ::name:: prefers to burgle fellow citizens. It's easier, and they generally bite less. *Generally*.</t>
		<t>keep an eye on your possessions, ::name:: is on the prowl near your houses and won't hesitate to help themselves...</t>
		<t>with ::n:: thefts to their name, ::name:: is surely *the* obvious choice for a hanging. Far be it from me to try to influence you though...</t>
		<t>that makes ::n:: times that ::name:: has taken stuff from your homes and nobody seems to have reacted. What do you people need? He's as bent as a 9 pound note!</t>
		<t>::name:: has been having a great time rummaging around in your homes of late... Does that not bother you?</t>
		<t>it's incredible that nobody has reacted to ::name::'s thieving ways! That makes ::n:: thefts to date... and yet I find it astonishing that *nobody* has really said or done anything*!</t>
		<t>::name:: seems to have confused your homes with the bank, as that makes ::n:: times that this citizen has robbed someone in town...</t>
		<t>Here's something for you all to do today : count the number of thefts committed by ::name:: since day 1... enlightening, isn't it? Worse still is that that's not *everything*...</t>
		<t>Multiple witnesses reported that ::rcitizen:: cursed the death of ::name::. "The thieving git was so crooked he slept on a spiral staircase !", explained ::rcitizen::.</t>
	</n>


	<n id="WaterThief" ::ignore::>
		<t>water is precious, everyone knows that. That's no doubt the reason why ::name:: likes to *take more* than their neighbours. No ? Is that not the reason ?</t>
		<t>yesterday, at the well, ::name:: looked really thirsty, having *stolen* ::n:: rations over and above the daily allowance...</t>
		<t>::name:: wasn't being a team player at the well. They helped themselves to ::n:: *additional* rations.</t>
		<t>we have to wonder if ::name:: is up to some kind of skulduggery, because they're taking on water like the titanic !</t>
		<t>have you run out of water ? Ask yourself the following question: what did ::name:: do with all the water they stole from the well yesterday?</t>
		<t>::name:: seems to be ignoring what "save water" means...</t>
		<t>Some citizens seem to be building their own private water reserves... Take ::name:: for example... They've stolen ::n:: rations.</t>
		<t>::name:: seems to be more in need of water than you are. ::n:: rations yesterday... How many will it be tomorrow?</t>
		<t>give this a go: take  look at yesterday's register, at ::name::'s page, under the *Well* section. That's all I'm saying...</t>
		<t>who took the most water from the well yesterday ? ::name::. Why ? That's a good question.</t>
		<t>::name:: really likes water. ::name:: likes it so much that their daily ration wasn't enough... so they stole ::n:: extra litres...</t>
		<t>Our water reserves are diminishing rapidly, possibly even quicker than they should be, thanks to::name:: who never seems happy with his quota...</t>
	</n>


	<n id="Murder" ::ignore::>
		<t>Good news my friends ! There is a traitor in our midst. As if the midnight zombie massive wasn't enough, we now need to worry about danger coming from within the town walls. Yesterday, *::name:: was murdered*. ::poison:: poisoning. Fellow citizens, it is time to panic!</t>
		<t>You should probably think about taking a quick look at ::name::'s body. The circumstances surrounding the death are somewhat curious... Hmm ? Murder ? Who said "murder" ?</t>
		<t>Clearly someone didn't like ::name:: : their meal yesterday turned out to be their last. The *poison* which had been added to it was most effective...</t>
		<t>If I were you, I'd double-check everything before you swallow it. It seems, ::name:: should have been more careful yesterday. A victim of ::poison:: poisoning. A crime? Accident ? Who knows ? ... Oh yes... *Me. I know*.</t>
		<t>Caution ! A murderer is hiding among us! We found ::name::'s body yesterday, who had been poisoned, probably with ::poison:: (don't ask me how I found that out). Who is the murderer ?</t>
		<t>There are more treacherous people than me in town. as proven by the untimely death of ::name:: yesterday, who was murdered (::poison:: poisoning, in my opinion). It was clean, and there wasn't too much mess, even though it seems that ::name:: suffered enormously. A job well done, keep it going, dear friend.</t>
		<t>There's been a murder ! *Someone has killed ::name::* ! And it wasn't me who did it (even though I maybe wanted to...). Which particular knave did the dirty deed ins my place?</t>
		<t>Don't bother starting any private investigations. If you wanto know who killed ::name:: yesterday (::poison:: poisoning), I firmly believe it was ::rcitizen::. I can't say too much on the subject, but let's just say that I have my sources. Treachery and treason - there's always an excuse for it. Ban the *traitor* !</t>
		<t>Regarding last night's little event (yes, you know, *the murder of ::name::*), opinion is divided. Some are talking about suicide, whereas others strongly suspect ::rcitizen::. For my money, the *second hypothesis* is more likely...</t>
		<t>From now on, in addition to the nightly attacks, we have to consider murders. ::name:: being a prime example. Ingestion of ::poison::... Looks like we'll have a great time from here on in...</t>
		<t>If you think the water tastes funny, maybe it's been spiked with ::poison::. Just like ::name:: yesterday, whose *suspicious death* has raised many questions...</t>
	</n>


	<n id="LastDayShort" ::ignore::>
		<t>There you have it, the *last bloodbath*. A tasty morcel of mayhem for a town that probably won't become the stuff of legend. The last screams of the citizens of ::city:: died suddenly at around 1 o'clock this morning...</t>
		<t>::city::, a small town that didn't last very long facing the hordes' savage assaults. The sands of the World Beyond will soon wipe away any trace of this brief adventure.</t>
		<t>Just *::days::days* since the attacks started on ::city::. That's all it took for the hordes to destroy everything but the memory of your existence...</t>
		<t>The zombie hordes did a *quick* and *efficient* job for a change : they only needed ::days:: days to wipe you of the face of the planet. Well done.</t>
		<t>::days:: days, that's it. It's extremely unlikely that ::city:: will make it into the history books. An unmitigated disaster.</t>
	</n>

	<n id="LastDayLong">
		<t>We did everything we could. The evidence seems to suggest that regardless of what the citizens did, ::city:: was headed for disaster from day one... A sterling effort in the hours leading up to the massacre on day ::days:: nonetheless.</t>
		<t>Ah ! We started off so well too ! Such a shame to bite the bullet on day ::days::... Having said that, the carnage at the end was incredible. You only need to look at what remains of ::city:: to see that.</t>
		<t>The citizens of ::city:: knew how to run things right up until day ::days::, before their untimely extermination by the zombie hordes... An adventure which could have gone further, had it not been for certain *problems* these last few days !</t>
		<t>All's well that ends well... For the zombies at least, given that all the inhabitants of ::city:: ended up being devoured ::days:: days after the assaults started... A good effort, but it just didn't quite come off. Shame.</t>
		<t>A decent attempt at survival, which unfortunately ended in monumental failure and in an downright bloodbath after ::days:: days of disillusionment. With a little bit of *organisation*, you could have gone far !</t>
	</n>	
	
	<n id="LastDayLegend" ::ignore::>
		<t>::days:: days ! Who would have thought ::city:: would last so long? Despite a dramatic end, the town held up well against the hordes until the last second. The last survivors will swell the ranks of the hordes nicely. *We all go that way sooner or later*.</t>
		<t>What an epic saga is that of ::city::, if we forget some minor cock-ups and bungling on day ::rday::. The hordes of living dead had a real fight on their hands with us! Even the last night was quite something to behold (in spite of the ... "situation", shall we say). A righteous death, my friends.</t>
		<t>Personally speaking, I wouldn't have bet a wooden nickel on you, especially after day ::rday::. Nonetheless you managed to make it to *day ::days::* ! That's quite something when you know everything that went on! Well done guys.</t>
		<t>The citizens of ::city:: officially became the stuff of legends tonight. After ::days:: days of fierce battle, the zombie hordes finally managed to march on our town and exterminate the remaining survivors.... *::days:: days*. It was still an impressive fight you put up there...</t>
		<t>They think it's all over... it is now ! After fighting for ::days:: days, with defences constructed in-extremis, conflicts of interest, last-minute expeditions, the remaining lights of *::city:: have been extinguished*. Even though some tension in the early days dampened the spirits somewhat, this close-knit community held on right up until the last moment. Not bad.</t>
		<t>Last night's carnage put an end to the the citizens of ::city::'s incredible adventure. It's not as if you didn't give it your all, and lasting ::days:: days is still an *epic achievement*! I really didn't think you'd make it at the start.You made it through the minor crisis on day ::rday::, and finally made it to day ::days::. Nice.</t>
		<t>It is plain to see that the citizens of ::city:: will not be munched quietly in the night ! Through construction projects carried out in-extremis and never-ending debates, you managed to push ::city:: far. Really far. An adventure lasting ::days:: nights. Before finally ending in blood, screaming and suffering.</t>
	</n>

	<n id="Devastation">
		<t>The town is now no more than a vast, sickening cemetary. There was nobody here last night to resist the last attack : *the town gates were forced open* and *reduced to splinters*. ::city:: is no more.</t>
	</n>

	<n id="DeadTown">
		<t>This town is dead... Flee you poor fools!</t>
	</n>
	
	<n id="ReactorDestroyed">
		<t>Multiple fires were reported in our *Reactor core* before it burst into flames. Then a huge green flash wiped out and contaminated the whole area. It only took *a few seconds* for the few remaining survivors to perish through *radiation poisoning.* What a climax!</t>
	</n>

</news>
