<quotes ::ignore::>
	<quote>Our work here is done... that much is true... but at what price?</quote>
	<quote>We've all tried to imitate the groans of a zombie, but who tries to imitate the screams of a human whose still warm flesh is being devoured ?</quote>
	<quote>Sometimes, when we're out and about, some sand moves and uncovers some remains. We never manage to identify them though...</quote>
	<quote>Have you ever seen cartilage liquify ? You don't forget that in a hurry.</quote>
	<quote>What is more irritating than a tick ? A tick weighing 3kg. We've only come across them once...</quote>
	<quote>That's three days now that I've had really bad stomach ache... I took loads of bicarbonate of soda, but I bet it's one of those bloody parasites that eats you from the inside out... </quote>
	<quote>Since they munched old Rosie, there's no need to do any cleaning ! ... Aaaaaah ! Aunt Rose ! ! ...Nooooo ! !... arrrggh nnnngg...  </quote>
	<quote>I'm so hungry I could eat my neighbour. Having seen the Zombies' vigour yesterday, it can't be that bad for you...</quote>
	<quote>One day when I was looking around my cabin, I found some gums. The ones that usually hold teeth. Rotten, obviously.</quote>
	<quote>Sometimes when we're outside the walls, shadows appear right next to us. Enormous shadows ! And you never hear them coming... </quote>
	<quote>One night, a long time ago, old Chuck saw the Horde and lived to tell the tale. When that happened he clenched his buttcheeks. They have not been unclenched since.</quote>
	<quote>The only good ghoul is a... (point not made due to sudden unexpected loss of voice).</quote>
	<quote>One day, a pastor went on a crusade against the evil Horde. It would appear that there were more of the latter. He never returned.</quote>
	<quote>We tell a lot of stories about the Hordes, but that doesn't even give you a hint of the extreme fear that hits you when they attack...</quote>
	<quote>......and she screamed all night, yelled too... And you know what ? We'll never forget her.</quote>
	<quote>What wouldn't I give to die today, once and for all, and never have to go through this again...</quote>
	<quote>Don't get involved ! Seriously ! Run away !</quote>
	<quote>There is only one way to forget : do I need to tell you what it is ?</quote>
	<quote>I always get quite emotional when I think about Heroes. They have their name forever etched in stone...</quote>
	<quote>My dog... I love him, what more is there to say ! He defends me and distracts me from this non-life... and if I get hungry...</quote>
	<quote>Why did nobody tell me that cat's piss vaporises zombies...</quote>
	<quote>Be brave or die. Why bother? Same end result...</quote>
	<quote>Facing 100 zombies, the best course of action is to haul ass !</quote>
	<quote>My favourite thing about group expeditions is letting everyone do the searching and bogarting the good stuff !!!</quote>
	<quote>I know, I know. The food is awful but at least it doesn't move when you're trying to tuck in.</quote>
	<quote>Seven minutes. Thats how long it takes a zombie to munch you and leave nothing but some bits that are too crunchy. In cases of extreme wriggling it can be as much as 9...</quote>
	<quote>A bone on the ground is a once lost friend, found.</quote>
	<quote>Who's afraid of the big bad wolf ? Certainly not the big zombie...</quote>
	<quote>Sometimes behind a great hero you find an ass.</quote>
	<quote>Before banning someone, make sure you can run...</quote>
	<quote>He who is hanged last, laughs loudest.</quote>
	<quote>What's that hairy and foul smelling thing hanging there ? Ah, it's my neighbour. (Don't get ahead of me now...)</quote>
	<quote>When I hear someone laughing, I wait a moment, then hang them...</quote>
	<quote>Cyanide... A jagged little pill indeed, but it beats listening to "Ironic" again... !</quote>
	<quote>I love escaping, changing my skin and dreaming. I often do this when I'm dead...</quote>
	<quote>If you're on an expedition and you sense danger, stay calm,  wait a second, get your Nikes on and RUN FORREST, RUUUUUUNNNN !!!</quote>
	<quote>Yesterday, Joe told the three of us : "The more of us there are, the stronger we are ! Let's go left ! We didn't go, we just left...</quote>
	<quote>When you steal from the bank, don't forget the cyanide pills...</quote>
	<quote>Slapping your neighbour is as worthwhile as slapping yourself.</quote>
	<quote>Yesterday, Jessica and I decided to share everything. Today, I'm a Hero...</quote>
	<quote>Jeremy told me : Just you watch, we're going to get them. Oh how they laughed when they hung him up by his feet...</quote>
	<quote>Chaos mode is the cherry on the cake. But the candles are your neighbour's fingers... and the cherry a snagged testicle. Enjoy!</quote>
	<quote>When the minds of others are dulled or distracted, it's time to make your move...</quote>
	<quote>If you live in a hovel, for friends you must grovel</quote>
	<quote>Chaos at night means you're right in <s>the sh...</s> trouble. Deep trouble.</quote>
	<quote>If you're always on guard then you're gonna go far...</quote>
	<quote>The watcher always misses his missing eye.</quote>
	<quote>A coalition between friends creates more problems than it ends...</quote>
	<quote>Finally, today, I understand everything...</quote>
	<quote>It is said that, "The newspapers contain the essential info from these lands... the memoirs of the forgotten".</quote>
	<quote>Reading the newspaper is the only way to find out what's really been going on.</quote>
	<quote>Traitors will be fed to the 'gators. Or they would be if 'gators weren't extinct. Traitors will be severely dealt with.</quote>
	<quote>Freedom is to be found in the white pill...</quote>
	<quote>Never forget the names of thieves...</quote>
	<quote>The soul never forgets. Don't forget it !</quote>
	<quote>Drink or die ? Why choose ?</quote>
	<quote>Come on guys, open up! I promise not to do it again... Guys ?...</quote>
	<quote>He who steals must be hanged ! He who commits someone to be hanged should be banned ! He who is banned must be eaten ! This is how the law should be !</quote>
	<quote>Always keep TWO bullets in your gun. One to take the head off a zombie, and another for yourself if you miss...</quote>
	<quote>Since Carla died I haven't slept a wink in three days. What ? Yeah, I know that was last week, but she's still banging around in the cellar.</quote>
	<quote>Everybody in town loved the mayor. It's a real shame we finished eating him yesterday.</quote>
	<quote>We had the choice of pardonning her or punishing her. In the end we built her a cremato-cue. Well, we've got to eat !</quote>
	<quote>For hours now they have wailed outside the gates. But now that midnight approaches, the citizens' insults have turned into pleas for mercy.</quote>
	<quote>Don't forget : friends won't be there forever.</quote>
	<quote>Be positive ! You're going to die. Every time.</quote>
	<quote>OK. You've thought about it for long enough : close the gates. You won't hear their cries from inside.</quote>
	<quote>What are you waiting for? Sell your soul !</quote>
	<quote>When you're in the midst of chaos, trust your instinct.</quote>
	<quote>There are no holy wars. There are no wars. There is no time.</quote>
	<quote>When they tell you black, think white. When they tell you white, think black. When this goes on for too long, just go without gloves.</quote>
	<quote>Carnage... Defeat... Treason... Cowardice... These are the words of the day.</quote>
	<quote>Do you really think that others are thinking of you ? No, they're thinking, "Bite Me!"</quote>
</quotes>
