<futureReleases ::ignore::>
	<!--
	<future major="1" name="Les veilleurs" icon="item_watergun_opt_3">
		Formez les rangs, ouvrez l'oeil, faîtes vos prières, vous êtes en première ligne pour résister à l'attaque
		des zombies ! Tous saluent votre héroïsme, la plupart du temps à titre posthume...
		Devenez veilleurs dans la saison 6 de Hordes !
	</future>
	-->
	<future icon="r_explor" name="Major Events"/>
	<future icon="r_surgrp" name="Specialities"/>
	<future icon="item_basic_suit_dirt" name="New professions"/>
	<future icon="r_buildr" name="New buildings"/>
</futureReleases>

<releases ::ignore::>
	<release version="4.7" name="Enter the Sandman">
		<item major="1" name="News">
			<p>You've barely got your head around this whole democracy thing and boom! It's coming for you again!</p>
			<p>Vote for the Guide to the World Beyond! This new role will help you organise your expeditions and grant you an extra control point for each person in their zone.</p>
			<p>The big return of the Firewords building. This time round it's a permanent building, bring your sunglasses next time your come past...</p>
			<p>There's a new win for the Towns ranked 15-35.</p>
		</item>
		
		<item name="Improvements">
			<ul>
				<li>The technician can now use their construction points to improve their own houses...</li>
				<li>The technician can open a container with nothing but their bear (sic) hands and their construction points.</li>
				<li>No more violent drunks on the town forums.</li>
			</ul>
		</item>
		
		<item name="Minor">
			<ul>
				<li>The voting system has had a makeover! Now the person who receives the most votes will be elected each time (not like some places eh). The non voters will still have their votes given out to whoever. Vote or DIE!</li>
				<li>Voting now appears in your list of daily actions. No excuses people!</li>
				<li>We fidddles with the Pro Watchmen hero upgrade. Now you have less survival chancem but better resistance to fatigue.</li>
				<li>No more hijacking the {habitant} format on the forums.</li>
			</ul>
		</item>
		
		<item name="BugFixes">
			<p>With about as much order as a Black Friday stampede: </p>
			<ul>
				<li>The technician now actually receives his wins as soon as he uses his construction points.</li>
				<li>Using an object in escort mode has been fixed, particularly with the Shamanic Potion.</li>
				<li>The night penalty on depleted ares is now calculated and applied correctly.</li>
				<li>The tortured souls in dead citizens chests are now counted in the attack. Get em outta there!</li>
				<li>Fixes to the CSS in general. Game less ugly.</li>
				<li>You can now see the gazette correctly from the World Beyond.</li>
			</ul>
		</item>
	</release>
	
	<release version="4.6" name="Demonocracy!">
		<item major="1" name="New Stuff!!!!">
			<p>The Shaman is loved by many reviled by an equal if not more vociferous bunch... So we've made some changes. We're unveiling the electoral office, the place to go to vote for the Shaman and take the power back from the god of RNG.</p>
			<p>Don't forget to vote though otherwise your votes will be distributed randomly.</p>
			<p>Heroes can vote via carrier pigeon from anywhere on the map.</p>
			<p>Small towns no longer have to deal with the Shaman. We've made them easier for the  new players... But.</p>
			<p>CAMPING is back for the small maps! A lot of people have complained about not being able to show the new players a good deal of the game and we're running a test just on the EN server to see if this is a good thing or not.</p>
		</item>
		
		<item name="Improvements...">
			<p></p>
			<ul>
				<li>Heroes with the "Mayor" bonus can now create private towns that are even more unique, you can control everything (although from memory I haven't finished translating the interface).</li>
				<li>Tortured Souls still need to be recovered, but they won't be as violent as before. The attack should be more balanced now...</li>
				<li>Souls will now be generated at more manageable distances from the town...</li>
				<li>Purified souls count towards the defence of the town.</li>
				<li>Souls kept in your house will give you a personal defence bonus.</li>
				<li>The meat locker now takes priority over the gallows, if both have been built.</li>
				<li>Drunks now have "a chance" of randomly wounding a person when posting on the forums. This costs 1 AP as being an aggressive drunk takes energy none the less...</li>
				<li>You can no longer repair a project if it's parent project has been destroyed.</li>
				<li>You now have the {habitant} option in the text field.</li>
				<li>Some of the smileys are back. :pc:, :pm: et :def: </li>
			</ul>
		</item>
		
		<item name="Minor changes">
			<ul>
				<li>The attack estimations are now more... Precise...</li>
				<li>The external API now gives direct access to a zone.</li>
				<li>Added some explanation for when a payer has been elected as Shaman.</li>
				<li>Added a popup that let's you know when you've passed 100 soul points. This way you know when you're no longer a complete noob.</li>
				<li>Got rid of the basic view for the construction sites. You'r in detailed view by default now.</li>
				<li>Fixed a problem relating to the chance of being wounded or terrorised during the attack.</li>
				<li>Added some distinctions and such for being wounded in town..</li>
				<!--<li>Distribution des pictos en cas de blessure en veille.</li>-->
			</ul>
		</item>
		
		<item name="We fixed some bugs... Finally!">
			<p>In no particular order: </p>
			<ul>
				<li>If a player is wounded or terrorised in a ruin, they are immediately ejected.</li>
				<li>Added the general register for D1 in the Gazette.</li>
				<li>Changes the name of the "Shaman points" (this might not be visible till tomorrow).</li>
				<li>Improved the creation of post-it threads in the town forums.</li>
				<li>Fixed the double soul in the bank problem.</li>
				<li>Fixed the disappearing Shamanic Potion.</li>
				<li>Ended the 'pre-vote' for the wall upgrade.</li>
				<li>The Day 8 rule has been refined. You need to reach the attack on the night of day 7 and die from something directly related to this attack in town. For example: being on the watch, when the watch is overrun, a body not being dragged out of town that comes to life and kills you...</li>
				<li>The Day 8 rule now correctly take into account the points accumulated from the beginning of the town.</li>
				<li>The laser point won't go off by itself now.</li>
				<li>Slightly changed the way rankings are calculated.</li>
				<li>Objects lost by citizens who were auto-searching and don't log back in are now left on the ground.</li>
			</ul>
		</item>
	</release>
	
	<release version="4.5" name="Save our souls!">
		<item major="1" name="The witch doctor is back">
			<p>Lost souls wandering the desert, waiting to be found... They're back this season and what's more, the Shaman will reincarnate in town to help you find the lost and bring them home.</p>
			<p>But watch out! It's not going to be like last time... The new version will leave you all feeling a little mystic. Whether you're a citizen or a hero, you'll have the chance to shepard the souls of the lost... </p>
		</item>
		<item major="1" name="Ranking">
			<p>We're changing up the way we calculate the town rankings.</p>
			<p>Going inactive is unfortunately an unavoidable nuisance imposed on us from time to time by 'responsibilities' and such. However it can be a real pain for glory seeking citizens hellbent on ranking. For this reason we're only counting the top 35 players in each town when we calculate the rankings.</p>
		</item>
		<item name="Hardcore">
			<p>Yes yes. This mode is only for the badest of badasses, the survivors and the mad. We've been listening.</p>
			<ul>
				<li>Our most dedicated players are capable of anything... However for their sanity we're opening up the Twinoid API to Hardcore towns. (just to be clear only the Twinoid API is available).</li>
				<li>Being a Watchman just got a little more risky.</li>
				<li>Playing Indiana Jones in ruins out of town will require even more skill from now on... Hold onto your hats!</li>
				<li>Just like you're not supposed to feed the Gremlins after midnight, you should NEVER, EVER, EVER leave tortured souls in the desert after midnight.</li>
				<li>Agression is less... Costly, than it once was.</li>
			</ul>
		</item>
		<item name="Worship the Watchmen">
			<p>the watchmen haven't been forgotten. From now on the townsfolk will have to work on a small construction site before they can access the night's watch. Who knows what this could be used for in the future...)</p>
			<p>The weapons of the watch have been slightly recalibrated.</p>
		</item>
		
		<item name="Improvements...">
			<ul>
				<li>The picto 'message' is now available from commenting on the forums (again).</li>
				<li>The use of defensive objects is now easier to get to from a basic construction site.</li>
				<li>Ruins are now closer to town (except for the Hardcore folks) which should make it easier for beginners and the less organised.</li>
			</ul>
		</item>
		
		<item name="Bugfixes">
			<ul>
				<li>Fixes relating to private towns.</li>
				<li>Added an option to disable the API flow for anyone who's interrested...</li>
				<li>Small tinkerings for some maps.</li>
				<li>A littel bit of CSS here, a little bit of Java Script there, and presto oit's pretty!</li>
				<li>Fixed a few bugs relating to some items during the watch.</li>
				<li>Cleaned up some texts.</li>
				<li>Fixed a few security loopholes (thank you MR Uruguay).</li>
				<li>Other little things just to make you happy. (And I, Buzzard, translated all of this goodness for your reading pleasure!)</li>
			</ul>
		</item>
	</release>

	<release version="4.4" name="Dev's not dead">
		<item major="1" name="Gameplay updates!">
			The attacks will be even more violent this season... No mercy from the very first day. Less immunity for the cowards who hide under their beds.
		</item>
		<item name="Simplification of the Non-Distant Regions.">
			<ul>
				<li>a few less zombies.</li>
				<li>buildings are further away (distance = 3).</li>
				<li>no dead-heads near the town.</li>
				<li>no advanced ruins (explorable).</li>
				<li>reduced number of buildings.</li>
				<li>no camping.</li>
			</ul>
		</item>
		<item name="Evolution for the heroes">
			<p>Become a Pro-Watchman and increase you chances of surving a watch.</p>
		</item>
		<item name="Updated help">
			<p>We've dusted of the help section of the game and updated it so as to make it your go to guide for surviving in the outer-world (uf yo notice any errors report it to your mods, they know what to do...)</p>
		</item>
		<item name="New texts to find">
			<p>The chronicals of Die2Nite get even thicker with a good dozen more chapters to find.</p>
		</item>
		<item name="New titles to unlock">
			<p>The titles for your miraculous achievements hae been stacked on... Will you be able to climb to the top of the new pile?</p>
		</item>
		<!--
		<item name="Evolution de l'Apprivoiseur">
			<p>Le bichon, fidèle compagnon de l'Apprivoiseur obtient un nouveau pouvoir héroïque :
			<em>il peut désormais ramener le contenu du coffre de l’apprivoiseur sur la case où se trouve son maître, où qu'il soit dans l'Outre-monde.</em>
			</p>
		</item>
		-->
		<item name="Loads of little bug fixes and calibrations">
			<ul>
				<li>Watches: We've added the idea of caccumulated fatigue. You lose 10% chance of survial with every night spent on lookout. You recover 5% with every night you rest.</li>
				<li>The return of Defensive Objects as an alternative for defence. Defensive focus offers the best conversion rate over 5 evolutions.</li>
				<li>Terrified? you'll find it harder to recover nowadays. (showers are less effective for a example).</li>
				<li>Worksite architecture evolves.</li>
				<li>Theft from the bank is back in Pandemonium (same rules in Distant Regions).</li>
				<li>Adjustments on worksites (no details here because it could change).</li>
				<li>correction of the Architects Chest in the Non-Distant Regions which bugged out occasionally</li>
				<li>Improvements and corrections in the logs of watchmen</li>
				<li>Reusing Earplugs willnow reduce terror (Effect non-accumulable).</li>
				<li>correction boobytrapped Doormat.</li>
				<li>correction of the state "immunised".</li>
				<li>correction and improvement of the objects Staff AND Brocken Staff.</li>
				<li>corrections of the CSS and general appearence...</li>
			</ul>
		</item>
	</release>

	<release version="4.3" name="Villa nostra">
		<item major="1" name="Private towns have evolved">
			From now on, the crow will be able to configure private towns exactly as the community wish them to be!
			Remember your liver is at risk, as they also have the ability to kill you instantly if your actions are not deemed acceptable in these event towns.
		</item>
		<item name="Night's watch re-balancing">
			The watch has been altered slightly as to favour construction of defensive structures.
			The attack curve has also been modified to avoid an excess of zombies at the town walls.
		</item>
		<item name="New texts to be found in the World Beyond">
			<p>The chronicles of Die Verdammten have been boosted by another dozen or more roleplay texts.</p>
		</item>
		<!--
		<item name="Evolution de l'Apprivoiseur">
			<p>Le bichon, fidèle compagnon de l'Apprivoiseur obtient un nouveau pouvoir héroïque :
			<em>il peut désormais ramener le contenu du coffre de l’apprivoiseur sur la case où se trouve son maître, où qu'il soit dans l'Outre-monde.</em>
			</p>
		</item>
		-->
		<item name="Lots of minor bug corrections too:">
			<ul>
				<li>The burning laser pointer now shows the number of charges remaining.</li>
				<li>Poisoned cans will no longer be able to be distinguished by the night's watch.</li>
				<li>The Spy Flares won't cause bugs when all buildings have been discovered.</li>
				<li>The + button in the private town rankings now functions correctly.</li>
				<li>It's now possible to share a link towards the game help.</li>
				<li>Several more minor fixes...</li>
			</ul>
		</item>
	</release>
	
	<release version="4.2" name="Sleight of Hand">
		<item major="1" name="Twinoid Applications">
			The developers amongst you will be happy to hear that Die2Nite will now benefit from the Twinoid application engine which will allow applications to be developed for Die2Nite.
			Validation carried out by appointed community members will mean that applications will be validated more quickly and be much better looked after.
			
			No applications using the XML feed will be validated from now on and we strongly encourage developers to make this alteration for their application.
			Documentation for this new application engine can be found here: <a href="http://twinoid.com/developers/api">http://twinoid.com/developers/api</a> et <a href="http://die2nite.com/tid/api">http://die2nite.com/tid/api</a>
		</item>
		<item name="New objects to be found">
			New objects will appear little by little in the World Beyond.
			These objects may be combined with others to create astonishing results, wil you manage to find all the combinations?
		</item>
		<item name="Lots of minor bug corrections">
			<ul>
				<li>Undefined meat no longer transforms citizens into ghouls.</li>
				<li>Negative watchmen defense bug corrected.</li>
				<li>Bugs with double deaths, injuries, and negative survival chances on the night's watch have been corrected.</li>
				<li>The Kalashni-Splash now works correctly in the World Beyond.</li>
				<li>The forum bug arising from the consumption of alcohol has been corrected.</li>
				<li>The Devastator now has the same functionality as the MARK II Battery Launcher.</li>
				<li>It's no longer possible to attack and wound a citizen twice.</li>
				<li>Ruins now give twice as many plans.</li>
				<li>The Technician now earns stat points when repairing constructions. </li>
				<li>Small towns now begin with some basic buildings.</li>
				<li>A drunk ghoul who devours a drunk citizen will now have a 'double-drunk' status!</li>
			</ul>
		</item>
	</release>

	<release version="4.1" name="Insidious Bugs">
		<item major="1" name="New texts to be found">
			<p>The litany of Die2Nite becomes even richer than before with many new texts to be found.</p>
		</item>
		<item major="1" name="The Watchmen will remain at their posts">
			<p>The bugs relating to the nights watch have been corrected.
			Certain objects collected for use in a watch or otherwise occasionally disappeared without giving the correct defensive bonus.
			Objects in chests didn't disappear after a watch.</p>
			<p>The defense taking into account the statuses of the watchmen is worked out prior to the attack.</p>
		</item>
		<item name="Construction Modifications">
			<p>Certain construction sites have undergone slight modifications:</p>
			<ul>
				<li>The Moat is no longer a temporary construction.</li>
				<li>The Gallows is no longer a temporary construction.</li>
				<li>The Meat Locker is now a standard plan available immediately.</li>
				<li>The Water Turret now gives a 20% bonus to all water weapons used during the nights watch.</li>
				<li>The Small Trebuchet now gives a 20% bonus for animals used, and also stops watchmen becoming terrified during a watch.</li>
			</ul>
		</item>
		<item name="Blueprints">
			<p>Ruins in the World Beyond now offer more plans to citizens righteous enough to explore their darkest corners.</p>
		</item>
		<item name="A Kick to the Ghouls">
			<p>Common suspicious objects no longer transform hungry citizens into ghouls, however, the traveller's corpse has a 90% chance of ghoulifying a citizen.
			Be careful where you sink your teeth...</p>
		</item>
		<item name="Picto Hunters">
			<p>Certain players have shamelessly exploited a flaw in the game which allowed them to suicide and still gain all the goodies they shouldn't have gotten on the first day.
			<em>These players have earned the right to be ineligible for the new distinction: <img src="/gfx/icons/r_goodg.gif" alt=""/> Good Guy.</em><br/>
			Ain't karma beautiful, baby?</p>
		</item>
		<!--
		<item name="Evolution de l'Apprivoiseur">
			<p>Le bichon, fidèle compagnon de l'Apprivoiseur obtient un nouveau pouvoir héroïque :
			<em>il peut désormais ramener le contenu du coffre de l’apprivoiseur sur la case où se trouve son maître, où qu'il soit dans l'Outre-monde.</em>
			</p>
		</item>
		-->
	</release>
	
	<release version="4.0" name="Death Watch">
		<item major="1" name="The Watchmen">
			<p>You now have the opportunity to put yourself in the front line when the attack comes. Try to make it back alive!</p>
			<p>To help you along, several weapons and forms of protection are available to you; a mattress, car door, water pistol? Anything is possible!</p>
		</item>
		<item major="1" name="Blueprint recalibration">
			<p>The rarities of certain plans have been reviewed, some are now available immediately in new towns.</p>
		</item>
		<item major="1" name="Construction recalibration">
			<p>Resource requirements have been reviewed, which should make for a more coherent construction system.</p>
		</item>
		<item major="1" name="Ghoul and the Gang">
			<p>Ghouls are partially infected citizens, but who are not completely transformed into zombies.
			You don't become a ghoul through bad luck alone, but be careful, you can easily become one by feasting on traveller's corpse or other less-then-conventional foods...
			Will you chance your arm? (literally...)
			</p>
		</item>
		<item name="Evolution of the Guardian">
			<p>The Guardians now have a better chance of surviving the night's watch than their fellow watchmen, they also contribute even more to the town defenses!<br/>
			Take on your true role, as the guardian of the town, and keep the townspeople safe from harm!
			</p>
		</item>
		<!--
		<item name="Evolutions de l'Apprivoiseur">
			<p>Le bichon, fidèle compagnon de l'Apprivoiseur obtient un nouveau pouvoir héroïque :
			<em>il peut désormais ramener le contenu du coffre de l’apprivoiseur sur la case où se trouve son maître, où qu'il soit dans l'Outre-monde.</em>
			</p>
		</item>
		
		<item name="Le Chaman était poussière et redevient poussière">
			<p>Le Chaman ne fait plus partie du choix des métiers.<br/>
			les âmes s'évanouïront désormais et rejoindront les abîmes infinies au lieu de vagabonder dans le désert.
			Les titres en rapport avec le Chaman et les âmes existent toujours mais ne donnent plus aucuns points Twinoid.
			</p>
		</item>
		-->
		<item name="Unforgiving Wastelands">
			<p>The chance of finding something to eat or drink in the World Beyond will diminish as time goes on.
			Nobody can resist the relentless onslaught from the World Beyond forever, once your town has been devastated, alia iacta est!
			</p>
		</item>
		<item name="Pandemonium Ruins">
			Two ruins will appear in the desert of the World Beyond in Pandemonium towns.
			The nightmare just lasts a little longer!
		</item>
	</release>	
	
	<release version="3.2" name="Shamanic Monday">
		<item major="1" name="Lost Souls">
			<p>When a citizen dies, their soul will appear in the desert of the World Beyond.
			If it is found by a town resident, they can collect it and bring it to the town bank.
			These souls give points to the town on its last day.</p>
			<p>These souls can also be converted into special constructions giving temporary defences if there is a Shaman in the town.</p>
			<div class="helpLink"><a href="/#help?id=soul" alt="">Read more...</a></div>
		</item>
		<item major="1" name="The Shaman">
			<p>A new profession appears!<br/> The Shaman can direct citizens to the souls of their former townmates using their voodoo mask	which shows the souls of freshly deceased citizens on the map..</p>
			<p>The Shaman is able to:</p>
			<ul>
				<li>transport as many souls as their inventory allows.</li>
				<li>to transform blue souls into red souls which can be used by the town to construct special temporary defences.</li>
			</ul>
			<div class="helpLink"><a href="/#help?id=job_shaman" alt="">Read more...</a></div>
		</item>
		<item major="1" name="New Leaderboard">
			<p>Over and above the global rankings, there is now a ranking of soul points earned for each season. This will show the top survivir of each season.</p>
			<p>The global ranking now displays all souls.</p>
			<div class="helpLink"><a href="/#help?id=seasons" alt="">read more...</a></div>
		</item>
 		<item name="Evolution of the Tamer">
			The labradoodle, fearless companion of the Tamer, now shows their master the way out of the ruins, a blue arrow appears to ensure that their master never again loses their bearings.
		</item>
		<item name="Evolution of the Technician">
			The Technician can now use their Construction Points (CP) to repair buildings and to transform / refine objects in the workshop.
		</item>
		<item name="Survivalist Restriction">
			The Survivalist, being a cantankerous neurotic with sociopathic tendencies, will not find food or water unless they are at a distance of 3km or more from the town.
		</item>
		<item name="Modifications to the Dump">
			The basic dump can now be built from a common blueprint.
			This will now allow you to use all objects to gain defences. New dump blueprints now increase the number of defence points given by the corresponding resources.
		</item>
		<item name="A new way to play in NDRs">
			Distinctions in non-distant regions will only be availble to experienced players as of day 8. However, they will earn new distinctions by making the town last as long as possible.
			<div class="helpLink"><a href="/#help?id=rne" alt="">read more...</a></div>
		</item>
		<item name="Another shovelful of updates">
			<ul>
				<li>The zombie attack curve has been revised</li>
				<li>New temporary constructions linked to the Shaman have been added</li>
				<li>New titles to unlock</li>
			</ul>
		</item>
	</release>	
	
	<release version="3.1" name="Going Underground">
		<item major="1" name="Abandoned Buildings" help="explo">
			<p>From now on you will be able to explore 3 types of buildings which you'll find scattered throughout the World Beyond:</p>
			<ul>
				<li>Bunkers: former centers of research and experimentation into the zombie menace, these buildings are nothing but zombie-infested mazes concealing a wealth of useful resources!</li>
				<li>Hospitals: back when humans still worried about their natural life expectancy, they constructed vast buildings at the cutting edge of medical technology. Since the attack of the zombie hordes, these places are only good for scavenging - on the plus side, you'll find almost everything here!</li>
				<li>Motels: huge, deluxe hotels where the wealthy thought they could escape the inevitable, these places reward the most daring explorers.</li>
			</ul>
			<em>You will find one building placed randomly on standard maps, and up to 2 buildings on maps of distant regions.
			Each of these buildings will contain blueprints which will be extremely useful for your town.</em>
		</item>
		<item major="1" name="Jump Limits">
			The MetaCap (jump limit) has been <strong>removed</strong>. Enjoy! ;) 
		</item>			
		<item major="1" name="Construction project rebalancing">
			Construction projects have been adjusted, the majority of which now require less resources for their completion!<br/>
			The defensive values of certain buildings have been modified.
		</item>
		<item major="1" name="The Technician" help="job_tech">
			A new profession has appeared. The technician has additional action points dedicated solely to the construction of new projects, and also has all the tools of a master burgl...
			locksmith which allows them to come to the aid of explorers in trouble in the ruins.
		</item>
		<item major="1" name="The Survivalist" help="job_hunter">
			The hermit's tongue swells day by day. Is this due to the fact that the hermit goes for days at a time without uttering a single word? Or is it simply down to the random assortment of strange things they tend to snack on?
			Nonetheless, there are none more skilled when it comes to finding food or a good place to hide in the World Beyond.
		</item>		
		<item major="1" name="Citizen Escorts" help="escort">
			This feature allows citizens to get involved with more distant and dangerous expeditions without necessarily having to be present for the whole event. Escort mode also allows you to conduct rescue missions into the World Beyond more easily...
		</item>		
	
 		<item name="Evolution of the Scavenger">
			The scavenger has a new advantage. <br/>Equipped with a 50% larger oxygen reserve than other citizens, the scavenger can explore abandoned buildings in more depth, and bring back more resources for the community.
		</item>
			
		<!--
		<item name="Vaccin de Goule">
			Si vous avez la chance de trouver hôpital abandonné dans le désert, fouillez bien les fonds de tiroirs, il est possible que vous dénichiez un vaccin expérimental pour contrer les effets de la goule...
		</item>
		-->
		<item name="Bug Fixes">
			Lots of bugs have been corrected:
			<ul>
				<li>Bug in the Garbage Dump.</li>
				<li>Problem with the Wall Upgrade construction projects.</li>
				<li>Bug allowing the town to survive only using personal defences.</li>
				<li>Display bug affectingthe location on SOS message posts.</li>
				<li>Display bug involving Heroic Actions at the Town Gates.</li>
				<li>Hero day gift bug.</li>
				<li>Water Turret descriptions updated.</li>
				<li>And more...</li>
			</ul>
		</item>
	</release>	
	
<release version="2.0" name="A Chemical Necromancy">
	
		<item major="1" name="Construction Blueprints" help="bplans">
			An invigorating breeze is blowing through the dusty building sites of Die2Nite... Discover the site plans, a vast collection of almost 140 construction projects with a huge range of results! The blueprints can be found in many ways:
			in the World Beyond, by camping, by constructing other buildings... Many new strategies are now open to you!
		</item>
		
		<item major="1" name="Modifications to Professions">
			The Scout can now examine as yet undiscovered buildings in the World Beyond to find out exactly what they are.
			The Guardian brings extra defence points to the town (and can provide even more if you complete the correct construction projects).
		</item>
		
		<item major="1" name="Attack Adjustments">
			The attack strength of the horde has been totally changed. The early attacks will be less horrific, but attacks from day 15 onwards will become much more challenging. The new system for calculating the attacks greatly reduces the effect of "open gates" which usually results in the whole town being overrun with zeds. It will therefore be possible for a town to survive a monstrous attack for the bargain price of a few human lives.
		</item>

		<item name="Jump Limits">
			There are new restrictions for those of you wishing to join a town. Each map can accommodate no more than 20  "coalition members". One place is taken each time: a citizen joins a town with their coalition (randomly or otherwise),
			or when a Hero chooses this town from the list.
		</item>
		
		<item name="New construction interface">
			The construction projects page has been reworked. It is now more practical, and lets you see the town's stocks and resources better than before if you activate "detailed" mode (Link at the bottom of the Construction Sites page).
		</item>
		<item name="Hero Power(Dictator v2.0)">
			The Hero power "Dictator" now allows Heroes to share their expert advice by "recommending" one project per day. The site with the most recommendations will appear at the top of the list in order to help less experienced players. <strong>This power remains available after only 1 month of playing as a Hero.</strong>
		</item>
		<item name="Hero Power (Architect)">
			this power allows you to begin each new town with a "common" blueprint in your possession.
		</item>
		<item name="Non-distant Regions">
			Non-distant regions or will benefit from "special treatment" to facilitate the integration of new players:
			pre-fabricated buildings, automatic recommendations, smaller maps, etc...
		</item>
		<item name="Camping Modifications" help="camp">
			The chances of surviving while camping in open countryside (no building in the zone) are now reduced. this is also the case if the town is devastated.
			Successfully camping in a building will be rewarded with a construction blueprint (uncommon in nearby buildings, rare in faraway buildings).
		</item>
		<item name="Coalitions & absences">
			From now on, a player that has not logged recently will automatically be classed as unavailable in their coalition.
		</item>
		<item name="A shedload of adjustments">
			Lots of minor corrections and bug fixes including: a new distinction for repairing buildings,
			the Heroic Return power is now limited to 11km, and the prices of upgrading your house have been revised.
		</item>
	</release>
	
<release version="1.2" name="Rise of the Labradoodle" img="/gfx/screen/rankingScreenshot.png">
		<item major="1" name="Large Maps" help="map">
			Die2Nite now offers a wider choice of maps - up to 25x25 (previously 14x14). This will allow more advanced expeditions and enhanced exploration - how far do you dare go on your own?
		</item>
		<item major="1" name="Extreme Camping" help="extreme_camping">
				 Extreme camping is the risky, but potentially rewarding strategy of hiding in the World Beyond during the attack at midnight. the way it works is simple:
				 <p>
				<ul>
				<li>find yourself a decent hiding place in the desert</li>
				<li>perform 3 hail marys and 2 hello dollys</li>
				<li>wait for the attack to be over</li>
				</ul>
				</p>
		</item>
		<item major="1" name="Introducing: The Tamer" help="tamer">
				 Always accompanied by their trusty 3-legged labradoodle, the tamer is the perfect profession for citizens looking to take full advantage of the large maps...
		</item>
		<item name="Shunned citizens update">
			Shunned citizens will now be able to scavenge objects from the town's waste and hide objects in the World Beyond... 
		</item>	

</release>	
	
<release version="1.1" name="Hang 'em high" img="/gfx/screen/rankingScreenshot.png">
		<item major="1" name="New Ranking System" help="seasons">
			The new ranking system gives citizens even more reason to survive <strong>together</strong> for as long as possible. All rankings are deleted at the end of each season, which means that they last for 3 months. All the more reason to kick some of your lazy neighbours' asses out of bed and into line! The prizes are worth the effort! Anyone found to be involved in <strong>account sitting</strong> will result in the town being excluded from the rankings. For more details on account sitting, please click <a href="http://www.die2nite.com/#help/about_accountsitting"> HERE</a>
		</item>
		<item major="1" name="The gallows" help="justice">
				 Anger and resentment has been building recently in the World beyond, through the insidious activities of griefers and saboteurs. They say that necessity is the mother of invention, and this twisted take on reality led to the invention of the gallows. The justice-hungry citizen's friend! Now <strong>every</strong> town can build a gallows to get rid of unwanted scoundrels, robbers and cads. A revolutionary wind is whistling through the town gates... There are three things you should know about the gallows:
				<ul>
				<li>To avoid excessive use, the gallows <strong>will be destroyed</strong> after <strong>every</strong> hanging. You must find more resources to build another.</li>
				<li>If the <strong>Rusty Chain</strong>, is in a citizen's possession when he is shunned by the community, the chain will be returned to the bank.</li>
				<li>Make sure to hang the correct scoundrel! <strong>Warning:&nbsp;</strong> The first citizen to receive 8 complaints after the gallows are built will be hanged.</li>
				</ul>
		</item>
		<item name="Creative Writing Contest">
			From the <strong>17th of January until the 31st</strong>, it's time to pick up that quill! Tell us about how things changed with the apocalypse, life under constant threat... The best roleplay / die2nite inspired texts will be included in the game, for future players to find... 
		</item>		
		<item name="Sponsorship">
		<p>As the saying goes: "A friend in need is a friend indeed." This is also true in "Die2Nite" ! <strong>Sponsorship</strong> means that for every player you bring to Die2Nite:</p>
			<ul>
			<li>You will get a bonus of 20% of their subscription !</li>
			<li>You will get a point towards impressive distinctions.</li>
			</ul>
		</item>

</release>

	<release version="1.0" name="Let's get it on!" img="/gfx/screen/rankingScreenshot.png">
		<item major="1" name="Die2Nite Launch">
				On the <em>1st of December 2010</em>, Die2Nite was officially launched. After an attack of monumental proportion the previous night, everyone died... and everyone will die again.
				There is a wealth of new content coming to you directly. Learning how to not die2nite is tricky, and it's only going to get harder! New professions, new towns, new constructions, new enemies... it's all happening here, so don't go anywhere.
				Special thanks to <strong>Deepnight</strong> and <strong>Dayan</strong>, without whom Die2Nite would not exist!
				All that remains is for me to officially welcome you to hell, citizen...
		</item>
	</release>	

</releases>
