<competences>

	<comp id="1" name="Perception" elt="2">
	The skill of Perception allows you to be always on the alert. When you are going to choose an opponent for the fight, your Dino can *choose his opponent from a greater number of Dino*.
	</comp>

	<comp id="2" name="Intelligence" elt="3">
	Intelligence allows your Dino to develop his skills of thought and of concentration. In this way, an intelligent Dino will learn more quickly than another, and will gain *more experience* at the end of each fight.
	</comp>

	<comp id="3" name="Stamina" elt="1">
	The stamina of your Dino measures his capacity of *resistence to the attacks of its opponent*. A stronger resistence improves his protection against enemy attacks.
	</comp>

	<comp id="19" name="Strength" elt="0">
	Brute force or strength is not the best way to solve problems. However, some Dino can't control themselves when there is an attack. Increasing the Strength skill permits your Dino *to cause more harm* to his opponent in combat.
	</comp>

	<comp id="20" name="Dexterity" elt="4">
	Dexterity permits them to be flexible and skillful. But this isn't all! Dextirity also permits them avoid combats by dodging the ambushes of their opponents. If you increase his Dextirity, your Dino *can avoid some fights*.
	</comp>

	<comp id="4" name="Martial Arts" elt="0" dep="19:20">
	Martial Arts are learnt after a long period of training. They allow your Dino to dominate the art of combat at an advanced level, thus taking the maximum advantage of his opponent's weaknesses. Martial Arts are best used only for self-defense.
	</comp>

	<comp id="5" name="Camouflage" elt="4" dep="19:1">
	Camouflage allows your Dino to hide, thus avoiding discovery by Dino that are hunting for opponents. Your Dino will see his *Danger level* progress more slowly and it will be attacked less frequently if he has a good level of camouflage.
	</comp>

	<comp id="6" name="Medicine" elt="3" dep="1:2">
	Medicine is a science, which once it has been mastered, will allow you to cure your less serious wounds just after a fight. It's very practical because you won't have to spend large amounts of money on healing potions.
	</comp>

	<comp id="11" name="Bargain" elt="3" dep="5:6">
	The sense of commerce is not necessarily an innate quality, but it is quite valuable. Every higher level in Bargain allows you to negociate a better price for the objects in the shop! (your Dino must be alive and a maximum of 10 Bargain points are counted in the Bargain level among all your Dino).
	</comp>

	<comp id="15" name="Luck" elt="4" dep="10:9">
	Not everybody is lucky. The more Luck points you have, the greater are your possibilities of success in the different factors of chance which rule the world of Dinoland, like the coins which are won at the end of each fight!
	</comp>

	<comp id="17" name="Cook" elt="2" dep="9:11">
	Knowing how to cook makes daily living much more pleasant, but only if you know how to spend time on its preparation. With a few ingredients, *even the most insipid of Cloudburgers will become tastier*, and therefore more effective.
	</comp>

	<comp id="7" name="Swim" elt="2" dep="3:2">
	Every Dino knows, since he was a baby, that if he falls into a river, he had better know how to swim if he wants to survive. Swimming enables him to learn and master many different swimming styles.
	</comp>

	<comp id="8" name="Climb" elt="1" dep="3:20">
	The Dino that want to reach their full potential can learn how to climb. Once they've mastered this skill, they will be able to climb the steeper and more challenging slopes.
	</comp>

	<comp id="9" name="Survival" elt="0" dep="4:8">
	In the face of danger, some are panic stricken, but others can overcome the situation. Learning survival enables us to react swiftly when in danger and to avoid the worst.
	</comp>

	<comp id="10" name="Strategy" elt="4" dep="4:5">
	Knowing how to define a clear and efficient strategy before entering into battle is an advantage towards victory.
	</comp>

	<comp id="12" name="Navigation" elt="2" dep="7:6">
	Your Dino's adventurous spirit motivates him to learn navigation. He will have to master this skill in order to take a ship under his command and cross the ocean. Each level of Navigation has its title: Apprentice, Sailor, Officer, Captain, Admiral.
	</comp>

	<comp id="13" name="Run" elt="1" dep="7:8">
	There are times when its better to be brave, and others when it's better to trust in your dinolegs and run as fast as possible away from the danger. Better than taking a risk with a gigantic and powerful opponent...
	</comp>

	<comp id="14" name="Counterattack" elt="0" dep="13:10">
	Counterattacking is a very interesting action in combat. In effect, conditions permitting, when you receive a blow, a counterattack can multiply the damage inflicted to your opponent.
	</comp>

	<comp id="16" name="Music" elt="3" dep="11:12">
	Knowing how to play an instrument and how to read music may seem useless in the world of Dinoland. However, the arts are always a means of filling up the day to day of daily life. As the dinoproverb states: ''music sweetens routine''.
	</comp>

	<comp id="18" name="Jump" elt="1" dep="13:12">
	When, in the course of an exciting chase in which you are trying to escape from a strong Dino, your Dino finds himself facing a wall several metres high, in a one-way street, then the only thing he can do is jump. And the faster and more agile he is, so much the better!
	</comp>

	<comp id="21" name="Dig" elt="1" dep="1:2:3:19:20">
	If your Dino learns this skill, a new action will be available on the list. *Dig* enables your Dino to look for -and sometimes find- an item from the Collection of Dinoland. Besides, *Dig* enables you to complete the *Totem* of the Clan.
	</comp>

	<comp id="22" name="Steal" elt="3" dep="19:20">
	At the end of each fight, this skill permits trying to *steal* an item from the Collection of your opponent. If your opponent is knocked out *KO*, this will increase your chances of success.
	</comp>

	<comp id="23" name="Juggle" elt="3" dep="-1">
	Using this skill, your Dino attracts attention to himself and lowers the level of Danger to your other Dino. But beware of counterattacks!
	</comp>

	<comp id="24" name="Provoke" elt="2" dep="5:6:7:8:9:10">
	This skill allows you to *select a different message* to show at the end of the fight. The higher your level, the more options you have.
	</comp>
	
	<comp id="25" name="Fire Apprentice" elt="0" dep="-1">
   It enables your Dino to learn the Shadow Power.
	</comp>
	
	<comp id="26" name="Earth Apprentice" elt="1" dep="25">
	It enables your Dino to learn the Earth Power.
	</comp>
	
	<comp id="27" name="Water Apprentice" elt="2" dep="26">
	It enables your Dino to learn the Water Power.
	</comp>
	
	<comp id="28" name="Thunder Apprentice" elt="3" dep="27">
	It enables your Dino to learn the Thunder Power.
	</comp>
	
	<comp id="29" name="Shadow Power" elt="4" dep="28">
	Once it's completely mastered, this Evil Power **triples the points won** by this Dino in the War of Clans!
	</comp>
	
</competences>
