<dialogs>

<dialog pos="-1" swf="merchant.swf" title="Speaking to the Merchant" name="Robbie the Merchant">
		<a id="0" next="1:2:3">Hiya traveller! How're things o.k? ... allow me to introduce myself: Robbie, professional travelling merchant... if you're looking for something to buy, then you've certainly come to the right place.</a>
		<q id="1">Huum... hi</q>
		<q id="2">Hi there Robbie!</q>
		<q id="3">Hi... mmm... ok, so what can you offer me?</q>

		<a id="2" next="9">Huum... have we met before, mate?</a>

		<a id="1" next="4:5:6:7:8">Look, this is what I have: a radio-cassette for the car, a bumper, caps (with a Dinoland design!), Naturalchemist t-shirts, &copy;, badges, false moustaches and... a magnificent pile of second-hand medals!</a>

		<a id="3" next="4:5:6:7:8">Look what I have here: a radio-cassette for the car, a bumper, caps (with a Dinoland design!), Naturalchemist t-shirts &copy;, badges, false moustaches and... a magnificent pile of second hand- medals!</a>

		<a id="10" next="4:5:6:7:8">Uum... don't be such a bonehead, look at this: a radio-cassette for the car, a bumper, caps (with a Dinoland design!), Naturalchemist t-shirts &copy;, badges, false moustaches and... a  magnificent pile of second-hand medals!</a>

		<q id="4">I'll have the radio!</q>
		<a id="4" next="18">Good. To take -away or to eat here?</a>

		<q id="18">Whaat?</q>
		<a id="18" next="19:20">Do you wanna eat it now?</a>
		<q id="19">But... you can't eat radios ...</q>
		<q id="20">Ah well, it so happens that right now I'm absolutely starving!</q>

		<a id="19" next="17">Oh yeah? It's really delicious with a little mayonnaise.</a>
		<a id="20" next="21">Ok, that'll be 150000 coins.</a>
		<q id="21">Whaaat...? How much? But that's a fortune!</q>
		<a id="21" next="22">It always depends on how hungry the customer is.</a>
		<q id="22">Ah... well I didn't know I was that hungry... have you got anything else?</q>
		<a id="22" next="4:5:6:7:8">a bumper, caps (with a Dinoland design!), Naturalchemist t-shirts &copy;, badges, false moustaches and... a magnificent pile of second-hand medals!</a>

		<q id="5">I'll have the bumper! It's for a Cargonian pal.</q>
		<a id="5" next="15">An excellent choice , mate! Would you like it gift wrapped?</a>
		<q id="15">Yes, please</q>
		<a id="15" next="16:13">That'll be 180000 coins, plus another 200 for the wrapping paper. After all, I'm a professional.</a>
		<q id="16">Agh! 180000 coins?! ... you certainly are a professional!</q>
		<a id="16" next="17">Well... I have to earn a living.</a>

		<q id="17">Yes, of course... what else can you offer me?</q>
		<a id="17" next="4:5:6:7:8">A radio-cassette for the car, a bumper, caps (with a Dinoland design!), Naturalchemist t-shirts copy;, badges, false moustaches and... a magnificent pile of second-hand medals!</a>

		<q id="6">I want a cap! a Dinoland cap!</q>
		<a id="6" next="30">A Dinoland cap? Okie dokie... let's see... 3.000.000 coins please</a>
		<q id="30">Th-Th-three millon??! for a plain, ordinary sponsored cap!</q>
		<a id="30" next="31">Dinoland caps are very scarce! Especially after the disaster.</a>
		<q id="31">Ah, well I suppose so... and with the quality garantee, how much is it?</q>
		<a id="31" next="32">154000 coins. Do you want sugar on it?</a>
		<q id="32">No thanks... I've changed my mind.</q>

		<a id="32" next="4:5:6:7:8">A radio-cassette for the car, a bumper, caps (with a Dinoland design!), Naturalchemist t-shirts &copy;, badges, false moustaches and... a magnificent pile of second-hand medals!</a>

		<q id="7">Well so let's see, I'll try one of those moustaches.</q>
		<a id="7" next="33">Coming up! Synthetic or real?</a>

		<q id="33">I don't know, it depends... What's the difference?</q>
		<a id="33" next="34">The genuine moustaches are made from real Gorilloz hair, and they weigh a little more (because of the fleas). The synthetic ones are made of glass fibre. They're a bit scratchy but you'll soon get used to that. As it's a luxury accessory, the price is only 40000 coins...</a>

		<q id="34">That's enough! Leave it, I'll have something else.</q>
		<a id="34" next="4:5:6:7:8">If you want... I still have: a radio-cassette for the car, a bumper, caps (with a Dinoland design!), Naturalchemist t-shirts &copy;, badges, false moustaches and ... a magnificent pile of second-hand  medals </a>


		<q id="8">Second-hand medals? You mean they've been used?</q>

		<q id="9">... you don't sing something like ''Rudebox'', do you?</q>

		<a id="9" next="10">What?</a>

		<q id="10">Sorry, I think I've got the wrong Dino...</q>

		<a id="8" next="14:12">I bought them from a really weird horse, some months ago.</a>

		<q id="14">A horse, mmmm... you're sure it wasn't a pony?</q>
		<q id="12">Yeah, yeah. And the medals, how much do you want for them?</q>

		<a id="12" next="13">Only 350000 coins</a>
		<q id="13">Whaat? That's way too expensive!... ah... well, haven't you got anything else?</q>
		<a id="13" next="4:5:6:7:8">A radio-cassette for the car, a bumper, caps (with a Dinoland design!), Naturalchemist t-shirts &copy;, badges, false moustaches and ... a magnificent pile of second-hand medals !</a>

		<a id="14" next="23:12">Ah yes, that was it. A pony with a really cool cap. His name was Cerbeck, that was it.</a>
		<q id="23">Cerbeck, yes, I met him too... It was just after the explosion at the road-block.</q>
		<a id="23" next="24:25">An explosion? like the cataclysm?</a>
		<q id="24">No, it wasn't as big as that.</q>
		<q id="25">It doesn't matter, how much do you want for the medals?</q>
		<a id="25" next="13"> 350000 coins</a>

		<a id="24" next="26:27:28">Right, time flies and I've got things to do. if you don't wanna buy anything then I'll be on my way. Time is money, mate!</a>
		<q id="26">"Time is gold" you mean.</q>
		<q id="27">Wait! Show me again what you have.</q>
		<q id="28">Cool! Best of luck, Robbie!</q>
		<q id="29">I understand... in that case, show me your stock, and hurry up, please!</q>

		<a id="29" next="4:5:6:7:8">You're right, here's my stock: a radio-cassette for the car, a bumper, caps (with a Dinoland design!), Naturalchemist t-shirts &copy;, badges, false moustaches and... a magnificent pile of second-hand medals! Hurry up, I haven't got all day!</a>
		<a id="27" next="4:5:6:7:8">A radio-cassette for the car, a bumper, caps (with a Dinoland design!),  Naturalchemist t-shirts &copy;, badges, false moustaches and... a magnificent pile of second-hand medals!</a>


		<a id="26" next="29:28">I'm from the province of Laninsupe. We move around slowly because of the burden we carry , so business isn't easy...</a>

		<a id="28">See you!</a>

	</dialog>

	<dialog pos="2" swf="prophete.swf" title="Speak to the prophet" name="Mysterious Prophet">
		<a id="0" next="20:1:2">I love that catapult.</a>
		<q id="1">What catapult?</q>
		<q id="20">I entirely agree with you.</q>
		<q id="2">The prophecy has been fulfilled... why is it still raining on him?</q>

		<a id="2" next="3:4">After the great Cataclysm, I had a deep and profound conversation with the little cloud that was following me everywhere. She doesn't want to leave me... she says that we make a great couple and she couldn't bear being apart after all we've been through. I haven't got the courage to tell her that we haven't got a future together.</a>
		<q id="3">Oh, how sweet...</q>
		<q id="4">That means that you love her!</q>

		<a id="3" next="1">I'll lend you her whenever you want. Not a day goes by but I think about launching her away with the catapult.</a>
		<a id="4" next="3">Yes, I'd love to be able to talk about love at first sight, but it wouldn't be the truth. By the way, her name's Kinton.</a>

		<a id="1" next="10:11:12">Well there's one here in the Clearing. It was installed by the Hell's Professional Catapult Company ®. It's the fastest way of reaching Jazz Island. Dangerous, no doubt about that, but it sure is fast!</a>
		<q id="10">Jazz Island?</q>
		<q id="11">What's the Hell's Professional Catapult Company ®?</q>
		<q id="12">And how risky is that thing?</q>

		<a id="10" next="13" pic="islandView.jpg">It's pronunced "Geys". After the prophecy, a gigantic explosion took place in the west of Dinoland island. When the dust finally settled, one could see that a great geyser has become solidified in the middle of nowhere.</a>
		<q id="13">A geyser?</q>

		<a id="11" next="10:12:14:15">It's a company recently set up to take advantage of new marketing opportunities. It specializes in the precise and violent launching of creatures whose body mass is similar to that of the average Dino. If all goes well, then you will land in the market on the island.</a>
		<q id="14">The market?</q>
		<q id="15">Are there any interesting things there?</q>

		<a id="12" next="15">Well...  the basic thing is that we hurl you through the air at 150km/h. Let's suppose that you don't know how to fly. It wouldn't be long before you realize that you'll have a few problems at the moment of landing...</a>

		<a id="13" next="16:11">It was AWESOME! An enormous explosion, so much better than the fireworks! A professional job, if you want my opinion. Afterwards, instead of gradually disappearing, the dust cloud became solid and turned into Jazz Island.</a>
		<q id="16">I suppose there's nothing to see round there...</q>

		<a id="14" next="17">It's the new in-place to be seen, it's a revolution!</a>

		<a id="15" next="17:14">Ha, ha ,ha, yes! Nobody  really knows how the island appeared, but, one thing is that suddenly a whole idea of free-will started up there.</a>
		<a id="16" next="17:14:11">You're wrong! Nobody knows exactly how it appeared, but the thing is that free-will suddenly started up there.</a>

		<q id="17">To cut a long story short... I've only got to buy a catapult ticket and be launched up there, is that it?</q>
		<a id="17" next="18">Exactly!</a>
		<q id="18">O.K. But how do I get back?</q>
		<a id="18" next="19">Well ... ummm, you'll see that when you get there... I suggest that you try it for yourself. Tickets are on sale right here, in the Clearing. Good luck .</a>
		<q id="19">There isn't any other way of going?</q>

		<a id="19">Yes, of course. You could try swimming there from Dinobeach. It's free, but I'd advise you to have good swimming  skills...</a>

		<a id="20" next="21:2">Well, of course I'm right. I'm always right! Being a prophet is a vocation, you know. Besides, one can always help a little to fulfill the prophecies if necessary.</a>
		<q id="21">What do you mean "help a little"?</q>

		<a id="21" next="22:2">Ah well, I... you know. Officially, I only have to predict the catastrophies. But in practice, it's rather different.</a>
		<q id="22">I see... it's useless going into details which are of no interest.</q>

		<a id="22" next="1:2">Yes, it wouldn't be very logical for you to know much more about this matter. Are you going to buy a ticket for the catapult?</a>
	</dialog>



	<dialog pos="21" pic="vieux1.jpg" title="Ask the Wise old Man" name="Wise Old Man">
		<a id="0" next="10:2"> Well,well, well- just look who's here! A lost soul! Lost! Hellooooo!</a>
		<q id="10">So... Hello, wise old man!</q>

		<q id="2">Hey! have a look at this one...</q>
		<a id="2" next="3">Hmph.</a>

		<q id="3">Tell me, are you feeling all right?</q>

		<a id="3" next="4">I'm hungry... mmm... I'd love some hamster.</a>
		<q id="4">HAMSTER?!</q>

		<a id="4" next="10">What are you saying?</a>

		<a id="10" next="12:11:13:20">Ah hello there. I didn't hear you COME IN ha, ha... if you're looking for the Jazz Island treasures, then you've come to the right place for information.</a>
		<q id="11">You look a bit dazed...</q>
		<q id="12">Who are you?</q>
		<q id="13">There's a strange smell here.</q>
		<q id="20">Tell me about the treasures!</q>

		<a id="11" next="18:12:13:20">Ah! As the proverb says: «nobody is conscious of the latent advention of repeated  frustrations in the search for the meaning!».</a>
		<q id="18">...that's it, it's true! but isn't it more of a question of temporary nihilism and therefore lacking in value, in terms of cause and effect?</q>

		<a id="18" next="12:13:20">Without wishing to offend, young jedi, but you have just talked nonsense!</a>

		<a id="12" next="14:15:11:13:20">Here's an easy question, young one. «Cute is the little squirrel who looks for food under the hazel-nut tree». I'm the Wise old man! You can call me "Old Man".</a>
		<q id="14">I'd be delighted, Old Man.</q>
		<q id="15">A squirrel?  And what's that got to do with it?</q>

		<a id="14" next="15:11:13:20">Hey!</a>
		<a id="15" next="16:11:13:20">A squirrel? What are you talking about, young one?</a>

		<q id="16">You have just told me something totally nonsensical about a squirrel...</q>

		<a id="16" next="17" pic="vieux2.jpg">I haven't a clue what you're talking about... oh! That reminds me of a Dino proverb: «Cute is the little squirrel if she eats another hazelnuta».</a>
		<q id="17">Yes,that's it! Although the other squirrel was looking for it or something...</q>

		<a id="17" next="11:13:20"pic="vieux2.jpg">Yes of course. Don't we all look for our hazelnut? Lost souls, wake up to the true Dino Wistiti which lies inside yourselves and dig deep to find your hazelnut.</a>

		<a id="13" next="19:11:12:20">Toby.</a>
		<q id="19">Toby?</q>

		<a id="19" pic="edmond.gif" next="60:61:11:12:20">Toby, the toadstool. It's the name of the toadstool which has grown in my shack. I'm not brave enough yet to evict it from my sink.</a>
		<q id="60">One would just love to visit his house.</q>
		<q id="61">Yup. So Toby is a toadstool which is rotting away, and you are completely mad. How do you suppose I'll cope with that situation?</q>

		<a id="60" next="63:11:12:20"pic="vieux2.jpg">Oh, please come, I beg you. Ha, ha. Toby loves visitors.</a>
		<a id="61" next="62:50">A hamburger.</a>

		<q id="62">Pardon?</q>
		<a id="62" pic="edmond.gif" next="60:50">Toby is a decomposing hamburger, not a toadstool. Well, it was a hamburger which has turned into a great big toadstool. And, what's more he a really nasty character... Toby the Evil, ha, ha.</a>

		<q id="63">I think I'll take a walk and get some air.</q>
		<a id="63" pic="vieux2.jpg" next="11:12:20">Wheeeee!! Toby Tooooooby! Yuju!</a>


		<a id="20" next="21:31:22:23:24:50" pic="vieux2.jpg">Ahah noooooo... so what. Five treasures lost on Jazz Island. Like the fingers on your hand. Or the toes of your foot. That's it, they're toes! small and plump. And I'll give you the clues to assemble the original foot.</a>
		<q id="21">... then, are there plump toes to look for on Jazz Island?</q>
		<q id="22">That's enough, I want to know nothing more about Jazz Island.</q>
		<q id="23">What is the universe?</q>
		<q id="24">Does God exist?</q>
		<q id="31">What kind of clues are these?</q>
		<q id="50">That's enough!</q>

		<a id="23" next="25:21:22:24:31:50">In our case, the universe is a web page. But, I would add, to be more exact, that the universe is like a giant banana. Which goes round and round. Or if you prefer, like a kind of sponge.</a>
		<a id="24" next="21:22:23:31:50">Yes, God is a PHP script. And Hell is the Big Mistake 404.</a>
		<q id="25">Do you mean that it's a yellow fruit, with skin and that it goes round and round and it absorbs everything?</q>
		<a id="25" next="26:21:22:24:31:50">It's rather simplistic, but that's the idea. A bit like a soup spoon. Yes, that's it: the universe is like a soup spoon. Or a banana.</a>
		<q id="26">I understand it better. It's clearer now.</q>
		<a id="26" next="27:21:22:24:31:50">Knowledge comes eating an apple, as the philosopher, who was resting in the Singing Fountain, rightly said.</a>
		<q id="27">You've got weird friends.</q>
		<a id="27" next="21:22:24:31:50">Rare is the night, strange is the morning. Round and round the little snail! Five spells- do your work!</a>

		<a id="21" next="30:22:23:24:31:50">Every toe has a toenail to cut, my young friend.</a>
		<q id="30">That's disgusting.</q>
		<a id="30" next="22:23:24:31:50">if we were talking about the toenail of a diseased pteroz from my shack, well, well that would be really disgusting. Oh yes, yuck! a diseased pteroz !</a>

		<a id="31" pic="vieux2.jpg" next="21:22:23:24:50">How many clues that it's a yes! if you want to know... Find the five and the and the glory will be yours. You'll have a problem if you don't know how to read between the lines. Like the lines in the palm of your hand. Or your foot... they are more difficult to read! And it tickles! Yep! ha ha ha!</a>

		<a id="22" next="33:34:35:38:32:50" pic="vieux2.jpg">Ah, but Jazz Island's really tiny! It's pronounced "Geys", for the geyser which it evolved from. Geeeeeys! Wheee! It may be on the small side unless appearances deceive.</a>
		<q id="32">And to get back to our initial topic of conversation?</q>
		<q id="33">What's this about a telescope on the mountain in the east?</q>
		<q id="34">Why is there such a stink with the tides?</q>
		<q id="35">What's a good-looking old man like you doing in a place like this?</q>
		<q id="38">What's the Anomaly Cave?</q>

		<a id="32" next="21:31:22:23:24:50" pic="vieux2.jpg">Ahah...  Five treasures lost on Jazz Island. Like the fingers on a hand. Or the toes on a foot. That's it, they're toes! Plump. And I'll give you the clues to assemble the original foot.</a>
		<a id="33" next="36:37:34:35:38:32:50">Ah yes, the great telescope! Have you been there yet? It's quite an experience! A 100% experience!</a>

		<q id="36">How do you get there?</q>
		<a id="36" next="34:35:38:32:50">If I were you, I'd try to climb from the south, it's more fun that way! But of course, that's if I were you, but I'm me... And then again, if I weren't me, who would I be to tell you what you have to do?</a>
		<q id="37">You have a strange obsession with toes...</q>
		<a id="37" next="34:35:38:32:50">"The toe is the key", said the wise man; "rubbish", said my psychiatrist</a>

		<a id="34" next="39:33:35:38:32:50" pic="vieux2.jpg">It's the Chikabum virus! BOOM! Nobody knows why, but it smells like cauliflower and steak and kidney pie. We wonder if there is any connection with the great explosion... The pie went boom! Ha ha ha! Boom!</a>
		<q id="39">and has it got a cure?</q>
		<a id="39" next="33:35:38:32:50" pic="vieux2.jpg">In the Fountain! Plaf, lalala, two sups and it  disappears!</a>

		<a id="35" next="33:34:38:32:50">Then answer the strange questions and always give helpful clues!</a>
		<a id="38" next="37:33:34:35:32:50">Ah, I always avoid going through there! Anything could happen! That's why I'd advise your Dino to be in the best of physical condition and to have peak stamina.</a>

		<a id="50" pic="vieux2.jpg">See you soon then and I hope you dig deep inside to find your hazalnut! As everybody knows, in Dinoland only by digging can you find. Let's dig, let's dig! Ha Ha Ha... WHEEEEEE!</a>

	</dialog>



	<dialog pos="15" pic="guide.jpg" title="Talk to the poster" name="The Talking Poster">
		<a id="0" next="10:1:2">Welcome to Jazz Island!</a>
		<q id="1">This is the first time I've talked to a poster.</q>
		<q id="2">Hi!</q>
		<q id="10">Is there anything interesting and worth knowing about Jazz Island?</q>

		<a id="1" next="10">You aren't the first who has said that to me today... then, you should know that inside this poster, there is the heart of a true Dino. I would have loved to have belonged... to a clan!</a>

		<a id="2" next="3:4">You're a guide too?</a>
		<q id="3">Yes, dear friend!</q>
		<q id="4">Eh, I said nothing, ok?</q>
		<a id="3">So that's how it goes... eh? I hope you are signed up with the Union, son. There's no messing about with the competition here. Now get out of here, you're on my territory!</a>

		<a id="4" next="10:1">I'd prefer that, in these parts, we don't like competition...</a>

		<a id="10" next="11">Fine, to start with, you should know that it isn't pronounced "yaaaz", but "jjjEEEIIzzz" with J as in JJJumper. And another thing, who do you think you are? that I'm going to tell you about everything you can visit? Have I got "Guide" written on my forehead?</a>
		<q id="11">Mmm well yes, actually, it's written on you. There.</q>

		<a id="11" next="12:13">Ah... yes... that's true. So, what will I tell you about, then? About the swamp, about the treasures?</a>
		<q id="12">What can you tell me about the swamp?</q>
		<q id="13">Tell me about the treasures!</q>

		<a id="12" next="14:13:50">It's in the centre of the island, you can't miss it. That's exactly the problem.</a>
		<q id="14">Oh yes?</q>

		<a id="14" next="15:16:17:13:50">If you cross the swamp, you run the risk of contracting the Chikabum virus. Then, it rapidly infects the others... The only way to cure it, is by going to the Singing Fountain. Then, there's also the problem of the tides.</a>
		<q id="15">The Chikabum virus?</q>
		<q id="16">Where's the Singing Fountain?</q>
		<q id="17">What's this about the tides?</q>
		<q id="50">Thanks for your help. See you soon!</q>

		<a id="15" next="16:17:13:50">It floats on the mist on the swamp. It's really easily caught! Only the slightest contact with another Dino, and he's infected.</a>
		<a id="16" next="15:17:13:50">It's to the west. It's called that because... well you'll soon find out for yourself.</a>
		<a id="17" next="19:15:16:13:50">Some days during the week, the swamp changes and becomes different. Sometimes, the water is so high that it's impossible to cross. Then, there are other days, when the thick mist hides the Dino and makes combat impossible. The rest of the time, the water is low and there are no problems.</a>
		<q id="19">And if I'm in the middle when the water rises?</q>

		<a id="13" next="18:12:50">They say that there are five treasures of great value. Once they are all gathered together... well, I don't really know, but they give you the creeps, don't they? To find them, you have to dig in certain places and fulfill certain, very specific conditions at the time of the search. To the west of here, you'll find the old wise man... he knows a lot about these things, even though he's a... difficult man to understand, I'd say.</a>
		<q id="18">What kind of conditions are they?</q>

		<a id="18" next="12:50">They say they've got something to do with "digging with a very specific race in a specific place". Well, that's only one example! But as far as the exact conditions go, I can't tell you anything.</a>

		<a id="19" next="15:16:13:50">You'll be stuck for the rest of the day! It'll be impossible to get out of that place. The same thing will happen to you if you move when the waters are high. You have to know the cycles well!</a>

		<a id="50">Bye for now! And if you want to come back to Dinoland, think about a *hang-glider*. Take the advice of a friend!</a>
	</dialog>


	<dialog pos="18" pic="touristik_fr.jpg" title="Talk to the guide" name="Vigilant">
		<a id="0" next="1:2:3">Ladies and gentleman, bienvenue à Bordesky. Mesdames et messieurs, welcome to Burdesky... No pushing or shoving, please! Wait your turn! In the case of fighting, you'll find your life-jackets under your seats. In case of big-boom, you will find a life vest under your seat.</a>
		<q id="1">Bonjour</q>
		<q id="2">Hello</q>
		<q id="3">Svidan das kritchek!</q>

		<a id="1" next="5:6:7" pic="touristik_eng.jpg">if you have a question, please ask the guide.</a>
		<a id="2" next="5:6:7">We remind passengers that running about and hitting each other is forbidden. Please do not lean on the barriers and please do not throw yourselves over the edge.</a>
		<a id="3" next="4:5:6:7"pic="touristik_sp.jpg">Ah well, das kritchek u too. I assume that you're Svidostinian?</a>

		<q id="4">Euh.. ploutchek?</q>
		<a id="4" next="7:5:6:50" pic="touristik_sp.jpg">Da! Ishka vi rom töstir.</a>

		<q id="5">What's that there?</q>
		<q id="6">Has it never occured to you to build a ladder to come up here?</q>
		<q id="7">How many languages do you speak?</q>

		<a id="5" next="8:6:7:50" pic="touristik_sp.jpg">It's the Great telescope. Made in the year 1 A.C (After the Catastrophe) by the architect Magunus Oculus. It's a great example of modern Baroque. Notice these incredible details and the marvellous finish on this device. You can see all the island from Bordesky.</a>
		<a id="6" next="5:7:50" pic="touristik_eng.jpg">Yes, but it's much more fun seeing the tourists falling off the mountain!</a>

		<a id="7" next="9:10:5:6:50">I speak more than 15 languages and many other dialëktes. I need it for my job; Dinozs from all over the oceandïch come here everyday!</a>
		<q id="9">How do you say "I love you" in Gorilloz?</q>
		<q id="10">How do you say "hello" in Winks?</q>

		<q id="8">But how can something like this stay on this piece of stone?</q>
		<a id="8" next="6:7:50">It's simply a question of counterbalance. It's for this reason that we have all de public ammenities on de othder side of Bordesky. That way, we spread out the tourists.</a>

		<a id="9" next="11:10:5:6:50" pic="touristik_sp.jpg">"Comeroundherecocott"</a>
		<a id="10" next="9:5:6:50"pic="touristik_eng.jpg">"Winkii!". It has to be shouted out really loud. WINKIIIII!</a>
		<q id="11">And in Rokky?</q>
		<a id="11" next="10:5:6:50">"Yeah baby, yeah". But in yeneral, it's accompanied by a tipical rokkian dance: the Jimi Hendrix wedding parade.</a>


		<q id="50">Well, I'm going to have a look at the island with the telescope. Bye for now!</q>
		<a id="50">I wish you a nice visit. Don't forget the guide!</a>
	</dialog>

</dialogs>
