<items xmlns="http://tempuri.org/items.xsd">
    <!--- NORMAL ITEMS -->
    <it id="1" name="Sparky's Potion" icon="potion.gif">
        <desc>
		Sparky's Potion enables the Dino that drinks it *to take another turn* without having to wait until the next day.
		</desc>
        <effect>
		::name:: can jump again and do another action! Thanks Sparky!
		</effect>
    </it>
    <it id="2" name="Angel Potion" icon="potionRes.gif">
        <desc>
        The Angel Potion enables you *to resurrect a dead Dino*. Furthermore, this potion *cancels all negative effects* (virus, poison, etc.). If you have 0 life points, your Dino can't do anything and needs to be resurrected.
		</desc>
        <effect>
		::name:: is coming round! He is slowly opening his eyes and he thanks you for having saved him.
		</effect>
    </it>
    <it id="3" name="Cloudburger" icon="heal1.gif">
        <desc>
		The Cloudburger enables you *to improve a Dino's health (+10% life)*. It's particularly useful after a fight, and is much appreciated by hungry Dinos.
		</desc>
        <effect>
		::name:: has recovered ::p::% of life after a short and well deserved break. He's happy that you are looking after him!
		</effect>
    </it>
    <it id="4" name="Oven Fresh Bread" icon="heal2.gif">
        <desc>
		The Oven Fresh Bread enables your Dino *to get back all his life points*! Its unique properties and its wonderful taste make the Bread one of the best foods in Dinoland.
		</desc>
        <effect>
		::name:: has got back all his life points! Jump for joy!
		</effect>
    </it>
    <it id="5" name="Blackberry Drink" icon="liquor.gif">
        <desc>
        Blackberry Drink brought directly from Saint Blackberrytown. Strictly controlled production, and of certified quality. A true delight!
		</desc>
        <effect>
        Blackberry Drink is delicious! But only if you like blackberries... The effect it has on your Dino enables him to win ::p2::% of Life and a ::p::% of experience.
		</effect>
    </it>
    <it id="6" name="Shepherd's Pie" icon="healRandom.gif">
        <desc>
        Shepherd's Pie is always a surprise! It enables your Dino *to recover between 10 and 20% of life* (chosen at random).
		</desc>
        <effect>
		::name:: has just taken a bite of his Shepherd's Pie. He recovered by ::p::% !
		</effect>
    </it>
    <it id="7" name="Chocolate Medal" icon="xp.gif">
        <desc>
        This sweet gives *an experience bonus to your Dino (+10%)*. Any amount can be eaten whenever he wants!
		</desc>
        <effect>
		::name:: has devoured his chocolate medal and he feels much stronger. He gains a ::p::% of experience!
		</effect>
    </it>

    <it id="8" name="Incandescent Spell" icon="charm_fire.gif">
    	<desc>
    	The Incandescent Spell enables your Dino to nullify the damage caused by the next *Fire* element attack that he suffers.
    	</desc>
    	<effect>
    	::name:: is now protected from the next *Fire* attack that he receives.
    	</effect>
    </it>

    <it id="9" name="Titan Spell" icon="charm_earth.gif">
    	<desc>
    	The Titan Spell enables your Dino to nullify the damage caused by the next *Earth* element attack that he receives.
    	</desc>
    	<effect>
    	::name:: is now protected from the next *Earth* attack that he receives.
    	</effect>
    </it>

    <it id="10" name="Volvik Spell" icon="charm_water.gif">
    	<desc>
    	The Volvik Spell enables your Dino to nullify the damage caused by the next *Water* attack that he receives.
    	</desc>
    	<effect>
    	::name:: is now protected from the next *Water* attack that he receives.
    	</effect>
    </it>

    <it id="11" name="220W Spell" icon="charm_thunder.gif">
    	<desc>
    	The 220W Spell enables your Dino to nullify the damage caused by the next *Thunder* attack that he receives.
    	</desc>
    	<effect>
    	::name:: is now protected from the next *Thunder* attack that he receives.
    	</effect>
    </it>

    <it id="12" name="Wind Spell" icon="charm_air.gif">
    	<desc>
    	The Wind Spell enables your Dino to nullify the damage caused by the next *Wind* attack that he receives.
    	</desc>
    	<effect>
    	::name:: is now protected from the next *Wind* attack that he receives.
    	</effect>
    </it>

    <it id="13" name="Poisoned Claws" icon="claw.gif">
    	<desc>
		These enable you *to poison your next opponent*, regardless of who starts the fight -either he or you!
    	</desc>
    	<effect>
		Your Dino has turned into a wild beast! The next Dino who dares to challenge yours will be *poisoned*.
    	</effect>
    </it>

    <it id="14" name="Wolf Cub's Spit" icon="cure_poison.gif">
		<desc>
		Wolf Cub's Spit enables you *to cure your poisoned Dino*. The side effects will be the envy of the battlefield!
		</desc>
		<effect>
		Your Dino is now *cured of the poison*! He's really keen to get back into the fight!
		</effect>
    </it>

    <it id="15" name="Ramen's Secrecy Bowl" icon="invisibility.gif">
		<desc>
		The unique recipe of these exotic noodles enables the Dino which eat them to become almost invisible *(dividing the Danger by half 2)* and consequently having less possibility of being attacked!
		</desc>
		<effect>
		Your Dino has lost *half of his Danger*! Now it's easier to avoid being attacked!
		</effect>
    </it>

    <it id="16" name="Cherry Liqueur" icon="cherryLiquor.gif">
		<desc>
		This thick and sweet juice has extraordinary effects. Not only does it *reduce your Danger Level to 0* but it will also seriously *weaken* the increase of the Danger in each fight.
		</desc>
		<effect>
		*Wooaaah.* For some time now, your Dino has been feeling stressed because of his Danger Level. Now he feels much better and thanks you by jumping for joy!
		</effect>
	</it>

	<it id="17" name="Tiger's Eye" icon="eyeOfTheTiger.gif">
		<desc>
		Thanks to the Tiger's Eye, your Dino can find his enemies wherever they are! The possibilities of *escaping* are lowered and allow you to pursue the *enemies of your Clan* in a Tournament. This has a *permanent* effect.
		</desc>
		<effect>
		One of ::name::'s eyes has changed colour... now you can find your next victims no matter how well they hide!
		</effect>
	</it>

	<it id="18" name="The Power of Nature" icon="buff_nature.gif">
		<desc>
		Once this power is used on one of your Dino, he will obtain *+2 in  Earth* and *+2 in Air*. This effect can be effective during many combats.
		</desc>
		<effect>
		::name:: has gained +2 in Earth and +2 in Air! This effect will last until the Power disappears.
		</effect>
	</it>

	<it id="19" name="Agressivity Power" icon="buff_aggro.gif">
		<desc>
		Once this power is used on one of your Dino, he will obtain *+2 in Fire* and *+2 in Lightening*. This effect can be effective during many combats.
		</desc>
		<effect>
		::name:: has obtained +2 in Fire and +2 en Lightening! This effect will last until the Power disappears.
		</effect>
	</it>

	<it id="20" name="The Power of Sirain" icon="buff_water.gif">
		<desc>
		Once this power is used on one of your Dino, he will obtain *+5 in Water*. This effect can be effective during many combats.
		</desc>
		<effect>
		::name:: has obtained +5 in Water! This effect will last until the Power disappears.
		</effect>
	</it>

	<it id="21" name="Chikabum Antidote" icon="cure_chika.gif">
		<desc>
		This antidote allows you to cure one of your Dinos of the Chikabum Virus. It will also make him *immune to the next virus that infects him* (only once).
		</desc>
		<effect>
		::name:: has been cured of the Chikabum Virus!
		</effect>
	</it>

	<it id="22" name="Market bond" icon="bill.gif">
		<desc>
		Certified by the Dinoland Bank, it's worth *1000 coins*. You can use it or exchange it.
		</desc>
		<effect>
		You have used a Market Bond, you get 1000 coins!
		</effect>
	</it>

	<it id="23" name="Shadow Potion" icon="potion_dark.gif">
		<desc>
		The Shadow Potion is a gift offered by the Demons of Dinoland to thank you for your sacrifices. Will you be brave enough to use it?
		</desc>
		<effect>
		Your Dino has been transformed! He feels stronger and he has turned into a Shadow Dino!
		</effect>
	</it>


<!-- CLAN TOTEM -->

	<it id="50" name="Manurek" icon="totem_buze.gif">
		<desc>The Manurek is a very strange type of earth used by the Dinos' ancestors.</desc>
		<effect>Your offering to the Clan has been accepted by the Totem.</effect>
	</it>

	<it id="51" name="Ketcha Feathers" icon="totem_feather.gif">
		<desc>The Ketcha is a poisonous snake covered in feathers, which are a great trophy.</desc>
		<effect>Your offering to the Clan has been accepted by the Totem.</effect>
	</it>

	<it id="52" name="Ancestral Tooth" icon="totem_tooth.gif">
		<desc>The Ancestral Tooth is a shiny little stone which gets its name from its dark colour and its strong smell of Blackberry Liqueur.</desc>
		<effect>Your offering to the Clan has been accepted by the Totem.</effect>
	</it>

	<it id="53" name="Unicorn's Mane" icon="totem_unicorn.gif">
		<desc>Unicorns are such rare animals that no Dino has ever seen one. However, from time to time a Unicorn's mane is found. It is recognisable by its slight silvery sheen.</desc>
		<effect>Your offering to the Clan has been accepted by the Totem.</effect>
	</it>

	<it id="54" name="Magic Wood" icon="totem_wood.gif">
		<desc>This is very rare and much sought after. When burnt, it produces fireworks specially favourable to the invocation to the Totem.</desc>
		<effect>Your offering to the Clan has been accepted by the Totem.</effect>
	</it>


    <!--- COLLECTION ITEMS

		parametres optionels :

		* tournoi :  position:or/argent/bronze:nombre de points

	-->

    <!-- tournoi dinoplage -->
    <it id="1001" name="Dinobeach Gold Medal" tournoi="3:0:15" icon="medal_gold.gif">
        <desc>You have won this medal for bravery shown in the Dinobeach Tournament!</desc>
    </it>
    <it id="1002" name="Dinobeach Silver Medal" tournoi="3:1:10" icon="medal_silver.gif">
        <desc>You have won this medal thanks to your efforts in the Dinobeach Tournament.</desc>
    </it>
    <it id="1003" name="Dinobeach Bronze Medal" tournoi="3:2:5" icon="medal_bronze.gif">
        <desc>It's a good start. All the great Dino started off once with this medal.</desc>
    </it>

    <!-- tournoi mont Dino -->
    <it id="1004" name="Mount Dino Gold Medal" tournoi="6:0:15" icon="medal_gold.gif">
        <desc>At the end of the dangerous Mount Dino Tournament you achieved this gold medal!</desc>
    </it>
    <it id="1005" name="Mount Dino Silver Medal" tournoi="6:1:10" icon="medal_silver.gif">
        <desc>This reward comes from the fearful Mount Dino Tournament.</desc>
    </it>
    <it id="1006" name="Mount Dino Bronze Medal" tournoi="6:2:5" icon="medal_bronze.gif">
        <desc>Proof of your bravery on Mount Dino, this medal can open up some paths for you...</desc>
	</it>

	<!-- tournoi zen -->
	<it id="1007" name="Zen Tournament Gold Medal" tournoi="10:0:15" icon="medal_gold.gif">
		<desc>This medal grants you the rank of Zen Master, bravo!</desc>
	</it>
	<it id="1008" name="Zen Tournament Silver Medal" tournoi="10:1:10" icon="medal_silver.gif">
		<desc>This medal grants you the rank of Zen Novice, brilliant!</desc>
	</it>
	<it id="1009" name="Zen Tournament Bronze Medal" tournoi="10:2:5" icon="medal_bronze.gif">
		<desc>This medal grants you the rank of Zen Apprentice, fantastic!</desc>
	</it>

	<!-- tournoi mayinca -->
	<it id="1010" name="Mayincas Gold Medal" tournoi="13:0:15" icon="medal_gold.gif">
		<desc>The Mayincas were destroyed because of that strange thing called ''gold'': If you wear this medal, at least think of your distant ancestors.</desc>
	</it>
	<it id="1011" name="Mayincas Silver Medal" tournoi="13:1:10" icon="medal_silver.gif">
		<desc>This medal rewards Dino that have triumphed in a hostile jungle.</desc>
	</it>
	<it id="1012" name="Mayincas Bronze Medal" tournoi="13:2:5" icon="medal_bronze.gif">
		<desc>After tough combat, you have obtained this super medal!</desc>
	</it>

	<!-- tournoi Dinoville -->
	<it id="1013" name="Dinotown Gold Medal" tournoi="0:0:15" icon="medal_gold.gif">
		<desc>You've obtained the last reward in Dinoland. Every Dino has dreamed at some stage of having his own between his hooves. Congratulations, you now are part of the Dinoland annals of history!</desc>
	</it>
	<it id="1014" name="Dinotown Silver Medal" tournoi="0:1:10" icon="medal_silver.gif">
		<desc>The silver medal gives you the strength to reach the last reward: the gold!</desc>
	</it>
	<it id="1015" name="Dinotown Bronze Medal" tournoi="0:2:5" icon="medal_bronze.gif">
		<desc>This bronze medal is worth gold, since only the strongest Dino have won it.</desc>
	</it>

    <!-- collection -->
    <it id="1016" name="Fossilized Cheese" icon="cheese.gif">
        <desc>It is said that this ancient piece of cheese was part of the first shipment of cheese produced in Dinoland. The sales were so disastrous that the production of cheese was immediately abandoned in favour of Dinodonuts (to the great delight of the younger dinoz). That's the reason why it's a collector's item. Unique in its kind.</desc>
    </it>
    <it id="1017" name="Aphrodisiac Pendent" icon="aphro.gif">
        <desc>An ancient inscription on the pendent makes us assume that it's a jewel which is several centuries old!</desc>
    </it>
    <it id="1018" name="Wooden Cocoffer" icon="chest.gif">
        <desc>The Cocoffer is a chest measuring less than one centimetre by one centimetre. At the present time, its contents are a mystery. Its small size impedes any attempt to open the lock since it could break into a thousand pieces. We only know that it makes a ''chic chic'' sound when it is shaken.</desc>
    </it>
    <it id="1019" name="Snail's Claw" icon="claw.gif">
        <desc>Normally snails don't have claws. But the Goliath snail, called ''the slaverer'', who lives in the North of Dinoland, has some very pretty claws on its shell. Occasionally, it loses one when it rubs itself against a tree or when it tries to move a rock. These claws, mainly for their rarity, are therefore, a much appreciated collector's item.</desc>
    </it>
    <it id="1020" name="4 Leafed Clover" icon="clover.gif">
        <desc>It's only one of the clovers that grow in the meadows of Dinoland. A very common species, nothing compared to the 12 leafed carnivorous clover.</desc>
    </it>
    <it id="1021" name="1 Gold Dineuro" icon="coin_gold.gif">
        <desc>This coin belongs to the old Dinoland currency: the dineuro. After the Great Crisis of 39, the Commerce Commission of the Council of the Wise proposed substituting the dineuro by the present Gold coin, which is the sole new currency of the Dinopean Community.</desc>
    </it>
    <it id="1022" name="1 Silver Dineuro" icon="coin_silver.gif">
        <desc>This extremely rare coin belongs to the old currency of Dinoland: the dineuro. After the Great Crisis of 39, the Commerce Commission of the Council of the Wise proposed substituting the dineuro by the present Silver Coin, which is the sole new currency of the Dinopean Community.</desc>
    </it>
    <it id="1023" name="The Mordor Flame" icon="fire.gif">
        <desc>This is a legendary flame which, so they say, can keep away the forces of evil thanks to its powerful magic. It's also useful for lighting a bonfire.</desc>
    </it>
    <it id="1024" name="Peanuts" icon="fruit.gif">
        <desc>Delicious Dinoland peanuts, ripe, juicy and tasting of grape. If allergic, keep away.</desc>
    </it>
    <it id="1025" name="Green Gem" icon="gem.gif">
        <desc>A mysterious green gem, with the letter K inscribed on one of its sides. It's strange, but if it gets lost or disappears, it comes back on its own the next day.</desc>
    </it>
    <it id="1026" name="Lead Glove" icon="glove.gif">
        <desc>This is a collection item formerly used by the Dinolean. Ball players the glove was used to liberate all the force of the thrower. This method, really efficient, was prohibited by the Sports Committee after the accidental destruction of a mountain during a particularly violent game.</desc>
    </it>
    <it id="1027" name="Pacific" icon="pacific.gif">
        <desc>The Pacific is the symbol of peace in Dinoland. It's a carnivorous plant several metres high which wanders through the woods. It can swallow up to 5 times its weight in meat, afterwards digesting it for days.</desc>
    </it>
    <it id="1028" name="Volcanic Pearl" icon="pearl.gif">
        <desc>Volcanic pearls have been used for a long time in adornment as well as in jewellery. Until one day, when someone realized that they were the cause of the numerous volcanic eruptions on the island. It only takes one small blow to liberate the volcano they contain. That would explain the presence of the numerous mountains that are characteristic of the island.</desc>
    </it>
    <it id="1029" name="Slaver Dust" icon="powder.gif">
        <desc>The process of production of this powder is still a mystery, which makes it a rare and expensive component. Although not necessarily in much demand.</desc>
    </it>
    <it id="1030" name="The Treasure Map" icon="scroll.gif">
        <desc>It's an old map of the treasure found in a pirates tavern. Next to the title, in careful hand writing, is the hiding-place of the legendary treasure of Captain Hatchet, nicknamed ''the Pitiless''. He is renowned, not only for his cruelty, but also for his intelligence, which explains why he forgot to mark the hiding-place with a cross on the map.</desc>
    </it>
    <it id="1031" name="Sweet Petal" icon="chocapic.gif">
        <desc>It's a dried petal from the chocoplant. It has the peculiarity of curling up when it dries. It's a crunchy sweet which is often eaten with milk.</desc>
    </it>
    <it id="1032" name="Socrates Tooth" icon="socrate_tooth.gif">
        <desc>They say that this tooth belonged to Socrates, a Moueffe, slightly bothered by a premonition. It seems that, in his day, he took advantage of this particular skill to do well in battle...</desc>
    </it>
    <it id="1033" name="Hamburger" icon="burger.gif">
        <desc>The classic hamburger used to be one of the most exquisite delicacies of the Dino. It was quickly replaced by the novelty Cloudburger, more tender, tastier and lighter. This object is a real collector's item.</desc>
    </it>
    <it id="1034" name="The Mysterious Eye" icon="eye.gif">
        <desc>There isn't a lot of information about the Mysterious Eye (nobody has made it speak yet). The only thing that is known is that it is alive and it moves by rolling around.</desc>
    </it>
    <it id="1035" name="The Golden Hook" icon="hook.gif">
        <desc>It's a golden hook which was found on a dock. A merchant, who had come from far-off islands, used to sell them a long time ago. He must have lost it.</desc>
    </it>

 	<it id="1036" name="Laba Ball" icon="star1.gif">
    	<desc>When you shake it, the Laba ball makes a clink, clink sound! It's a most highly esteemed collector's item, but, in fact, it's quite useless. It's one of the 5 elements of the treasure of Jazz island!</desc>
    </it>

    <it id="1037" name="Depth Ball" icon="star2.gif">
    	<desc>Strange things float in the interior of the Depth Ball. They say that sometimes you can nearly see inside it a Dino, of an unknown, yet superior race. It's one of the 5 elements of the treasure of Jazz island!</desc>
    </it>

    <it id="1038" name="Snow Ball" icon="star3.gif">
    	<desc>The Snow Ball is very much in demand for its hypnotic powers, but it's a poisonous item. Damned be he who dares to stare at this ball, because its magic will send him into a deep and dark sleep. for your safety, remove the batteries. It's one of the 5 elements of the treasure of Jazz island!</desc>
    </it>

    <it id="1039" name="Sea Ball" icon="star4.gif">
    	<desc>It's the biggest of the 5 balls. It is almost 150cm in diametre and it weighs several hundred kilos. You really have to want it if you ant to keep it. It's one of the 5 elements of the Jazz island treasure!</desc>
    </it>

    <it id="1040" name="Spider Ball" icon="star5.gif">
    	<desc>The Spider ball is covered in a slimey substance, which drips all the time. Everything that comes near gets stuck for a long time. The advantage is that you can use it as a pendent without needing a chain. It's one of the 5 elements of the treasure of Jazz island!</desc>
    </it>

    <it id="1041" name="Fimacling Spider's Web" icon="web.gif">
    	<desc>It's a solidified spiders web. The Fimacling are tiny spiders who live in the undergrowth of the swamp. The web is so fine that it hardly lasts for more than a few minutes, and the mists of the swamp solidify it. The collectors would buy it for *astronomical* prices! But, obviously, you don't want to sell it :)</desc>
    </it>

    <it id="1042" name="Mini-Toby" icon="edmond.gif">
    	<desc>In the past, it was undoubtedly something delicious and tasty. But now, it's just a rotten toadstool, slimey and stinking. Actually, it isn't a collectors' item, but there's no way you can get rid of it, because it's stuck to your fingers.</desc>
    </it>

    <it id="1043" name="Manurex with moss" icon="oldBuze.gif">
    	<desc>This manurex is of no interest to the totem because the passing of time has covered it with moss. It's an excepcionally rare item.</desc>
    </it>

    <it id="1044" name="The Administrator's Ring" icon="ring.gif">
    	<desc>It is said that the ring bearer will get supreme powers! He will be capable of instantly striking his opponent with a bolt of lightening and he will obtain thousands of coins with a simple movement of his ring finger! This would seem to be the key to enter the legendary ''Administrator's space''. The Ring Bearer will be like God! It's a pity that the instructions are in Korean.</desc>
    </it>

    <it id="1045" name="Pocket Lightening Conductor" icon="staff.gif">
    	<desc>It should have been a good idea: a portable lightening conductor for protection in case of necessity. Unfortunately, the inventor didn't realize that having a lightening conductor in your hands was not such a good idea... Keep it well (just in case). There's only one.</desc>
    </it>

	<it id="1046" name="Pressure cooker Valve" icon="valve.gif">
		<desc>This item is a complete mystery. Nobody has the remotest idea as to how this item was able to get to Jazz island. It smells of steak and kidney pie and cauliflower. It has an inscription, like the trade mark: «Free Tibet!»</desc>
	</it>

	<it id="1047" name="Baby Cloud" icon="cloud.gif">
		<desc>This baby cloud has been following you everywhere since you found it. It doesn't speak much, but when it gets angry, it gets above you and rains and shoots bolts of lightening at you.</desc>
	</it>

	<it id="1048" name="Virgin Spell" icon="charm.gif">
		<desc>For unknown reasons, this spell has never been broken since it was first used. The element which it contained has been used up, but the talisman hasn't evaporated. It's so rare that it's great to boast about.</desc>
	</it>

	<it id="1049" name="Dissecated Piopi" icon="piou.gif">
		<desc>This small solidified creature is, it would appear, a Piopi. You don't know how it got here because the Piopi race belongs to a paralell world (www.pioupiouz.com). Anyway, it's very decorative.</desc>
	</it>

    <!--
	    	SPECIAL Items
	    	Items non collectionnables
    -->

    <it id="1036" name="A Real Peruvian Hat" icon="hat.gif">
	    <desc>This Peruvian hat is a present from Cerbeck, the pony. You are asking why it insisted so much on giving you this gift... by the way, the culprit of the theft of the medals is still a mystery... So many mysteries! Someone has written ''Free Tibet'' on the inside of the hat.</desc>
    </it>

    <it id="2002" name="The Sword of the Conquerors" icon="katana.gif">
	    <desc>For your Excellence in the Great War of the Clans, we present you with this powerful and unique blade together with our most sincere congratulations. It's a sign of your great domination over the other clans! We hope that your bravery will serve as an example to future generations of Dino Masters</desc>
    </it>

    <it id="2003" name="War Rune" icon="war_stone.gif">
     	<desc>This distinction bears witness to your exemplary participation in the Great War of the Clans, in which you were outstanding for having reached the highest classification.</desc>
    </it>

	<it id="2004" name="Tana Katana" icon="katana2.gif">
    	<desc>For your excellence in the battlefield of the War of the Clans, you receive this unique weapon together with our most sincere congratulations. It's a sign of your great domination over the other clans! We hope that your valour will be an example to future generations of Dino Masters.</desc>
    </it>

	<!--
    <it id="2005" name="Zod War Rune" icon="war_stone2.gif">
    	<desc>This distinction bears witness to your exemplary participation in the War of the Clans, of which you are an illustrious and distinguished participant, forming part of the highest classification.</desc>
    </it>-->

    <it id="2005" name="--" icon="--">
    	<desc>NOT USED</desc>
    </it>

	<it id="2006" name="Magic Sword" icon="katana3.gif">
    	<desc>For your warrior qualities shown in the *War of the Clans*, we wish to honour you with this unique weapon together with our most sincere congratulations. It's a symbol of absolute domination over the other clans! We hope that your bravery will serve a an example to future generations of Dino Masters.</desc>
    </it>

    <it id="2007" name="Totem Tears" icon="war_stone3.gif">
    	<desc>This illustrious distintion bears witness to your exemplary participation in the *War of the Clans*, in which you reached the highest point of the classification.</desc>
    </it>

    <it id="2008" name="Jazz Ball" icon="star_full.gif">
    	<desc>This prestigious reward shows the whole world that you have discovered the Five Magic Balls and that therefore you have solved the mystery of  Jazz island. Congratulations!</desc>
    </it>

    <it id="2009" name="The Triple-force Metal Balls" icon="katana4.gif">
    	<desc>For your excellence in the *War of the Clans*, we present you with this legendary weapon as a sign of your fierce domination over the other clans. This weapon was forged by the council of Softys a long, long ago during the time of the Great Microwave-Burn-All crater.</desc>
    </it>

    <it id="2010" name="Totem Eye" icon="war_stone4.gif">
    	<desc>This distintion bears witness to your exemplary participation in the *War of the Clans*, and in this clasification, you obtained an illustrious and leading position.</desc>
    </it>

	<it id="2011" name="5th Sense Rune" icon="war_stone2.gif">
		<desc>Congratulations for your participation to the epic *3rd Clans War*, hoping that you will renew your exploit for the 4th!</desc>
	</it>

	<it id="2012" name="PomPom Hammer" icon="katana5.gif">
		<desc>Great Warrior of the *3rd Clans War*! You are rewarded for your bravery by a numbered exemplary of the PomPom Hammer. Keep it away from children under 8 years old.</desc>
	</it>

    <it id="2013" name="Médaille Clignotante" icon="war_stone5.gif">
    	<desc>Cette médaille récompense les valeureux Guerriers de la *6ème Guerre des Clans*. Pour votre courage dans cette guerre, l'équipe de Dinoparc vous offre une médaille clignotante. Il paraît en effet que tous les 1000 ans, elle change de couleur. Pas de risque d'épilepsie donc...</desc>
    </it>

    <it id="2014" name="Kabuki Prize" icon="kabuki.gif">
		<desc>This prize rewards you for finishing the *Kabukis Quest*! Now you'll be able to find Kabukis in the Dino shop.</desc>
    </it>

	<it id="2015" name="Magic Shuriken" icon="shuriken.gif">
		<desc>Your Clan have been noticed during the 4th Clans War, this *Magic Shuriken* rewards your strategist talents. Thanks to your shoe size 16, you had let no chances to your enemies, trampling them without mercy.</desc>
	</it>

	<it id="2016" name="Magic Duck" icon="coincoin.gif">
		<desc>For your noticed participation to the 4th Clans War, you receive this *Magic Duck* that, people says, brings luck in case of drowning. Do not forget it before making your Dinoz swim!</desc>
	</it>

	<it id="2017" name="Viscera-Turner" icon="katana6.gif">
		<desc>To honour your victory during the Superb 5th Clans War, this *Viscera-Turner* in stainless steel has been offered to you. To test in priority on all your enemies, including your little	sister who creates multi-accounts.</desc>
	</it>

	<it id="2018" name="Bomb-Pendant" icon="war_stone6.gif">
		<desc>For your participation more than honourable to the Superb 5th Clans War, The Dinoparc Team congratulates you by offering this *Bomb-Pendant*, very practical to defend yourself where you are unexpectedly attacked!</desc>
	</it>

	<it id="2019" name="Coal Globe" icon="globe_charbon.gif">
		<desc>This *Coal Globe* rewards you for your courage in the *Hermite Arena*. Good luck!</desc>
	</it>

	<it id="2020" name="Bronze Globe" icon="globe_bronze.gif">
		<desc>This *Bronze Globe* rewards you for your exploits in the *Hermite Arena*. Good luck for what happens next!</desc>
	</it>

	<it id="2021" name="Silver Globe" icon="globe_argent.gif">
		<desc>This *Silver Globe* is reserved to the greatest Warriors of the *Hermite Arena*! Congratulations for your exploits!</desc>
	</it>

	<it id="2022" name="Gold Globe" icon="globe_or.gif">
		<desc>The *Gold Globe* is the elite item of the *Hermite Arena* ! The Dinoparc team congratulates you for your tenacity!</desc>
	</it>

	<it id="2023" name="Gods Book" icon="katana7.gif">
		<desc>To honour your victory during the *Gods War* (6th War), this *Gods Book* will tell your exploits during many generations.</desc>
	</it>

	<it id="2024" name="Dinosopher's Stone" icon="war_stone7.gif">
		<desc>For your noticed participation to the *Gods War* (6th War), the Dinoparc team congratulates your by offering this *Dinosopher's Stone*, which apparently transforms the Pruniac in Gold Coins! (even if nobody has ever made it work)</desc>
	</it>

	<it id="2025" name="Alliance Treaty" icon="katana8.gif">
		<desc>Congratulations! Your victory in the *7th Clan War* has been rewarded by this Alliance Treaty, that certifies your dual talents of Warrior and Diplomat.</desc>
	</it>

	<it id="2026" name="The Laughting Cowed-Axe" icon="war_stone8.gif">
		<desc>For your noticed participation to the *7th Clan War*, the Dinoparc team congratulates you by offering this *Laughing Cowed-Axe*: made from 100% natural products, a small axe blow every day is apparently very good for the health.</desc>
	</it>

	<it id="2027" name="Twin Blades of Mr Per Nicious" icon="katana9.gif">
		<desc>Congratulations! Your victory in the *8th Clan War* has been rewarded by these Twin Blades, which certify your dual talents of Warrior and Diplomat. Forged by Mr Per Nicious, famous master in the negociation, trickery and cunning art. People says that he would have usually offered one of this blades 	as proof of trust before stabbing its twin in an ancient ally's back.</desc>
	</it>

	<it id="2028" name="Broken Pact" icon="war_stone9.gif">
		<desc>For your noticed participation to the *8th Clan War*, the Dinoparc team congratulates you by offering this *Broken Pact*: symbol of your political schemes in the battle for the clans ranking in the Dinoparc world.</desc>
	</it>

	<it id="2029" name="Cosmik Sword" icon="katana10.gif">
		<desc>Congratulations! Your victory in the *9th Clan War* has been rewarded by this Cosmik Sword. People say that the eye in its center sees and knows all ... too bad that it can't speak....</desc>
	</it>

	<it id="2030" name="Monstroplankton" icon="war_stone10.gif">
		<desc>For your participation in the *9th Clan War*, the Dinoparc team has awarded you this *Monstroplankton* amulet: if freed, it is possible that this animal-plant would devastate the universe. Fortunately, this pendant is pretty tough... according to the manual at least...</desc>
	</it>

	<it id="2031" name="Gene-and-Tick" icon="adn.gif">
		<desc>This item given by the professor Alphagen enables you	to access to a new Dinoz via the Shop</desc>
	</it>

	<it id="2032" name="Tohn Hammer" icon="katana11.gif">
		<desc>For your excellence in the *10th Clan War*, we give this Hammer to you which was owned by the legendary warrior Tohn!	It is said that the bearer can use it to provoque earthquakes and cataclysms ... that is if one day you are able to lift it.</desc>
	</it>

	<it id="2033" name="Living Soda" icon="war_stone11.gif">
		<desc>This distinction testifies your notable participation to the *10th Clan War*, in which you have been ranked amongst the most powerful Clans of Dinoland.</desc>
	</it>
	
    <it id="2036" name="Sound Forger" icon="hammer.gif">
    	<desc>In recognition of your exploits in the *11th Clan War*, you have earned  a hammer which seems to allow you to fabricate false market bonds, fortunately it's in safe hands.</desc>
    </it>

    <it id="2037" name="Beer of Brothers" icon="beer.gif">
    	<desc>This Beer of Brothers has been given to you in recognition of your achievnments in the *11th Clan War*. It symbolizes the friendship and brotherhood of all the Dinoz Masters in Dinoland, regardless of Clan allegiances. This won't stop the next war, but as they say, it's the thought taht counts!</desc>
    </it>

	<it id="2038" name="Goblin Skull" icon="war16a.gif">
		<desc>For your excellence in the *12th Clan War*, you have earned this magnificent Goblin Skull, as a souvenir of the massacres you had to carry out to get to the top!</desc>
	</it>

	<it id="2039" name="Goblin Chains" icon="war16b.gif">
		<desc>In recognition of your exploits in the *12th Clan War* you have been given these Goblin Chains, ideal for keeping your enemies captive!</desc>
	</it>

	<it id="2040" name="Baboom" icon="war17a.gif">
		<desc>In recognition of an amazing performance in the *13th Clan War*, you have been awarded a Baboom: it won't explode, but it'll certainly frighten your enemies!</desc>
	</it>

	<it id="2041" name="Blue Rune" icon="war17b.gif">
		<desc>In recognition of your exploits in the *13th Clan War* you have been awarded this Blue Rune, famed for its ability to render the wearer immune from Type d1n6 Flu!</desc>
	</it>

	<it id="2042" name="Heavenly Helmet" icon="war18a.gif">
		<desc>In recognition of an amazing performance in the *14th Clan War*, you have been awarded a Heavenly Helmet, a unique object which allows you to hear the movement of the sea...</desc>
	</it>

	<it id="2043" name="War Helmet" icon="war18b.gif">
		<desc>In recognition of your exploits in the *14th Clan War* you have been awarded this War Helmet, which is only given to warriors who are not wet behind the ears, probably due to the built-in dehumidifier!</desc>
	</it>

	<it id="2044" name="Precious Ring" icon="war19a.gif">
		<desc>A golden ring, topped with 3 rubies, ''one ring to tame them all'' according to the tiny script engraved on the inside. Only the champions of the 15th Clan War have earned the right to wear it!</desc>
	</it>

	<it id="2045" name="Tarnished Ring" icon="war19b.gif">
		<desc>A pale blue ring, given to clan members in recognition of their exploits during the 15th Clan war... A legend tells of certain warriors feeling ill upon removing it.</desc>
	</it>	

	<it id="2046" name="Dorogon Canine" icon="war20a.gif">
		<desc>A Dorogon canine tooth is offered to the winners of the 16th Clan War. You show it off with pride. Just be sure taht the Dorogon that lost it isn't in the area!</desc>
	</it>

	<it id="2047" name="Dorogon Molar" icon="war20b.gif">
		<desc>A Dorogon molar is awarded to the clans who showed extreme valour in the 16th Clan War. It weighs almost 3kg so not very easy to transport, however, it could be used as a luxury paperweight.</desc>
	</it>

	<it id="2048" name="Golden Armour" icon="war21a.gif">
		<desc>Well this is pretty much what is says on the tin, and was awarded to the winners of the *17th Clan War*. Those who wear it are never worried about being targeted: which is fortunate because it shines so brightly, you're the only thing anyone can see on the battlefield.</desc>
	</it>

	<it id="2049" name="Glove of Righteous Fury" icon="war21b.gif">
		<desc>In recognition of your exploits in the *17th Clan War* you have been awarded The Glove of Righteous Fury. Equipped with this glove, nobody will dare stand against you, that said, that's pretty normal, whosoever wears this magical artefact can't stop punching those around them in the throat.</desc>
	</it>

	<it id="2050" name="Shining Samurai" icon="war22a.gif">
		<desc>
			You have been awarded a samurai helmet for winning the *18th Clan War*! The former owner was a powerful shogun who won many battles, in no small part due to the fear caused by this helmet. Unfortunately it now shines too brightly to be used in battle.
		</desc>
	</it>

	<it id="2051" name="Phantom Samurai" icon="war22b.gif">
		<desc>
			The helmet of the phantom samurai is said to contain the souls of warriers struck down on the battlefield. This serves as proof of your exploits in the *18th Clan War*. However, it's only purpose now is decoration. In fact, it's now impossible to wear the helmet without hearing the screams of the ghosts residing within...
		</desc>
	</it>

	<it id="2052" name="Mage Sword" icon="war23a.gif">
		<desc>
			An extremely powerful magic sword has been awarded to you for winning the *19th Clan War*! It's just a shame it's shattered and now only measures three centimetres...
		</desc>
	</it>

	<it id="2053" name="Mage Stone" icon="war23b.gif">
		<desc>
			You have been awarded the Mage Stone in recognition of your performance in the *19th Clan War*. It contains an extremely powerful magic, it's a shame we no longer know how to forge it.
		</desc>
	</it>
	
	<it id="2054" name="Djinn Statue" icon="war24a.gif">
		<desc>
			This statue of Djinn has been awarded to you for winning the *20th Clan War*. It brings happiness, luck, and most of all, dust.
		</desc>
	</it>
	
	<it id="2055" name="Yggdra Statue" icon="war24b.gif">
		<desc>
			You have been awarded the Statue of Yggdra in recognition of your performance in the *20th Clan War*. It seems to emanate warmth, hope, and splinters.
		</desc>
	</it>
	
	<it id="2056" name="Citadel of Vertigo" icon="war25a.gif">
		<desc>
			The Citadel of Vertigo has been awarded to you for winning the *21st Clan War*. From it's balconies, you'd be forgiven for thinking you can see the entire world. Don't look down though - unless you want a fright!
		</desc>
	</it>
	
	<it id="2057" name="Jade Palace" icon="war25b.gif">
		<desc>
			You have been a stay in the Jade Palace in recognition of your performance in the *21st Clan War*. You have to use your arm strength to climb all the way to the top, the lift repair man still hasn't shown up!
		</desc>
	</it>

	<it id="2058" name="Ancien guerrier" icon="war26a.gif">
		<desc>
			Cette figurine d'un ancien guerrier maintenant à la retraite vous est offerte pour avoir remporté la 26ème Guerre des clans .
		</desc>
	</it>
	
	
	<it id="2059" name="Artiste martial" icon="war26b.gif">
		<desc>
			Cette figurine d'un pratiquant des arts martiaux vous est offerte pour vos exploits lors de la 26ème Guerre des clans.
		</desc>
	</it>

	<it id="2060" name="Coupe d'Or" icon="war27a.gif">
		<desc>
			Cette coupe récompense vos victoires lors de la 27ème Guerre de Clans : un véritable objet de Champion !
		</desc>
	</it>
	
	
	<it id="2061" name="Coupe d'Argent" icon="war27b.gif">
		<desc>
		Cette coupe récompense votre performance lors de la 27ème Guerre de Clans : c'est la marque d'un grand exploit !
		</desc>
	</it>
	
	<it id="2062" name="Coupe d'Or rare" icon="war28a.gif">
		<desc>
			Cette coupe récompense vos victoires lors de la 28ème Guerre de Clans : c'est une grande distinction reservée aux meilleurs joueurs !
		</desc>
	</it>
	
	
	<it id="2063" name="Coupe de Bronze" icon="war28a.gif">
		<desc>
		Cette coupe récompense votre performance lors de la 28ème Guerre de Clans : celà n'est déjà pas facile à obtenir !
		</desc>
	</it>
	
</items>