<map>
	<zone id="0" name="Dinotown" nexts="1:4" pro="in " items="30:35" img="zone0.gif">
		Dinotown is the capital of Dinoland. It's a bustling, cosmopolitan city. It's also famous for its Great Bazaar, where thousands of items are bought and sold each day. It's tournament is reckoned to be the ultimate challenge and winning it is the greatest honour that can be bestowed upon a Dino.
	</zone>
	<zone id="1" name="Sparky's Cave" nexts="0:2" pro="in " items="21:22" img="zone1.gif">
		Sparky the Witch lives in this dark cave. She sells strange potions which allow Dino to break through time limits and thus carry out several actions every day. Anyway, the different fragances of the potions, of orange to banana with a scent of kiwi, are a real gift.
	</zone>
	<zone id="2" name="Clearing in the Wood" nexts="1:3" pro="in the " items="17:32" img="zone2.gif">
		Some Dino love to stop for a while in the clearing to rest amidst the ancient trees of the wood. They are easily recognizible by their slight tan. But there are also some other Dino who run past without stopping. These are the ones who have taken a Sparky Witch Potion to make them go faster!
	</zone>
	<zone id="3" name="Dinobeach" nexts="2:4" pro="at " items="19" img="zone3.gif">
		In Dinobeach there are spas where Dinos, from all over the world, come for a break. It's famous for its hot, relaxing baths which rapidly restore health. Whats more, the Dinobeach Tournament is accesible to all Dinos.
	</zone>
	<zone id="4" name="Check Point" nexts="0:3" pro="at the " items="" img="zone4.gif">
		Dinoguards, in uniform, control the road which leads to Mount Dino. They check all Dinos that are going in that direction. If you wish to go north in the direction of Mount Dino, you'll have to go through this check-point.
	</zone>
	<zone id="5" name="Hermitage Cliffs" nexts="4:6:7" pro="in " items="34" img="zone5.gif">
		From the highest point of the cliffs, a hermitage overlooks the ocean. They say that, years ago, a powerful Dino decided to give up warfare, after having been defeated in the Dinotown Tournament. Since then, he has taught his secret knowledge to young Dinos who have talent.
	</zone>
	<zone id="6" name="Mount Dino" nexts="5" pro="in " items="31" img="zone6.gif">
		 Mount Dino is the highest mountain in Dinoland. A small village, where old combat traditions still survive, is situated on its summit. It is here, where many Dinos regularly meet to prepare for the most dangerous tournament in Dinoland.
	</zone>
	<zone id="7" name="Granite Door" nexts="5" pro="at the " items="16:28" img="zone7.gif">
		A gigantic granite door hinders the entrance of the travellers. There are inscriptions engraved in an ancient Dino language. This door has been here from ancient times, which is why it must be a vestige of the ancient Empire. This must be a sign that you are on the right track! However, until the door opens, you can't go on...
	</zone>
	<zone id="8" name="Bandits Road" nexts="7:9:11" pro="in the " items="18" img="zone8.gif">
		This route is known as the "Bandits Road". In ancient times, famous bandits lived here, who used to rob the poor Dino who took this road. But that was a long time ago, and since then, many casinos have turned this place into a Gaming shrine. It's a very disreputable place, but sometimes, with a little luck, you can make a fortune.
	</zone>
	<zone id="9" name="Ancient Wood" nexts="8:11" pro="in the " items="23" img="zone9.gif">
		The Ancient Wood is situated here. Its gigantic trees and the gloomy darkness make it one of the most feared places in Dinoland. Many fairy stories in Dinoland begin with the words "Once upon a time, in the Ancient Wood..." It's often used to frighten the children ("if you don't finish your soup, we'll send you to the Ancient Wood"). It's actually a real natural labyrinth, where every step could prove fatal. Are you brave enough to cross through it?
	</zone>
	<zone id="10" name="Buddhist Temple" nexts="9" pro="in the " items="25:26" img="zone10.gif">
		In the highest part of Tibya, Dino-monks, clad in orange robes, meditate for hours, and even sometimes for days, to purify their Karma. You must be really careful not to interrupt them, because they get really angry when someone interrupts their deep and profound meditation.
	</zone>
	<zone id="11" name="Port of Saint Berry" nexts="8:9" pro="in the " items="24" img="zone11.gif">
		The Port of Saint Berry is always extremely busy. Every day, in this port, tons of blackberry are embarked to the different ports of Dinoland. Blackberries are a much sought after local delicacy, and numerous Dino depend on it for a living. All along the docks, you can see many Blackbarques, great ships which give off the aroma of blackberry.
	</zone>
	<zone id="12" name="Pity Island" nexts="11:13" pro="on " items="" img="zone12.gif">
		Along the coast of Dinoland, the dark silouette of Pity Island can be seen through the mist. It's always night in the narrow, twisting streets of its one, small village. There are many old beggars on every street corner.
	</zone>
	<zone id="13" name="Mayinca Ruins" nexts="12:14:0" pro="in the " items="27:29:33" img="zone13.gif">
		In this dangerous jungle, you can find the ruins of the ancient Mayinca civilization. There are many legends about these ancestors of the Dino. It is said, among other things, that they were the original inventors of the tournaments, and that their descendents are extremely strong warriors. If you think that you have mayinca blood in your veins, then why don't you try participating in the Tournament that takes place here?
	</zone>
	<zone id="14" name="Institute of Olympic Credit" nexts="13" pro="in the " items="20" img="zone14.gif">
		The Institute of Olympic Credit is the most important bank in Dinoland. Originally, it was run by goblins who hid their clients money in holes in the trees, far out of the sight of nosy people and thieves. At the present time, it's a very grand marble building, with safes and armoured bank vaults. But anyway, the goblins are still hiding money in trees.
	</zone>
	<zone id="15" name="Jazz island Market" nexts="16" pro="in the " items="46" img="zone15.gif">
		It's the first arrival point on Jazz island. There are many Dino-merchants installed here and the busy atmosphere reminds you of Dinoville. Dino' masters can buy and sell Dino here. Sometimes, you can find some really good offers!
	</zone>
	<zone id="16" name="Sticky Swamp" nexts="15:17:19" pro="in the " items="42" img="zone16.gif|zone16_fog.gif|zone16_flood.gif">
		This swamp takes up the centre of Jazz island. It's a big problem for travellers because it changes depending on what day it is. Be careful with mosquito bites: it's very easy to catch the Chikabum Virus if you stay here. \n
		##Today *the tide is low*: you can move around with no problems.|*The mist is covering the whole swamp...* You can't attack or be attacked (as on every *Wednesday* and *Friday).|*THE swamp is completely flooded!* You can't move. You'll have to wait until tomorrow to get out of here (as on every *Tuesday* and *Saturday*).##
	</zone>
	<zone id="17" name="The Wistitis Jungle" nexts="16:20" pro="in the " items="43" img="zone17.gif">
		The Wistitis Jungle is a strange and dangerous place. They say that a dangerous monster lives round here... Although, it's not easy to quite sure because the thick vegetation makes it impossible to see more than a few meters. A word of advice: don't go near the lake if you don't want to be attacked by a crocodinoz.
	</zone>
	<zone id="18" name="Burdesky" nexts="16:21" pro="at " items="41" img="zone18.gif">
		From this height, you can see all of Jazz and Dinoland islands, thanks to the Great Chaman's telescope. They say that the Great Chaman constructed the telescope with his own hands, to observe the stars and so understand the meaning of the Universe. Recent arqueological research has shown that the telescope actually was originally directed towards the Singing Fountain, where many Dino-girls used to go to bathe.
	</zone>
	<zone id="19" name="Singing Fountain" nexts="16:21" pro="at the " items="47" img="zone19.jpg">
		The waters of the Singing Fountain are a cure for the Chikabum Virus. The problem is that instead of sounding like a normal Fountain, this Fountain sings the latest Dinoland pop hits. Rumour has it that connected to the Buddhist Temple, and that it's the dinoz-monks you're hearing.
	</zone>
	<zone id="20" name="Anomaly Cavern" nexts="17" pro="in the " items="45" img="zone20.gif">
		Whether it's singing stones or card-playing toadstools, everything here seems to function in the opposite way. In the deepest heart of the cavern, a magic coffer is floating in mid-air. Visitors can make a wish in exchange of some coins. However, it quite often makes mistakes and an a catastrophe might occur. Because of this, there's never a queue waiting. It's so dangerous that nobody dares!
	</zone>
	<zone id="21" name="Wise Old Man's shack" nexts="19" pro="at the " items="48:49" img="zone21.jpg">
		In this shack. the wisest old man of Jazz island lives. He is so well-known for his wisdom that many people come to consult him even about the Meaning of Life... the problem is that nobody understands a word he says. Some say that, the only thing he knows is where the five legendary treasures are hidden on the island. Like all confirmed old bachelors, his shack really stinks, and that's why nobody stays very long.
	</zone>
	<zone id="22" name="Crater of the Great Lord Burn-All" nexts="11" pro="in the " items="44" img="zone22.gif">
		It's taken several hours of hard climbing to reach the summit of the volcano... here is where the Great Lord Burn-All lives. It is said that his mood changes are legendary and they can cause dramatic eruptions. Without doubt, that's why he gets so few visitors...
	</zone>
</map>