<races>
	<r name="Softy" rarity="1" elts="2:0:0:0:0" price="8000">
	It is peaceful and obedient. The Softy is a gentle companion who will never cause you any problems.
	</r>

	<r name="Picori" rarity="1" elts="0:0:0:0:2" price="8000">
	These flying Dino are incredibly agile and fast! They can often be found in the Dinoland woods, especially in spring.
	</r>

	<r name="Castivore" rarity="1" elts="0:1:0:0:1" price="8000">
	Swift and agile, with a soft, but at the same time, thick skin, the Castorians are also very loyal.
	</r>

	<r name="Sirain" rarity="1" elts="0:0:2:0:0" price="8000">
	Many thousands of years ago, the Siranians decided to abandon the woods and their pillagers and enter the depths of the oceans. Some have come back to land.
	</r>

	<r name="Winks" rarity="1" elts="0:0:1:1:0" price="8000">
	Protected by their thick shells, the Winks are always on the prowl. Be careful- those who dare to annoy them!
	</r>

	<r name="Gorilloz" rarity="1" elts="0:2:0:0:0" price="8000">
	Originally from the jungle, the Gorilloz are big and just spoiling for a fight. Astute and stubborn, they are usually very strong.
	</r>

	<r name="Cargon" rarity="1" elts="0:1:1:0:0" price="8000">
	The Cargonians love rain as much as they love fine weather. They aren't very fast but they're capable of dealing with many different situations.
	</r>

	<r name="Hippoclamp" rarity="3" elts="1:1:1:1:1" price="12000">
	The Hippoclamps are rare and delicate animals. They are nearly extinct but they are protected by Greenfriends. However, hunters still pursue them, because they seem to be the perfect ingredient for soup.
	</r>

	<r name="Rokky" rarity="2" elts="0:0:0:0:0" price="10000">
	They may be boneheads, but they have the most amazing theatrical skill in Dinoland! This bestows them with a special and unique skill: juggling!
	</r>

	<r name="Pigmon" rarity="2" elts="2:0:0:0:0" price="8000">
	The Mountain Pigmons have very strange and changeable moods. They can be so happy and tender, with eyes full of tears, and suddenly become violently angry if you brush against them in the queue for an ice-cream. Their opponents must be very careful when they meet them.
	</r>

	<r name="Wanwan" rarity="1" elts="0:0:0:2:0" price="9000">
	The WanWan is the Dino master's best friend. However, in spite of its gentle and calm appearance, he is capable of going for the throat of anyone whom he thinks is a threat to his master. If you choose him, look after him well!
	</r>

	<r name="" rarity="0" elts="" price="0">TODO</r>

	<r name="Kump" rarity="1" elts="0:0:2:0:0" price="8000">
	The Kumps used to sleep in the deep caverns of the Ocean until they were awakened by the apparition of Jazz island. They are impulsive, intelligent and skillful.
	</r>

	<r name="Terroz" rarity="2" elts="0:0:0:0:4" price="10000">
	The Terroz is a Dino who is a native of Mount Dino. His speciality is finding the elements of the Totem, because the Divine Gods have a special preference for his warrior blood. And what's more, he's a fierce opponent!
	</r>

	<r name="Mince Pie" rarity="0" elts="1:0:2:0:1" price="20000">
	Congratulations! These Mince Pies are Dino, who are very much sought after, and impossible to find in the Shop. Enjoy the privilege of being their Master and spoil them a lot, especially at Christmas time!
	</r>

	<r name="Wistiti" rarity="0" elts="0:1:1:1:0" price="15000">
	The Wistitis are mysterious Dinos who are extremely wild. They live in the *Wistitis Jungle*. Be careful, if an opponent kills your Wistiti, then he's *captured* and isn't yours any longer! (up to a certain level).
	</r>

	<r name="Korgon" rarity="10" elts="0:2:0:1:0" price="15000">
	*Korgons* appeared suddenly in Dinoland. Did they come from outer space? Or maybe from deep underground? Nobody has discovered their *secret* yet. I wouldn't ask them either, they get *very* angry!
	</r>
	
	<r name="Kabuki" rarity="0" elts="0:0:2:0:5" price="20000">
	The *Kabuki* are Ninja-Dinos who hide everywhere in the shadows of Dinoland. They say that they are those who control in secret a big part of the economy, specially with their strong muscles.	
	</r>
	
	<r name="Serpantin" rarity="0" elts="4:0:0:0:0" price="50000">
	The *Serpantin* race was created by Professor Alphagen through strange genetic experimentation. Their natural element is fire, which offers them substantial protection against this element.
	</r>

</races>
