<!-- ***************************************************************************** -->
<!-- Chrysanthe et Cassandre gardent l'entrée du palais de Caushesmesh --->
	
<d place="cpyra1" name="Chrysanth" gfx="chrysanthe" cond="scenario(caush,42-)">
	<phase id="begin" next="hein:mission:comin">
		[I feel so empty, nothing is happening, I can't go on.]
		[GO. Leave me. What if I just let myself fall into this lake of ether?]
		[What is love, what is life?]
	</phase>
	<a id="hein" cond="scenario(caush,25-)">...Uuh...Hello...</a>
	<phase id="hein" next="sieste">
		[Noone may enter, the guardian is mid-siesta.]
		[She's right. What is the point in staying awake in a world as sad as this.]
		[I hope she is dreaming of her lost love, and most of all, most of all...]
	</phase>
	<a id="sieste">most of all?</a>
	<phase id="sieste" next="bon:nobon:mission">
		[Most of all that she doesn't wake up like a bear with a sore head!]
		[...]
		[Are you still there?]
	</phase>
	<a id="bon" cond="scenario(caush,21)">I'd like to come in...</a>
	<a id="nobon" cond="!scenario(caush,21)">I'd like to come in...</a>
	
	<phase id="nobon" fast="1">
		The Amazonian isn't even looking at you any more, she is too busy moping, sitting on the stairs.
		Nothing you can say to her will change anything.
	</phase>
	
	<phase id="bon" scenario="caush:22">
		[Winter is coming but the cold still reigns in my heart.]
		[If you wish to take some of the flak, I won't stand in your way.]
		[At least for once it won't be me...]
		[Go ahead, before the ice in my heart tells me the opposite.]
	</phase>
	
	<a id="mission" cond="scenario(caush,25+)">Do you have a mission for me?</a>
	<a id="comin" cond="scenario(caush,25+)">May I enter?</a>
	
	<phase id="comin">
		[Winter is coming but the cold still reigns in my heart.]
		[If you wish to take some of the flak, I won't stand in your way.]
		[At least for once it won't be me...]
		[Go ahead, before the ice in my heart tells me the opposite.]
	</phase>
	
	<phase id="mission" missions="amazon"></phase>
</d>

<d place="cpyra1" name="Cassandra" gfx="cassandre" cond="scenario(caush,42-)">
	<phase id="begin" next="quoi">
		[OH MY GOD!]
	</phase>
	<a id="quoi">What's going on?</a>
	<phase id="quoi" next="chic:mission:comin">
		[Oh no no, I've lost a priceless earring!]
	</phase>
	<a id="chic" cond="scenario(caush,25-)">Is that it?</a>
	<phase id="chic" next="dodo">
		[What do you mean?]
		[Oh good grief, you just have to take one look at you and your entourage of Dinoz to know you're not cool!]
		[It's really important, I must look perfect, how do you suppose I got this job in the first place?]
	</phase>
	<a id="dodo">I'd rather not think about it.</a>
	<phase id="dodo" next="bribe:nobribe:cadeau:mission">
		[Oh dear, honestly, I feel sorry for you, not being able to recognize style and good taste when you see it...]
		[...]
		[ANyway, what is it that you want anyway?]
	</phase>
	<a id="bribe" cond="scenario(caush,20)">I'd like to come in...</a>
	<a id="nobribe" cond="!scenario(caush,20)">I'd like to come in...</a>
	<a id="cadeau" cond="scenario(caush,24)">Is there any way to please the guardian?</a>
	
	<phase id="bribe" next="got1:got2:got3:nogot">
		[Our mistress has awoken... Her yelling can be easilt heard from here...]
		[You've not even done anything to merit seeing her.]
		[Bring me a beautiful jewel and I may just let you pass!]
	</phase>
	
	<a id="got1" target="got1" cond="hasingr(art1)">Give her a precious ring</a>
	<a id="got2" target="got2" cond="hasingr(art2)">Give her a carved chalice.</a>
	<a id="got3" target="got3" cond="hasingr(art3)">Give her a nice necklace.</a>	
	<a id="nogot" cond="!hasingr(art1)">You have nothing that might satisfy her.</a>
	
	<phase id="nogot">
		[Oh no, you really have nothing of interest!]
		[Come back and see me when you deserve to stand before me!]
		[...Bzzzz]
	</phase>
	
	<phase id="nobribe" next="nan">
		[HIHIHIHI, you're dreaming!]
		[Firstly, you're badly dressed, secondly, you make too much noise, furthermore, you nothing of the latest Caushemeshian fashion.]
		[Oh yes, and doesn't want to be bothered.]
		[...and I, I don't wan't to put up with this attitude.]
		[OK, bzzzz, disappear!]
	</phase>
	<a id="nan">But...</a>
	<phase id="nan">
		[BZZZZZ !]
	</phase>
	
	<phase id="got1" scenario="caush:21" fast="1" useingr="art1">
		The unsociable amazon is bored of you now, she only has eyes for the jewel which you gave her.
		You now have to convince the other amazon to let you in to the palace.
	</phase>
	
	<phase id="got2" scenario="caush:21" fast="1" useingr="art2">
		The unsociable amazon is bored of you now, she only has eyes for the jewel which you gave her.
		You now have to convince the other amazon to let you in to the palace.
	</phase>
	
	<phase id="got3" scenario="caush:21" fast="1" useingr="art3">
		The unsociable amazon is bored of you now, she only has eyes for the jewel which you gave her.
		You now have to convince the other amazon to let you in to the palace.
	</phase>
	
	<phase id="cadeau" next="easy">
		[So you have met the other guardian and you're still standing...]
		[You should count yourself lucky!]
		[They say she is the most powerful sorceress in all of Dinoland. So if I were you, I'd tread carefully around her.]
	</phase>
	<a id="easy">I want to know more about Caushemesh!</a>
	<phase id="easy" next="mission" scenario="caush:25">
		[Seriously, you're a real pain.]
		[But at least you're not completely inane. In fact it would appear that she is the best person to advise you.]
		[Listen up. Here's what we're going to do. I'm going to give you a short list of missions to carry out, and I'll give her little presents from you as we go along.]
		[With a little luck, she'll want to speak to you then...!]
	</phase>
	
	<a id="mission" cond="scenario(caush,25+)">Consult the list of missions!</a>
	<a id="comin" cond="scenario(caush,25+)">May I come in?</a>
	
	<phase id="comin">
		[Oh good grief you're irritating.]
		[You can clearly see which door lies open to you, so why waste my time asking me about it.]
		[BZZZZZZ!]
	</phase>
	
	<phase id="mission" missions="amazon"></phase>
</d>

<d place="cpyra1" name="Chrysanth" gfx="chrysanthe" cond="scenario(caush,43+)">
	<phase id="begin" next="mission">
		[Our mistress abandoned us here, alone.
		I'm caught between the feeling of joy at not having to put up with her any more, and the extreme boredom afforded by the task I've been given...]
		[What do you want Dinoz master?]
	</phase>
	<a id="mission">Consult the list of missions!</a>
	<phase id="mission" missions="amazon"></phase>
</d>

<d place="cpyra1" name="Cassandra" gfx="cassandre" cond="scenario(caush,43+)">
	<phase id="begin" next="mission">
		[My, my, my...]
		[Now that the colossi are gone, we're getting more and more visites from the Acropolis.]
		[The Caushemesh merchants should think about replenishing their stocks. I'm going round and round in circles here!]
		[You wanted to give me something?]
		[...]
		[No? Shame...]
	</phase>
	<a id="mission">Consult the list of missions!</a>
	<phase id="mission" missions="amazon"></phase>
</d>


