<!-- Roi de Dinoville-->
	
<!---
Condition d’accès : avoir fait les missions de gulom.
Le roi invite le joueur dans son château situé sur un plateau de dinoplaza par l’intermédiaire d’un de ses gardes, il veut enfin faire connaissance du sauveur de caushemesh.
Arrivé au cinéma, le garde constate que l’accès au chateau est bloqué depuis son départ.
Les expérimentations sur le mana, acquis grâce à l’effort de guerre, affecte les environs du château.

il faut ensuite aller voir le shaman mou, constituer une potion en assemblant des ingrédients et en allant battre le vénérable (il la faut bien frappé)
Une fois arrivé dans le palais, le roi reçoit le joueur.
Il fait la connaissance du conseiller (aveugle) qui ne lui adresse pas un mot.
Le roi demande de réaliser des missions:

Récompense : item consommable permettant de booster x2 son xp lors d’un combat,
durée nombre de combats 1,2,10 ?
-->

<d place="dnv" gfx="garde_dnv" name="King's Guard" background="3" cond="(admin()|active(roi))+fx(morsso)+scenario(king,0)">
	<phase id="begin" next="humpf" frame="stop" fast="1">
		[A female soldier stops you in the street, she is wearing the uniform of the Royal Guard.]
		[She looks at you aggressively, however, you've not done anything particularly illegal lately, so what could you have done to deserve this animosity...]
	</phase>
	<a id="humpf">...?</a>
	<phase id="humpf" next="pf" frame="talk">
		[Dinoz master...!]
		[Yes! You!. The one dragging all these dinoz through the streets! I'm sure you've never asked if all your dinoz were bothering the residents of Dinotown!]
		[If it were up to me, I'd lock up the whole menagerie in the castle dungeons and have no qualms about it.]
	</phase>
	<a id="pf">What can I do for you?</a>
	<phase id="pf" next="chateau" frame="talk">
		[And he's asking ME questions now?]
		[All these Dinoz masters are nothing but scumbags, I'm telling you.]
		[They call themselves heroes too! Whatever... Save Dinoville once, and you never hear the end of it.]
		[LONG LIVE MODESTY!]
	</phase>
	<a id="chateau">But what have I done?</a>
	<phase id="chateau" next="viens" frame="talk">
		[You should know that the Royal Guard is more than capable of defending Dinoville, we don't need Dinoz masters like you.]
		[And as Captain of the guard, I'm keeping my eye on you!]
		[I still don't understand why his Majesty the King wishes to see you.]
	</phase>
	<a id="viens">I've been invited to the castle?</a>
	<phase id="viens" next="go" frame="talk">
		[If it were up to me, you'd be invited straight to the dungeons!]
		[Anyway, in the meantime, his Majesty the King wants to meet the Dinoz master that he's heard so much about.]
	</phase>
	<a id="go">Where is the castle?</a>
	<phase id="go" next="suis" frame="talk">
		[Hmmpf, you just follow the road to Dinoplaza, go past the Cinema Paradino, and you'll arrive at the border guard post.]
		[Don't get lost on the road, and whatever you do, don't keep the King waiting!]
	</phase>
	<a id="suis">I'm on my way!</a>
	<phase id="suis" fast="1" scenario="king:1" frame="vide">
		The captain has set off well ahead of you, her mission accomplished, she has no inclination to spend any more time at your side.
		Let's hope she's in a better mood the next time you meet her.
	</phase>
</d>

<d place="poste" gfx="garde_dnv" background="2" name="Captain of the Guard" cond="scenario(king,1)">
	<phase id="begin" next="block" frame="vide" fast="1">
		You see a passage leading to a plateau which overlooks all of Dinoplaza, the castle must have been there the whole time!
		There is a troop of soldiers around the frontier guard post preventing access to the castle.
	</phase>
	<a id="block">Let's see what she's been up to.</a>
	<phase id="block" frame="talk" next="lichen">
		[There you are... You took your time!]
		[Your interview with the King is going to have to wait, access to the castle has been blocked again.]
	</phase>
	<a id="lichen">Blocked?</a>
	<phase id="lichen" frame="lichen" next="why">
		[As you can see, some kind of phosphorescent lichen is stopping us from going any further.]
	</phase>
	<a id="why">How did it manage to grow so quickly?</a>
	<phase id="why" next="how" frame="talk">
		[This is happening more and more regularly. I did warn the King that he shouldn't stock so much mana in the castle.]
		[However, the astronomical quantity of mana created in the mana wars has to be stored somewhere.]
		[Thanks once again, dinoz masters!]
	</phase>
	<a id="how">Surely I can do something!</a>
	<phase id="how" next="oue" frame="talk">
		[You could make yourself useful, the soft shaman should have a solution for our problem!]
		[Be quick about it, the King waits for no man!]
	</phase>
	<a id="oue">To the Lavapit!</a>
	<phase id="oue" frame="stop" scenario="king:2" fast="1">
		The captain watches you out of the corner of her eye all the while barking orders to other guards.
		If you want to avoid her wrath, you should maybe get this mission completed asap.
	</phase>
</d>

<d place="fosslv" name="Soft Shaman" gfx="shaman" cond="scenario(king,2)">
	<inject id="shaman:begin" next="potion"/>
	<a id="potion">We have a problem at the castle!</a>
	<phase id="potion" next="trankil">
		[Oh dear... be calm, friend, the sea is not on fire...]
		[We don't see the King very often nowadays, is he enjoying himself in his castle?]
		[Sounds like it's quite a place to be these days, what with all the mana you guys are producing...]
	</phase>
	<a id="trankil">True story, this level of production seems to have some pretty serious side effects!</a>
	<phase id="trankil" next="alors">
		[Is it still that glowing lichen stuff sprouting around the castle?]
		[Personally I don't find it all that surprising... mana isn't exactly like a bad fix, but like most good gear, if you abuse it, it screws up your entire ecosystem man...]
		[I don't really know what the King is playing at, but you know what, he must know what he's doing, there are plenty boffins over there...]
	</phase>
	<a id="alors">Ok then, what can we do to solve the problem?</a>
	<phase id="alors" next="remede" scenario="king:3">
		[Well, look. The potion isn't that difficult to prepare, but it need a good shakeup, if you know what I mean.]
		[...]
		[No, you don't know what I mean, do you...]
		[OK, the Venerable is apparently the cat you need to see so I'll give you the potion and you can go and discuss it with him!]
		[If you've already defeated him once, it shouldn't be a problem for you.]
	</phase>
	<a id="remede">The Venerable? Gulp...</a>
	<phase id="remede" popup="1" fast="1">
		You are given a potion containing a blue flame @/img/icons/fx_potio1.gif@, it needs really well shaken up, remember!
	</phase>
</d>

<d place="vener" name="The Venerable" gfx="dorogon" cond="!(scenario(nimbao,14+)+scenario(nimbao,41-))+scenario(king,3)+(fx(vkill)|admin())">
	<inject id="venerable:begin" next="frappe"/>
	<a id="frappe">Sorry to disturb you, but I've got this potion...</a>
	<phase id="frappe" next="grr:pasgrr">
		[Grumpf...ROOOOAAARR!!!]
		[You disrupt my siesta for a damn potion!]
		[Prepare to feel my wrath! ROOOOAAARR!!!]
	</phase>
	<a id="grr">That works for me! Bring it!</a>
	<a id="pasgrr">Euh, maybe I'll come back later.</a>
	<phase id="pasgrr">
		You set off, leaving the venerable to his own devices. It's best to be well prepared before interrupting his siestas.
	</phase>
	<phase id="grr" fightgroup="vener4" next="cayest" scenario="king:4">
		[Grumpf, still as strong as ever I see.]
		[Fine then, you want my help. Tell me what you need.]
	</phase>
	<a id="cayest">As it happens, it's already done!</a>
	<phase id="cayest" next="done" scenario="king:5">
		[Go away then, I don't like it when you visit, I always end up with bruises.]
	</phase>
	<a id="done">See you soon!</a>
	<phase id="done"popup="1" fast="1">
		The potion now contains a red flame @/img/icons/fx_potio2.gif@, ideal for burning man-a-ctive plants!
	</phase>
</d>

<d place="poste" gfx="garde_dnv" frame="talk" background="2" name="Captain of the Guard" cond="scenario(king,4)|scenario(king,5)">
	<phase id="begin" next="etvous">
		[There you are... You took your time!]
		[Well, I hope you've found a solution for our problem.]
	</phase>
	<a id="etvous">Yes Captain! (What exactly was the contribution from your end?)</a>
	<phase id="etvous" next="lichenpouf">
		[We stopped the man-a-ctive lichen spreading.]
		[All that's left is for you to burn the source and then we'll finally be able to get to the castle.]
	</phase>
	<a id="lichenpouf">use the potion</a>
	<phase id="lichenpouf" next="gocastle" frame="pouf">
		[.....]
		[There we go, we're rid of the lichen. For now...]
	</phase>
	<a id="gocastle">To the castle!</a>
	<phase id="gocastle" scenario="king:6" fast="1" frame="stop">
		The captain has set off well ahead of you, you're finally going to meet the King of Dinoville.
		You've been waiting for this ever since grandpa joe told you stories of their golf games.
	</phase>
</d>

<d place="chato" gfx="gardien" frame="stop" background="1" name="King's Counsel" cond="scenario(king,6)">
	<phase id="begin" next="rien">
		[...]
		
		[...]
	</phase>
	<a id="rien">This counsellor isn't very chatty...</a>
	<phase id="rien">
		The Counsellor only speaks to the King and doesn't seem interested in you at all.
		He wandered around constantly waiting for you to leave, and strangely enough, in spite of his blindness, he didn't bump into anything...
	</phase>
</d>

<d place="chato" gfx="garde_dnv" frame="talk" background="1" name="Captain of the Guard" cond="scenario(king,6)">
	<phase id="begin" next="mission:end">
		[Stand to attention in the presence of the King!]
	</phase>
	<a id="mission" cond="tag(roi)">Consult the list of Missions</a>
	<phase id="mission" missions="roi"></phase>
	<a id="end" cond="mission(roif)">I've completed the missions</a>
	<phase id="end">
		[Hmpf, I suppose suppose I should congratulate you then.]
		[Don't use this as reason to be a smartass while you're within the castle walls, I've still got my eye on you!]
	</phase>
</d>

<d place="chato" gfx="roi" background="1" name="The King of Dinoville"  cond="scenario(king,6)+!curmission(roif)">
	<phase id="begin" next="leroi" frame="cottent">
		You enter a large room, and in the centre, you see the King sitting on his throne, with the captain, and an apparently eccentric individual at his sides.
		The King is trembling with anticipation of meeting you.
	</phase>
	<a id="leroi">Your Majesty.</a>
	<phase id="leroi" next="story:end" frame="blabla">
		[Oh, oh, oh!]
		[Finally, the Dinoz master I've been hearing about for so long!]
		[You must have many stories to tell me, please, take a seat and tell me everything!]
	</phase>
	<a id="story">I can tell you about my adventure in the Dark World!</a>
	<phase id="story" next="toobad" gfx="gardien" frame="talk" name="King's Counsel">
		[Majesty, it is unwise to delay at a time like this.]
		[The kingdom needs your undivided attention...]
	</phase>
	<a id="toobad">(...PFFFT!)</a>
	<a id="end" cond="mission(roif)">I've completed the missions</a>
	<phase id="toobad" tag="roi" frame="blabla">
		[Dinoz master!]
		[The Kingdom needs your help!]
		[Could you carry out some missions for me? You will be justly rewarded!]
		[If you go and see my Captain, you can see the list of missions which are critical to the Kingdom's wellbeing!]
		[...Nonetheless, I'd like to visit this Dark World...]	
	</phase>
	<phase id="end" frame="blabla">
		[Congratulations Dinoz master!]
		[You really helped us out.]
		[Thanks to you and our dear Captain, Dinoville is safer than ever before.]
		[And even better, I got to visit the Dark World...]
		[What a terrifying place, who would have thought an alternative Dinoland existed... for my money, we haven't heard the last of it...]
	</phase>
</d>























