<!-- ANIMATION DE ST.PATRICK 2013 SERVEUR EN-->


<d place="port" name="Shaun DeLear" gfx="leprechaun" cond="active(leprechaun)+gvar(xavent,0)+event(xstpatrick)+!uvar(xmasev)">
	<phase id="begin" background="1" next="gift">
		[Top o' the mornin' to ye!]
		[Ah sure it's a grand day t' be out and about, getting some fresh air before the big day... y'know, St. Patricks's day!]
		[Ah come on now, don't be tellin' me ye didn't know what St. Patrick's day was?]
		[Haha yer windin' me up 'der sure? Ah ye nearly got me 'der! Here ye go, here's a gift for ye!]
	</phase>	
	<a id="gift">Wow, 2 Irma's potions! Thanks very much!!</a>
	<phase id="gift" give="irma:2" nocheck="1" next="cool" uvar="xmasev:1" background="1">		
		[Well then, I'll be off... Gots to get ready for de drinkin' an' de partyin' tomorrow sure, come and see me if you're celebrating, I'll be knocking around for a few days so!]
		[Be well!]
	</phase>
	<a id="cool">Thanks for the potions Shaun!</a>
	<phase id="cool" fast="1" frame="atchoz" background="1">
		You head off, over the moon, with the Irma's Potions in your hand!
		I thought leprechauns were evil... maybe I've just been watching too many low-budget horror movies!
	</phase>
</d>

<d place="fosslv" name="Al O'Moaney" gfx="leprechaun" cond="(active(leprechaun)|admin())+gvar(xavent,1)+event(xstpatrick)+!uvar(xmasev)">
	<phase id="begin" background="2" next="gift">
		[Hi diddle dee dee, a... Oh! Hello there - nice weather for ducks, eh fella?]
		[I hear ye met me brother Shaun yesterday, me name's Al O'Moaney, but Betty when you call me you can call me Al!]
		[I'm full o' the joys today to be sure, although I might just be full of the Guinness! Have a grand St. Patrick's day when it comes!]
	</phase>	
	<a id="gift">What's this? More gifts? Sweet!!</a>
	<phase id="gift" give="tictac:1" nocheck="1" next="cool" uvar="xmasev:1" background="2">
		[There you go! A *Tac Ticket* - get yourself up to Papy Joes - tell 'im I was askin' for 'im sure!]
		[If it's gifts yer after, try to catch me cousin Ronan tomorrow!]
		[Good luck!]
	</phase>
	<a id="cool">Thanks for the ticket Al, I'll be seeing you!</a>
	<phase id="cool" fast="1"  frame="simploz" background="2">
		You head off, over the moon, with the Ticket in your hand!
		I thought leprechauns were miserly... maybe I should stop reading graphic novels!
	</phase>
</d>

<d place="corail" name="Ronan O'Haha" gfx="leprechaun" cond="(active(leprechaun)|admin())+gvar(xavent,2)+event(xstpatrick)+!uvar(xmasev)">
	<phase id="begin" background="3" next="gift">
		[Ah there ye are sure!]
		[Oh whit a head I've got on me today, it feels like Flatley and his troupe are riverdancing in me head!]
		[I found these in my coat this morning when I woke up in the hedge there - take 'em, they're yours! I say my coat, I found it in the hedge. Anyways...]
	</phase>
	<a id="gift">Great!! Thanks, I can always use Irma's Potions</a>
	<phase id="gift" give="irma:3" nocheck="1" next="cool" uvar="xmasev:1" background="3">
		[Irma's get you moving when you would usually have to wait for a new turn!]
		[I, however won't be needin' them... I'll be back on the Pat Cash tonight sure, startin' in the Hairy Lemon, on to Flannery's, Coppers, the lot!]
		[Good luck te ye!]
	</phase>
	<a id="cool">Thanks for everything, especially the potions - they're really useful!</a>
	<phase id="cool" fast="1" frame="neigeoz" background="3">
		You head off, over the moon, with Irma's Potions rattling in your pockets!
		Maybe it's not true what they say about leprechauns - this one seems pretty likeable!
	</phase>
</d>

<d place="svillg" name="Pat MacGroyne" gfx="leprechaun" cond="(active(leprechaun)|admin())+gvar(xavent,3)+event(xstpatrick)+!uvar(xmasev)">
	<phase id="begin" background="3" next="affts">	
		[*singing* Oh I used to work in Killarney, in de ol' department store, I used to work in Killarney, I don't work der any more!]
		[A man came into de store one day an' he asked me for some fish he did.]
	</phase>
	<a id="affts">A fish from the store?</a>
	<phase id="affts" next="gift">
		[A fish from the store. A fish he wanted, codswallop he got! I don't work there any more.]
	</phase>
	<a id="gift">Haha! I hope this isn't your day job!</a>
	<phase id="gift" giveingr="fish3:2" nocheck="1" next="cool" uvar="xmasev:1" background="3">
		[There ye are! Some fishes fer me favourite master!]
		[Ye'll be gettin' a good price fer those there...]
		[Sure you might bump into my second cousin twice removed if you're around tomorrow...]
	</phase>
	<a id="cool">Thanks, that's really kind of you!</a>
	<phase id="cool" fast="1" frame="joyoz" background="3">
		You head off, over the moon, with the fish in your bag!
		It's a shame Pat wasn't staying longer - i was really getting to like him!
	</phase>	
</d>

<d place="iroche" name="Rick O'Shea" gfx="leprechaun" cond="active(leprechaun)+gvar(xavent,4)+event(xstpatrick)+!uvar(xmasev)">
	<phase id="begin" background="1" next="gift">
		[Ah hello hello 'der master!]
		[I hope yer as excited as we are for the weekend now!]
		[There'll be dancin' in the streets of Dinotown this Sunday to be sure!]
		[If yer not there, ye'll be missin' out there so! Take this bread to keep the wolf from the door!]
	</phase>	
	<a id="gift">Authentic bread? Brilliant, this will definitely come in handy!!</a>
	<phase id="gift" give="hotpan:1" nocheck="1" next="cool" uvar="xmasev:1" background="1">		
		[OK, I can't hang around all day... If you're doing some travelling, you might bump into my cousin Phil tomorrow!]
		[If you do, tell 'im he'd better not be late for Sunday!]
	</phase>
	<a id="cool">Thanks for the bread Rick!</a>
	<phase id="cool" fast="1" frame="atchoz" background="1">
		You head off happy to have met Mr O'Shea and aven happier with the free bread!!
		There I thought St. Paddy's day was just for the Irish... seems everyone is invited!
	</phase>
</d>

<d place="cpuits" name="Phil McCracken" gfx="leprechaun" cond="(active(leprechaun)|admin())+gvar(xavent,5)+event(xstpatrick)+!uvar(xmasev)">
	<phase id="begin" background="3" next="gift">
		[Mornin' mornin' mornin'!]
		[You've just caught me, I'm off down the Old Storehouse fir a couple before stockin' up for tomorrow... the big day!]
		[Got to go, but take this and top o' the mornin' to ya...]
	</phase>
	<a id="gift">And the rest o' the day to yourself Phil!! (Where did THAT come from?) Erm... Thanks, I love Magic Fuses</a>
	<phase id="gift" give="petard:2" nocheck="1" next="cool" uvar="xmasev:1" background="3">
		[Head over to Dinotown and try yer luck on the grid!]
		[I'm not goin' to need them this weekend... sur I'll have forgotten I gave you them by tomorrow!]
		[All the best sir!]
	</phase>
	<a id="cool">Thanks for the fuses Phil - fingers crossed!</a>
	<phase id="cool" fast="1" frame="neigeoz" background="3">
		You head off, over the moon, with the fuses nesteld in your hip pocket!
		I could really get used to these little guys hanging around you know...
	</phase>
</d>

<d place="dnv" name="Paddy O'Furniture" gfx="leprechaun" cond="(active(leprechaun)|admin())+gvar(xavent,6)+event(xstpatrick)+!uvar(xmasev)">
	<phase id="begin" background="3" next="gift">	
		[Hello der Dinoz Master!]
		[Sure ye just caught me - I'm headin' back to Ireland tonight.
		It's been a pleasure sure, here - take these!]
	</phase>
	<a id="gift">Wow! Awesome!!</a>
	<phase id="gift" give="tictac:2" nocheck="1" next="cool" uvar="xmasev:1" background="3">
		[There you go! A couple o' tickets for the big game at Joe's!]
		[Best get up there before the place is all dug up sure!]
		[Ye'll not be seein' me for a while - Take care!]
	</phase>
	<a id="cool">Thanks, that's really kind of you!</a>
	<phase id="cool" fast="1" frame="joyoz" background="3">
		You head off, over the moon, with the tickets in your hand!
		St. Paddy's day is almost gone... maybe we'll see you next year!
	</phase>	
</d>