<tutorial>
	<t id="first">
		<s id="welcome" auto="1">Welcome, agent ::name::. My name is *Circe*. I've been given the task of taking your through *a quick refresher course in what it is you do*.</s>
		<s id="welcome2" auto="1" y="1">You are connected to your target's computer network.</s>
		<s id="entrance" auto="1">This is the access point, this is your entrance and exit (*to log out at the end of your mission*).</s>
		<s id="connect">Connect to the *training terminal* by clicking on it.</s>
		<s id="showDock" auto="1">This is where to find your viruses. *You can use viruses to accomplish various tasks*: inflicting damage, copying a file, detecting anti-virus systems... </s>
		<s id="showDmgVirus" y="0">For example, this virus *inflicts damage*: click on it to activate it.</s>
		<s id="damageExp" auto="1">Most viruses require a *target* to function. In the case of a *damage* virus like this one, *the target will the file being attacked*.</s>
		<s id="askTarget">Choose *a DOC file* from those below to select it as your target.</s>
		<s id="fileDestroyed" auto="1" y="1">Once a file takes too much damage it will be destroyed. DOC files are simple documents: this means they are not very resistant to attack.</s>
		<s id="mana" auto="1">Deploying a virus *costs resources*. Your resource reserves are represented by the blue bar.</s>
		<s id="briefing" auto="1">Now, back to our mission! Your mission objective is displayed *underneath the game window*.</s>
		<s id="briefing2" auto="1">In this mission, your client has asked you to *crash the training terminal*. You are currently connected to it.</s>
		<s id="briefing3" auto="1">To crash a system, you have to *delete all files in thy system with the extension CORE* (i.e. the filename ends in "CORE").</s>
		<s id="briefing4" auto="1" y="1">As there are none of these here, you will have to *search the folders* on the training terminal in order to find them.</s>
		<s id="cd">Click on the *folder* icon to open it.</s>
		<s id="core">Here is a *CORE file*! Destroy it using your damage virus.</s>
		<s id="shield" auto="1" y="1">Unfortunately, the task is rarely as simple as this: *CORE files are often extremely well guarded*.</s>
		<s id="shield2" auto="1">This icon shows that the CORE file is protected against damage.</s>
		<s id="guardian" auto="1" y="1">GUARDIAN files protect CORE files. *Destroy them first to then be able to destroy the CORE system files* (there is only one in this mission).</s>
		<s id="targetGuardian" y="1">Click on the GUARDIAN file to target it.</s>
		<s id="attackGuardian" y="1">Click multiple times on the damage virus to repeat attacks.</s>
		<s id="coreExposed">The CORE file is no longer protected: *destroy it*.</s>
		<s id="crashed">Good work! Your mission is complete, now simply *log out* to receive your bonus.</s>
	</t>

	<t id="second">
		<s id="hiAgain" auto="1">First of all, allow me to congratulate you on successfully completing your *first test*.</s>
		<s id="avIntro" auto="1">During this mission, we're dropping you in to a *real situation*. You also risk coming across *anti-virus* systems.</s>
		<s id="avIntro2" auto="1">These programs are used by administrators as *defences against your viruses*. Inflict *damage* on them to get rid of them.</s>
		<s id="avIntro3" auto="1">Most anti-virus systems *react to your actions*. Example: the *MINE* anti-virus will inflict damage on you *if you leave the folder in which it is installed*. It is therefore in your best interests to delete this anti-virus before you go anywhere else, let's call it *damage limitation*...</s>
		<s id="life" auto="1">If you take damage, you lose *armor points* (the green bar on your screen). If your armor drops to *zero*, your terminal will be put out of service and you'll have no opttion but to *abandon your mission*.</s>
		<s id="avIntro4" auto="1">other anti-virus systems are more *passive*: they *protect other files* or *disrupt your actions*.</s>
		<s id="endSecond" auto="1">Now it's down to you. *Delete the files you were instructed to*.</s>
		<s id="waitConnect">Log in to one of the terminals on this network, *it's most likely here that you'll find the MAIL folders*.</s>
		<s id="scanner">We strongly recommend you to use your scanner to *check out a system*. It can be extremely useful indeed.</s>
		<s id="scannerDone" auto="1" y="1">The SCANNER provides you wih a map of the system. *Certain upgraded versions of the SCANNER even allow you to find anti-virus systems!* However, you need the means to acquire these much sought-after versions.</s>
		<s id="scannerDone2" auto="1" y="1">As you have been asked to delete MAIL files, the places you should be looking on this system should correspond more or less to that genre of file...</s>
		<s id="scannerDone3" auto="1" y="1">*On the list on the left*, find a folder which is likely to contain MAIL files.</s>
		<s id="mapDone" y="1">Once you have finished *examining the map*, click here to close the SCANNER.</s>
		<s id="mapAfter" y="1" auto="1">Good. Do you know which folder to open to find the MAIL files?</s>
		<s id="userProfile">This folder looks like a *user folder*... Here you will generally find personal files belonging to the owner of this computer (documents, mails, videos...).</s>
		<s id="waitDelete" y="1">Find then destroy the requested files.</s>
		<s id="showLog" auto="1">Notice that there is a REGISTER here. *This is of the highest importance, because this shows you everything that is happening in the game*: damage sustained, mission progress, other events...</s>
		<s id="showLog2">You can check the most recent messages in the register at any time by clicking here.</s>
		<s id="showLog3">You can close the history by clicking here, or by pressing *Escape* on your keyboard.</s>
		<s id="showLog4" auto="1" y="0">Always keep an eye on the *register*. Now back to work.</s>
		<s id="waitKillMail">-</s>
		<s id="deletedAll" auto="1" y="1">Good work! Your mission is complete, all that remains is for you to *log out* to receive your bonus.</s>
		<s id="exit1" y="1">Clion this icon to *return to the parent folder*.</s>
		<s id="exit2" y="1">This icon allows you to *disconnect from the system*.</s>
		<s id="nowExit">Click on the *access point* to *complete the mission*.</s>
	</t>

	<t id="third">
		<s id="bypassIntro" auto="1">During previous missions, we have only come across "simple" tasks: a few anti-virus systems or guardians getting in the way of your acting freely.</s>
		<s id="bypassIntro2" auto="1">In reality, you will often find that the system you need to access is *hidden behind another system*.</s>
		<s id="showTargetTerm" auto="1">Let's look at the training terminal here.</s>
		<s id="showFirewall" auto="1">It is located behind a firewall so it cannot be accessed directly.</s>
		<s id="showTargetTerm2">Click on the training terminal.</s>
		<s id="unreachable" auto="1" y="1">The red line between the access point and the terminal indicates that you cannot connect to it.</s>
		<s id="needBypass" auto="1">The only solution is to *find a way through the firewall*.</s>
		<s id="bypassMethods1" auto="1">There are 2 ways to proceed: the brutal method, which is to *destroy all the CORE files* relating to the firewall.</s>
		<s id="bypassMethods2" auto="1">The more subtle approach is to *corrupt all the CONTROL files* present in the firewall. This method, however, requires a *CORRUPTION virus* which you don't yet have in your possession.</s>
		<s id="connectFirewall">Therefore, we are going to use the *brutal method* (deleting *CORE* files). Log in to the firewall.</s>
		<s id="openSys" auto="1">You also have the option of *destroying anti-virus systems* which may get in your way. Otherwise, open the folder containing the *CORE* files.</s>
		<s id="waitOpenSys">-</s>
		<s id="killCore" auto="1" y="1">*Destroy the CORE*. Remember to get rid of the *GUARDIAN files* first of all.</s>
		<s id="waitKillCore">-</s>
		<s id="bypassed" auto="1" y="1">Perfect, *you have crashed the firewall!* The route to your target is now clear.</s>
		<s id="copyFile" y="1">Find the file you were asked to obtain.</s>
		<s id="copyFile2">Use the COPY virus on the required file.</s>
		<s id="copied" y="1">*You have achieved your objective!* Log out to confirm completion of your mission.</s>
	</t>

</tutorial>
