<text>

	<c id="espion">
		<t>No job too big for Agent 009!</t>
		<t>I am a double agent!</t>
		<t>Nobody worked out my triple identity!</t>
		<t rare="1">The micro-film is in my underpants!</t>
		<t>I'll never talk!</t>
		<t>Another brilliantly successful mission!</t>
		<t rare="1">I'm going to hack into the system and take over the DB. Piece of cake!</t>
		<t>Sorry, I knew that already!</t>
		<t>You are the most pathetic bad guy in history!</t>
		<t rare="1">Haha, I've never been hit between the legs with a laser!</t>
		<t>BOOM! Invisible mode. Your security system is officially worthless!</t>
		<t>Why are female spies always drop-dead gorgeous?</t>
		<t>I've only got 30 seconds left to defuse the bomb!</t>
		<t>Your mission should you choose to accept it... whatever, no worries. I got this!</t>
		<t>I'm not who you think I am, which isn't great for you either...</t>
		<t>My watch contains a miniature detonator!</t>
		<t>I am the man of a thousand faces, nobody knows my true identity!</t>
		<t rare="1">I travel so much that the earth is my playing field!</t>
		<t>My contact is in Copacabana... again!</t>
		<t>I'm being followed. The situation is critical... Or not!</t>
		<t>An XYZ cocktail on the rocks please!</t>
	</c>

	<c id="acteur">
		<t>I dedicate this Oscar to my family!</t>
		<t>And that's another victory for the sacred tree feller!</t>
		<t>In life, there are two kinds of people. Those who've got it and those who don't!</t>
		<t>I've waited for this moment all my life. Now, finally, recognition!</t>
		<t>I play the role of a brain-eating psychopath... Bleeuugh!</t>
		<t rare="1">I do my own stunts!</t>
		<t>No photos please!</t>
		<t>The camera flashes light me up as bright as day!</t>
		<t>And there you go, divorce number 5!</t>
		<t rare="1">I've adopted 12 children... What are they called again?</t>
		<t>If I'd had relations with that woman, I'd know about it!</t>
		<t rare="1">We met in which film again?</t>
		<t>I have to choose between Burton and Scorcese, what should I do?</t>
		<t>If I want to cry in a scene, I pull out some nose hair!</t>
		<t>Gossip journalists know more about my life than I do!</t>
		<t>Would you like an autograph?</t>
		<t rare="1">I know Mr Willis well, we saved the world together once!</t>
		<t>It feels strange to be 1/3 of the film's production budget?</t>
		<t>Come and visit me in California or Cathcart!</t>
		<t>I'm an actor, producer, director and extra all at once!</t>
	</c>

	<c id="sportif">
		<t>Another magnificent goal. My bonus just went up!</t>
		<t rare="1">One more header, one less neuron, a boost to the bonus!</t>
		<t>A three-pointer from the other end of the court - too easy!</t>
		<t>Oh say can you see by the dawn's... what comes next?!</t>
		<t>My father was a famous footballer - life's been tough for me!</t>
		<t>I told Tiger to go and look for me in the woods for me!</t>
		<t rare="1">I have to film an ad for chocolate? Is this a joke?</t>
		<t rare="1">My racquet is an extension of my body. I sleep with it!</t>
		<t>I wouldn't mind a bit more EPO!</t>
		<t>Médaille d'or au curling, la classe !</t>
		<t>Feel the rhythm! Feel the rhyme! Get on up, its bobsled time...</t>
		<t>I declare this Olympic games open. No no no, don't thank me!</t>
		<t>I dedicate this victory to my mother!</t>
		<t>Multi-Strike a perfect score. One!</t>
		<t>Watch out - I'm on my way, this crowd will go crazy when I get here!</t>
		<t>A gentle stroll, 100m in 8 seconds. Standard.</t>
		<t>Right hook, stinging uppercut, opponent on the canvas, KO!</t>
		<t>A winning smash, and a standing ovation at Roland Garros!</t>
		<t>When I retire, I'll be the minister for sport!</t>
		<t rare="1">Onward to the... Falcon shooting, YEAAAHHH!</t>
	</c>

	<c id="chanteur">
		<t>Quelle maîtrise, quel talent, je suis le meilleur !</t>
		<t>Mon tube est disque d'or avant même d'être sorti !</t>
		<t>Un petit solo à la guitare, la scène est hypnotisée !</t>
		<t rare="1">Je remplis le stade de France quand je veux !</t>
		<t>Et je chante, je danse, jusqu'au bout de la nuit !</t>
		<t>Je suis en tournée dans le monde entier !</t>
		<t>Après Paris, New-York et Londres, en avant pour Tokyo !</t>
		<t>Mon timbre de voix est si puissant qu'il fait trembler les murs !</t>
		<t>Ma chanson est traduite dans plus de langues que la Bible !</t>
		<t rare="1">La page web de mon groupe de Rock a plus d'un million de vues !</t>
		<t rare="1">Je viens de composer ma 9ème symphonie !</t>
		<t>Avec ça, je mériterai ma place parmi les Enfoirés !</t>
		<t>Pas besoin de micro, ma voix porte à 3 km !</t>
		<t>Zazie me demande encore un duo !</t>
		<t>Il manque encore une corde à mon Stradivarius pour que je puisse exprimer tout mon talent !</t>
		<t>Chef d'orchestre de l'opéra de Prague, y'a pire comme boulot !</t>
		<t>J'ai tourné le clip de mon dernier titre en Polynésie française, la vie est belle !</t>
		<t>Mon tube est premier au Top50 depuis l'année dernière !</t>
		<t rare="1">Après U2, c'est décidé je me lance en solo, appelez moi U1 !</t>
		<t>On m'a demandé de donner un concert lors de l'ouverture des JO !</t>
	</c>
	
</text>
